<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<GettingAroundAustralia pageID="33" isTemplate="1">
	<breadcrumb>
		<element level="1">
			<headline><![CDATA[Homepage ]]></headline>
			<href><![CDATA[/index.xml]]></href>
		</element>
		<element level="2">
			<headline><![CDATA[Plan]]></headline>
			<href><![CDATA[/plan.xml]]></href>
		</element>
		<element level="4">
			<headline><![CDATA[Getting Around Australia]]></headline>
			<href><![CDATA[/plan/while-your-here/getting-around.xml]]></href>
		</element>

	</breadcrumb>
	<hdl_Title><![CDATA[Getting Around Australia]]></hdl_Title>
	<img_Banner><![CDATA[/contentimages/plan-while-youre-here-getting-around.jpg]]></img_Banner>
	<img_SearchThumbnail><![CDATA[/thumbnails/plan-while-youre-here-getting-around-search.jpg]]></img_SearchThumbnail>
	<img_Thumbnail><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/plan-while-youre-here-getting-around-th.jpg" alt="Getting Around Australia">]]></img_Thumbnail>
	<opt_HideInBreadcrumbs><![CDATA[]]>
	</opt_HideInBreadcrumbs>
	<stf_description><![CDATA[Find info on getting around Australia by plane, car, bus, coach, train, public transport, ferry and walking. Australia is a big, but it's easy to enjoy.]]></stf_description>
	<stf_ExcludedCountries><![CDATA[AU]]></stf_ExcludedCountries>
	<stf_hideInXmlSitemap><![CDATA[]]>
	</stf_hideInXmlSitemap>
	<stf_ImageLocation><![CDATA[The Sunlander External]]></stf_ImageLocation>
	<stf_IsExternalSiteArticle><![CDATA[]]>
	</stf_IsExternalSiteArticle>
	<stf_IsMobile><![CDATA[y]]></stf_IsMobile>
	<stf_keywords><![CDATA[Getting Around Australia, transport, travel]]></stf_keywords>
	<stf_LinkLearnMore><![CDATA[Learn More]]></stf_LinkLearnMore>
	<stf_NavigationTitle><![CDATA[Getting around Australia]]></stf_NavigationTitle>
	<stf_PageHeading><![CDATA[]]>
	</stf_PageHeading>
	<stf_TargetedCountries><![CDATA[]]>
	</stf_TargetedCountries>
	<TA_Title><![CDATA[Getting Around Australia]]></TA_Title>
	<txt_Teaser>
        <![CDATA[
        Find info on getting around Australia by plane, car, bus, coach, train, public transport, ferry and walking. Australia is a big, but it's easy to enjoy.
    ]]>
	</txt_Teaser>
	<con_Body>
		<TopCategoryHighlights isTemplate="1">
			<stf_Heading><![CDATA[Getting Around Australia]]></stf_Heading>
			<stf_InformationTitle><![CDATA[]]>
			</stf_InformationTitle>
			<txt_Information><![CDATA[You know Australia is a big country, but you may not know how easy it is to get around. The untouched beaches that stretch for miles and deserts that touch the horizon are all within your reach. Want to sail the Whitsundays, cross the continent by car or take a train through the rainforest canopy? Following are the different ways you can explore our vast and diverse country.&nbsp; 
<P></P>]]></txt_Information>
			<con_CenterContent>
				<CenterContent isTemplate="1">
					<hdl_Title><![CDATA[Air]]></hdl_Title>
					<img_MainImage><![CDATA[]]>
					</img_MainImage>
					<stf_Caption><![CDATA[]]>
					</stf_Caption>
					<anc_link><![CDATA[]]>
					</anc_link>
					<txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[
        Flying is the best way to cover large distances in a short time. You’ll spend less time travelling and more time on the ground savouring Australia’s can’t-miss landscapes and laid-back lifestyle. Australia’s domestic airlines – Qantas, Jetstar, Virgin Blue, Rex and their subsidiaries - serve all state <a href="/about/australias-landscapes/cities.xml" target="_self">capital cities</a> and <a href="/explore/cities/regional-cities.xml" target="_self">regional centres</a>. Competition amongst domestic airlines means that great fares are available. 
    ]]>
					</txt_Information>
				</CenterContent>
				<CenterContent isTemplate="1">
					<hdl_Title><![CDATA[Drive]]></hdl_Title>
					<img_MainImage><![CDATA[]]>
					</img_MainImage>
					<stf_Caption><![CDATA[]]>
					</stf_Caption>
					<anc_link><![CDATA[]]>
					</anc_link>
					<txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[
        Australia has a vast network of well-maintained roads and some of the most beautiful <a href="/explore/itineraries-ideas/holiday-ideas.xml" target="_self">touring routes</a> in the world. Travel from <a href="/explore/cities/sydney.xml" target="_self">Sydney</a> to <a href="/explore/cities/brisbane.xml" target="_self">Brisbane</a> past sleepy seaside towns and lush hinterland. Experience Australia’s <a href="/explore/icons/red-centre.xml" target="_self">Red Centre</a> in an epic drive across the desert. Or follow Victoria’s <a href="/explore/icons/great-ocean-road.xml" target="_self">Great Ocean Road</a> as it hugs our spectacular south-east coast. You’ll find car rental companies at major airports, central city locations, suburbs and resorts. So hire a car, four wheel drive, caravans or motorbike and hit the highway.  
    ]]>
					</txt_Information>
				</CenterContent>
				<CenterContent isTemplate="1">
					<hdl_Title><![CDATA[Driving Laws]]></hdl_Title>
					<img_MainImage><![CDATA[]]>
					</img_MainImage>
					<stf_Caption><![CDATA[]]>
					</stf_Caption>
					<anc_link><![CDATA[]]>
					</anc_link>
					<txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[Australians drive on the left-hand side of the road, with the steering wheel on the right-hand side of the car. The maximum speed limit in cities and towns is 60km/h and 50km/h&nbsp; in some suburban areas. On country roads and highways, the maximum speed is usually 110km/h. For your safety, drink-driving laws apply, and drivers and passengers must wear seat belts at all times. Motor cyclists and cyclists must wear helmets. An international visitor may drive in Australia on a valid overseas driver’s licence for the same class of vehicle. You should carry both your home licence and international licence when driving. ]]>
					</txt_Information>
				</CenterContent>
				<CenterContent isTemplate="1">
					<hdl_Title><![CDATA[Bus/Coach]]></hdl_Title>
					<img_MainImage><![CDATA[]]>
					</img_MainImage>
					<stf_Caption><![CDATA[]]>
					</stf_Caption>
					<anc_link><![CDATA[]]>
					</anc_link>
					<txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[Coach and bus travel in Australia is comfortable, easy and economical. Coaches generally have air conditioning, reading lights, adjustable seats and videos. Services are frequent, affordable and efficient. Australia’s national coach operator, Greyhound, offer passes to fit every budget. ]]>
					</txt_Information>
				</CenterContent>
				<CenterContent isTemplate="1">
					<hdl_Title><![CDATA[Rail]]></hdl_Title>
					<img_MainImage><![CDATA[]]>
					</img_MainImage>
					<stf_Caption><![CDATA[]]>
					</stf_Caption>
					<anc_link><![CDATA[]]>
					</anc_link>
					<txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[
        Train travel is a convenient, affordable and scenic way to explore Australia. Interstate and intra-state rail services connect our cities and regional centres, while cross-country train trips offer a unique insight into Australia’s size and diversity.  Travelling options range from budget to luxury, and a range of rail passes can reduce your costs if you plan to see large sections of the country.
        <p>Countrylink trains connect <a href="/explore/states/nsw.xml" target="_self">New South Wales</a> destinations and also travel along Australia’s east coast to <a href="/explore/cities/melbourne.xml" target="_self">Melbourne</a>, Brisbane and <a href="/explore/cities/canberra.xml" target="_self">Canberra</a>.  VLine trains link Melbourne with regional hubs in <a href="/explore/states/vic.xml" target="_self">Victoria</a>, Traveltrain covers <a href="/explore/states/qld.xml" target="_self">Queensland</a> and TransWA criss-crosses <a href="/explore/states/wa.xml" target="_self">Western Australia</a>. </p>
        <p>Australia also has epic rail journeys such as The Ghan and Indian-Pacific, which sweep across the continent, offering comfort and a sense bygone romance. The Indian-Pacific travels between Sydney to Perth, stopping for whistle-stop tours of Broken Hill, Adelaide and gold-rich Kalgoorlie. The legendary Ghan travels between Adelaide and Darwin, taking in Australia’s Red Centre and the tropical Top End.</p>
    ]]>
					</txt_Information>
				</CenterContent>
				<CenterContent isTemplate="1">
					<hdl_Title><![CDATA[Public Transport]]></hdl_Title>
					<img_MainImage><![CDATA[]]>
					</img_MainImage>
					<stf_Caption><![CDATA[]]>
					</stf_Caption>
					<anc_link><![CDATA[]]>
					</anc_link>
					<txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[All of Australia’s capital cities are served by a wide variety of public transport, including trains, buses, ferries, monorail, light rail and trams.&nbsp; Taxis charge according to their meter. ]]>
					</txt_Information>
				</CenterContent>
				<CenterContent isTemplate="1">
					<hdl_Title><![CDATA[Ferries]]></hdl_Title>
					<img_MainImage><![CDATA[]]>
					</img_MainImage>
					<stf_Caption><![CDATA[]]>
					</stf_Caption>
					<anc_link><![CDATA[]]>
					</anc_link>
					<txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[
        The Spirit of Tasmania runs a passenger and vehicle ferry service between Melbourne and <a href="/explore/states/tas.xml" target="_self">Tasmania</a> nightly. Extra services are running during summer peak times.  Sealink ferries connect South Australia and <a href="/explore/icons/kangaroo-island.xml" target="_self">Kangaroo Island</a> several times a day.  Ferries connect suburbs in our capital cities – they criss-cross Sydney Harbour, the Swan River in Perth and the Brisbane River in Brisbane. 
    ]]>
					</txt_Information>
				</CenterContent>
				<CenterContent isTemplate="1">
					<hdl_Title><![CDATA[Walks]]></hdl_Title>
					<img_MainImage><![CDATA[]]>
					</img_MainImage>
					<stf_Caption><![CDATA[]]>
					</stf_Caption>
					<anc_link><![CDATA[]]>
					</anc_link>
					<txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[
        Walking is a great way to get around our cities, so get ready to pound our wide, easy-on-the-feet pedestrian streets. You can also  tackle some of the longest <a href="/explore/itineraries-ideas/walking-australia.xml" target="_self">tracks and trails</a> in the world in Australia – impressive journeys of a thousand kilometres or more that can take several weeks to complete.
    ]]>
					</txt_Information>
				</CenterContent>
			</con_CenterContent>
		</TopCategoryHighlights>
	</con_Body>
</GettingAroundAustralia>