<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<ConsumerBaseFoundation pageID="50" isTemplate="1">
    <breadcrumb>
        <element level="1">
            <headline><![CDATA[Homepage ]]></headline>
            <href><![CDATA[/index.xml]]></href>
        </element>
<element level="2">
            <headline><![CDATA[Explore ]]></headline>
            <href><![CDATA[/explore.xml]]></href>
        </element>
<element level="4">
            <headline><![CDATA[Australia’s Food and Wine]]></headline>
            <href><![CDATA[/explore/things-to-do/food-and-wine.xml]]></href>
        </element>

    </breadcrumb>
    <img_background><![CDATA[/contentimages/explore-things-to-see-do-food-wine.jpg]]></img_background>
    <hdl_Title><![CDATA[Australia’s Food and Wine]]></hdl_Title>
    <img_Banner><![CDATA[]]></img_Banner>
    <img_SearchThumbnail><![CDATA[/thumbnails/explore-things-to-see-do-food-wine-search.jpg]]></img_SearchThumbnail>
    <img_Thumbnail><![CDATA[/contentimages/explore-things-to-see-do-food-wine-th.jpg]]></img_Thumbnail>
    <opt_HideInBreadcrumbs><![CDATA[Show]]></opt_HideInBreadcrumbs>
    <opt_HidePage><![CDATA[no]]></opt_HidePage>
    <opt_hideTitle><![CDATA[0]]></opt_hideTitle>
    <opt_hide_in_sitemap><![CDATA[no]]></opt_hide_in_sitemap>
    <opt_IncludeVideo><![CDATA[0]]></opt_IncludeVideo>
    <opt_isHubPage><![CDATA[0]]></opt_isHubPage>
    <opt_isNewWindow><![CDATA[_self]]></opt_isNewWindow>
    <opt_PageLayout><![CDATA[]]></opt_PageLayout>
    <opt_PartnerLead><![CDATA[no]]></opt_PartnerLead>
    <stf_description><![CDATA[Learn about Australian food and wine culture. Discover our fresh produce, unique culinary style, wine regions, tasting events and more.]]></stf_description>
    <stf_ExcludedCountries><![CDATA[]]></stf_ExcludedCountries>
    <stf_hideInXmlSitemap><![CDATA[]]></stf_hideInXmlSitemap>
    <stf_ImageLocation><![CDATA[Maxwell Wines, McLaren Vale, Fleurieu Peninsula, SA. &copy; SATC]]></stf_ImageLocation>
    <stf_intro_title><![CDATA[]]></stf_intro_title>
    <stf_IsExternalSiteArticle><![CDATA[]]></stf_IsExternalSiteArticle>
    <stf_IsMobile><![CDATA[y]]></stf_IsMobile>
    <stf_keywords><![CDATA[Australian Food, Australian Wine]]></stf_keywords>
    <stf_LinkLearnMore><![CDATA[Learn More]]></stf_LinkLearnMore>
    <stf_NavigationTagLine><![CDATA[]]></stf_NavigationTagLine>
    <stf_PageHeading><![CDATA[]]></stf_PageHeading>
    <stf_TargetedCountries><![CDATA[]]></stf_TargetedCountries>
    <stf_TrackingTitle><![CDATA[]]></stf_TrackingTitle>
    <TA_Title><![CDATA[Australian Food &amp; Wine – Tourism Australia]]></TA_Title>
    <txt_Intro>
        <![CDATA[]]>
    </txt_Intro>
    <txt_MobileContentOnly>
        <![CDATA[]]>
    </txt_MobileContentOnly>
    <txt_SpotlightTag>
        <![CDATA[]]>
    </txt_SpotlightTag>
    <txt_Teaser>
        <![CDATA[
        Experience the freedom and creativity of Australia’s food and wine culture that helps us produce fresh and innovative flavours and wines that are the envy of the world.
    ]]>
    </txt_Teaser>
    <con_Body>
        <SubPageLayout isTemplate="1">
    <con_Banner>
        
    </con_Banner>
    <con_RHSModules>
        <Listing isTemplate="1">
<anc_List1><![CDATA[/about/australias-landscapes/australian-wineries.xml]]></anc_List1>
<anc_MoreLink><![CDATA[]]></anc_MoreLink>
<hdl_Title><![CDATA[More Australian Ideas]]></hdl_Title>
<img_Thumbnail><![CDATA[]]></img_Thumbnail>
<med_File><![CDATA[]]></med_File>
<opt_isNewWindow><![CDATA[]]></opt_isNewWindow>
<stf_externalLink><![CDATA[]]></stf_externalLink>
<stf_ExternalLinkTitle><![CDATA[]]></stf_ExternalLinkTitle>
<stf_IsExternalSiteArticle><![CDATA[]]></stf_IsExternalSiteArticle>
<stf_LinkLearnMore><![CDATA[]]></stf_LinkLearnMore>
<txt_Teaser><![CDATA[]]></txt_Teaser>
<opt_national_landscapes_id><![CDATA[]]></opt_national_landscapes_id>
<stf_hideInXmlSitemap><![CDATA[]]></stf_hideInXmlSitemap>
<stf_TargetedCountry><![CDATA[]]></stf_TargetedCountry>
<con_Banner></con_Banner>
<con_Body></con_Body>
<con_RHSModules></con_RHSModules>
<con_Category></con_Category>
<lst_Subpages></lst_Subpages>
</Listing><PlanYourVisit isTemplate="1">
<anc_AccommodationSearch><![CDATA[/AccommodationSearch.ignore]]></anc_AccommodationSearch>
<anc_ASPSearch><![CDATA[/plan/plan-your-trip/find-travel-agent.xml]]></anc_ASPSearch>
<anc_Attraction><![CDATA[/AttractionSearchResults.ignore]]></anc_Attraction>
<anc_Destinfo><![CDATA[/DestinfoSearchResults.ignore]]></anc_Destinfo>
<anc_EventsSearch><![CDATA[/EventsSearch.xml]]></anc_EventsSearch>
<anc_GeneralSearch><![CDATA[/GeneralSearch.ignore]]></anc_GeneralSearch>
<anc_Hire><![CDATA[/Hire.ignore]]></anc_Hire>
<anc_Info><![CDATA[/InfoSearchResults.ignore]]></anc_Info>
<anc_More><![CDATA[]]></anc_More>
<anc_RestaurantSearch><![CDATA[/RestaurantSearch.ignore]]></anc_RestaurantSearch>
<anc_Tour><![CDATA[/TourSearchResults.ignore]]></anc_Tour>
<anc_Transport><![CDATA[/Transport.ignore]]></anc_Transport>
<hdl_Title><![CDATA[Plan Your Visit]]></hdl_Title>
<language><![CDATA[ENA]]></language>
<stf_Accomodation><![CDATA[]]></stf_Accomodation>
<stf_AreaFilter><![CDATA[]]></stf_AreaFilter>
<stf_Attractions><![CDATA[]]></stf_Attractions>
<stf_AussieSpecialist><![CDATA[]]></stf_AussieSpecialist>
<stf_Destinationinfo><![CDATA[]]></stf_Destinationinfo>
<stf_DomesticRegion><![CDATA[]]></stf_DomesticRegion>
<stf_Events><![CDATA[]]></stf_Events>
<stf_Hire><![CDATA[]]></stf_Hire>
<stf_Informationservices><![CDATA[]]></stf_Informationservices>
<stf_PlanYourVisitTitle><![CDATA[Plan Your Visit]]></stf_PlanYourVisitTitle>
<stf_StateFilter><![CDATA[]]></stf_StateFilter>
<stf_Tours><![CDATA[]]></stf_Tours>
<stf_Transport><![CDATA[]]></stf_Transport>
</PlanYourVisit><PlanYourHolidayBox isTemplate="1">
    <anc_MoreLink><![CDATA[]]></anc_MoreLink>
    <hdl_Headline><![CDATA[Plan Your Holiday]]></hdl_Headline>
    <language><![CDATA[ENA]]></language>
    <opt_IsOnHomepage><![CDATA[]]></opt_IsOnHomepage>
    <stf_MenuIconClass><![CDATA[]]></stf_MenuIconClass>
    <stf_More><![CDATA[More]]></stf_More>
    <stf_PlanYourHolidayTitle><![CDATA[Plan your holiday]]></stf_PlanYourHolidayTitle>
    <lst_PageLinks>
        <lst_PageLink>
            <url><![CDATA[/plan/plan-your-trip/find-travel-agent.xml]]></url>
            <hdl_Title><![CDATA[Find a Travel Specialist]]></hdl_Title>
            <opt_MenuIconClass><![CDATA[]]></opt_MenuIconClass>
        </lst_PageLink>
        <lst_PageLink>
            <url><![CDATA[/plan/plan-your-trip/getting-there.xml]]></url>
            <hdl_Title><![CDATA[Find Flights]]></hdl_Title>
            <opt_MenuIconClass><![CDATA[]]></opt_MenuIconClass>
        </lst_PageLink>
        <lst_PageLink>
            <url><![CDATA[/plan/plan-your-trip/accommodation.xml]]></url>
            <hdl_Title><![CDATA[Accommodation]]></hdl_Title>
            <opt_MenuIconClass><![CDATA[]]></opt_MenuIconClass>
        </lst_PageLink>
        <lst_PageLink>
            <url><![CDATA[/plan/plan-your-trip/tours.xml]]></url>
            <hdl_Title><![CDATA[Find Tours]]></hdl_Title>
            <opt_MenuIconClass><![CDATA[]]></opt_MenuIconClass>
        </lst_PageLink>
        <lst_PageLink>
            <url><![CDATA[/plan/plan-your-trip/specialoffers.xml]]></url>
            <hdl_Title><![CDATA[Special Offers*]]></hdl_Title>
            <opt_MenuIconClass><![CDATA[]]></opt_MenuIconClass>
        </lst_PageLink>
    </lst_PageLinks>
</PlanYourHolidayBox>
    </con_RHSModules>
    <con_Video>
        
    </con_Video>
    <con_Body>
        <TopCategoryHighlights isTemplate="1">
            <stf_Heading><![CDATA[Australia’s Food and Wine]]></stf_Heading>
            <stf_InformationTitle><![CDATA[]]></stf_InformationTitle>
            <txt_Information><![CDATA[
        Experience the freedom and creativity of Australia’s food and wine culture that helps us produce fresh and innovative flavours and wines that are the envy of the world.
        <p>Australia’s unspoilt landscapes produce an incredibly wide variety of fresh and tantalising produce. There’s also a freedom and creativity to our food and wine culture that helps us produce fresh and innovative flavours, including wines that are the envy of the world, as well as exciting ingredients and ‘fusion’ food. But what really sets us apart is the place – our stunning weather, sunshine, outstanding natural beauty and outdoor dining lifestyle means you can enjoy some of the world’s best food and wine in some of the world’s most stunning surroundings. Australia does open air dining like nowhere else.</p>
    ]]></txt_Information>
            <con_CenterContent>
                <CenterContent isTemplate="1">
                    <hdl_Title><![CDATA[Food and Wine experiences]]></hdl_Title>
                    <img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/explore-things-to-see-do-food-wine-experiences-hl.jpg" alt="Saffire Signature Experience, TAS">]]></img_MainImage>
                    <stf_Caption><![CDATA[Saffire Signature Experience, TAS]]></stf_Caption>
                    <anc_link><![CDATA[]]></anc_link>
                    <txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[
        Australia offers any number of culinary adventures. Dining on Sydney Harbour is magical, from the high-calibre fare of city restaurants to fish and chips at <a href="/explore/cities/sydney/nsw-manly-beach.xml" target="_self">Manly Beach</a>, or on the deck of a luxury harbour cruise. Dine under a million stars at the <a href="http://www.australia.com/campaigns/nothinglike/en/uluru-product4.htm" target="_blank">Sounds of Silence</a> or capture the legend of the Outback stockmen with camp-oven cooking in the Northern Territory. Explore the <a href="/explore/cities/melbourne/melbourne-hidden-laneways.xml" target="_self">laneways of Melbourne</a> where you’ll find world-class restaurants in converted warehouses and secret underground locations. Dine overlooking the vineyards in Victoria’s <a href="/about/australias-landscapes/wine-regions/yarra-valley.xml" target="_self">Yarra Valley</a>. Enjoy an Outback barbecue in the Kimberley for a uniquely Australian experience. Wander through the <a href="/explore/cities/darwin/nt-mindil-markets.xml" target="_self">Mindil Beach Markets</a> in Darwin and taste a breadth of fare from across the globe. Visit the rows of fresh produce and sumptuous delicatessens of the Victoria Markets in Melbourne or the <a href="/explore/cities/adelaide/adelaide-central-market.xml" target="_self">Central Markets in Adelaide</a>. Dine on seafood served fresh from the day’s catch at the Sydney Fish Market. Hunt for truffles in Western Australia or the Australian Capital Territory. You can shuck your own fresh oysters on Tasmania’s Freycinet Peninsula. Meet the growers in regional Australia. Outdoors, by the water and in stunning locations, the range of ways to experience food and wine in Australia is almost as varied as the goods we produce.
    ]]>
                    </txt_Information>
                </CenterContent><CenterContent isTemplate="1">
                    <hdl_Title><![CDATA[Produce]]></hdl_Title>
                    <img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/explore-things-to-see-do-food-wine-produce-hl.jpg" alt="Mures Fish Centre, TAS">]]></img_MainImage>
                    <stf_Caption><![CDATA[Mures Fish Centre, TAS]]></stf_Caption>
                    <anc_link><![CDATA[]]></anc_link>
                    <txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[
        The range and quality of produce found in Australia is one of the keys to our culinary creativity. With so many different climate zones, from tropical to desert and temperate to cool, there’s almost nothing Australia can’t grow or produce. We also have ingredients that you can't find anywhere else in the world. The ‘bush tucker’ ingredients of <a href="/explore/things-to-do/aboriginal-australia.xml" target="_self">indigenous Australia</a> are having a growing influence on our distinctive culinary style. Our pristine seas and rivers provide a bounty of seafood: from salmon and freshly shucked oysters from Tasmania to barramundi from the Northern Territory and marron from Kangaroo Island. There’s venison and black truffles from Western Australia and much prized wagyu beef is raised across the country. There are world-class cheeses from Tasmania’s Bruny Island and Kangaroo Island. Some of the finest chick peas in the world come from the Ord River in north-western Australia; while the sun-kissed regions of <a href="/explore/states/qld.xml" target="_self">Queensland</a> produce an amazing array of tropical fruits.
    ]]>
                    </txt_Information>
                </CenterContent><CenterContent isTemplate="1">
                    <hdl_Title><![CDATA[Food and Wine events]]></hdl_Title>
                    <img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/explore-events-food-and-wine-events-hl.jpg" alt="Taste Festival, Sydney, NSW">]]></img_MainImage>
                    <stf_Caption><![CDATA[Taste Festival, Sydney, NSW]]></stf_Caption>
                    <anc_link><![CDATA[]]></anc_link>
                    <txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[
        Across Australia and in every season, you’ll find major <a href="/explore/australian-events/food-wine-events.xml" target="_self">food and wine festivals</a> showcasing the country’s best. Australia’s food festivals range from regional events to internationally recognised events in cities attracting some of the world’s best chefs. Visit during the <a href="/explore/events/melbourne-food-and-wine-festival.xml" target="_self">Melbourne Food & Wine Festival</a> to taste the flavour of autumn; or dig for winter truffles in Western Australia or Canberra. Sample the variety of our rich produce at the Kangaroo Island Seafood ‘FEASTival’; Margaret River’s Gourmet Escape; Victoria’s High Country Harvest Festival; <a href="/explore/events/nsw-orange-food-week.xml" target="_self">Orange FOOD Week</a>; or <a href="/explore/cities/canberra/act-fireside-festival.xml" target="_self">Canberra’s Fireside Festival</a>. Throughout October and November, celebrate Australia’s largest food festival during Good Food Month in Sydney, Melbourne, Canberra and Brisbane. Wine connoisseurs also have plenty of options, including Adelaide’s Cellar Door Festival and the Barossa Gourmet Weekend. Toast the New Year with Tasmania’s finest cool-climate wines at the <a href="/explore/events/tas-taste-festival.xml" target="_self">Tasmania’s Taste Festival</a>; or sample the country’s entire rich harvest during Aussie Wine Month in April.
    ]]>
                    </txt_Information>
                </CenterContent><CenterContent isTemplate="1">
                    <hdl_Title><![CDATA[Restaurants]]></hdl_Title>
                    <img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/explore-things-to-see-do-food-wine-restaurants-hl.jpg" alt="Sydney, NSW">]]></img_MainImage>
                    <stf_Caption><![CDATA[Sydney, NSW]]></stf_Caption>
                    <anc_link><![CDATA[]]></anc_link>
                    <txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[
        Around Australia you’ll find a collection of restaurants that tell the story of Australia’s dining excellence; the creative direction of our chefs and our high standards of service. Many chefs come to Australia and open restaurants because of our fresh produce, open air locales and fresh thinking. Some of the world’s top restaurant critics and chefs are amazed by the quality and sophistication of our restaurants and the diversity of their menus. Our globally recognised chefs have the freedom to be playful and creative, and create their own rules. You’ll find menus using indigenous ingredients such as wallaby, warrigal greens and quandongs. You’ll find Australian restaurants have relaxed feel, mostly due to our weather that draws us outside and towards the water or the shade of a gum tree. Even the most prestigious fine dining restaurants offer an informality that make them welcoming. Whether you dine in an internationally acclaimed restaurant or a local caf&eacute; in a regional town or city suburb the quality of the menu and fresh flavours on your plate will be a delight.
    ]]>
                    </txt_Information>
                </CenterContent><CenterContent isTemplate="1">
                    <hdl_Title><![CDATA[Food and Wine trails]]></hdl_Title>
                    <img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/explore-things-to-see-do-food-wine-trails-hl.jpg" alt="Tamar Valley Wine Route, TAS">]]></img_MainImage>
                    <stf_Caption><![CDATA[Tamar Valley Wine Route, TAS]]></stf_Caption>
                    <anc_link><![CDATA[]]></anc_link>
                    <txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[
        Food and wine trails can be found across Australia to help you explore and discover our best regional food and wine offerings. Follow the <a href="/explore/itineraries/act-poachers-way.xml" target="_self">Poacher’s Way</a> from Canberra and you’ll find gourmet delights dotted throughout the countryside. Close to Adelaide are the <a href="/explore/itineraries/sa-3weeks-adelaide.xml" target="_self">Adelaide Hills</a>, Barossa Valley, <a href="/about/australias-landscapes/wine-regions/clare-valley.xml" target="_self">Clare Valley</a> and <a href="/about/australias-landscapes/wine-regions/mclaren-vale.xml" target="_self">McLaren Vale</a>, where you’ll find hundreds of cellar doors plus farmers’ markets, exquisite restaurants and artisan producers. The Clare Valley’s Riesling Trail and Rattler Trail is perfect for walking or cycling between local towns. In Western Australia the Swan Valley Food and Wine Trail and Gascoyne Food Trail feature an array of wineries, breweries, fine restaurants, cafes, and fresh produce; while the Chittering Valley Wine Trail provides a unique combination of wine and art. Follow Tasmania’s Tamar Valley Wine Route and see where 40% of Tasmania’s premium wine is produced. Or experience the authentic ‘bush tucker’ trails of the Northern Territory.
    ]]>
                    </txt_Information>
                </CenterContent><CenterContent isTemplate="1">
                    <hdl_Title><![CDATA[Food and wine characters]]></hdl_Title>
                    <img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/explore-things-to-see-do-food-wine-characters-hl.jpg" alt="Mt Borradaile, Arnhemland, NT">]]></img_MainImage>
                    <stf_Caption><![CDATA[Mt Borradaile, Arnhemland, NT]]></stf_Caption>
                    <anc_link><![CDATA[]]></anc_link>
                    <txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[
        Australia is home to a wonderful mix of cultures from all over the world. We celebrate our multicultural diversity with enthusiasm and passion, creating a dimension to our cuisine that is uniquely Australian. What sets Australia apart is that while our chefs and winemakers honour traditions, they are also leading the charge and experimenting with new styles and fresh ingredients that can only be found in Australia. Industry icons Cheong Liew and Tetsuya Wakuda pioneered the art of fusing Asian flavours with European techniques. Peter Conistis took the food of his Greek heritage and added Australian influences; and several of our finest chefs, including Neil Perry who takes influences from Asia, Italy and Spain to produce uniquely Australian dishes that showcase the depth and quality of our produce. Maggie Beer has created inspiration for inspired local produce through her diverse line of products, arguably the most highly-esteemed and much loved range for Australian gourmets. A down-to-earth, unpretentious style characterises much of Australia’s food and wine culture, much like our approach to life.
    ]]>
                    </txt_Information>
                </CenterContent><CenterContent isTemplate="1">
                    <hdl_Title><![CDATA[The wine story]]></hdl_Title>
                    <img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/explore-things-to-see-do-food-wine-story-hl.jpg" alt="Seppeltsfield Winery Cellar, SA">]]></img_MainImage>
                    <stf_Caption><![CDATA[Seppeltsfield Winery Cellar, SA]]></stf_Caption>
                    <anc_link><![CDATA[]]></anc_link>
                    <txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[
        Australia is one of the world’s outstanding wine-producing countries. Some of the world’s oldest vines can be found here. Large and small, traditional and boutique – our wineries offer a range of different experiences. Australia has more than 60 wine regions each with its own personality and signature variety. Walk into almost any cellar door, from the <a href="/explore/states/wa/margaret-river.xml" target="_self">Margaret River region</a> to Tasmania’s Huon Valley, from the <a href="/explore/cities/melbourne/mornington-peninsula.xml" target="_self">Mornington Peninsula</a> to the <a href="/explore/states/nsw/hunter-valley.xml" target="_self">Hunter</a> or <a href="/explore/states/sa/barossa-valley.xml" target="_self">Barossa Valley</a>, and you are likely to find yourself talking directly to the winemaker, who are often second or third generation vignerons. Our wines display the diversity of the early migrants whose skills influenced the industry. Most of Australia’s wineries are within easy reach of the major cities. Many offer behind-the-scenes tours, quality restaurants and wine appreciation classes to enrich your experience. Visit during harvest season and smell, touch and taste each vintage as it comes off the vine.
    ]]>
                    </txt_Information>
                </CenterContent>
            </con_CenterContent>
        </TopCategoryHighlights>
    </con_Body>
</SubPageLayout>
    </con_Body>
    <lst_Subpages>
    </lst_Subpages>
</ConsumerBaseFoundation>