<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<ConsumerBaseFoundation pageID="15308" isTemplate="1">
    <breadcrumb>
        <element level="1">
            <headline><![CDATA[Homepage ]]></headline>
            <href><![CDATA[/index.xml]]></href>
        </element>
<element level="2">
            <headline><![CDATA[Explore ]]></headline>
            <href><![CDATA[/explore.xml]]></href>
        </element>
<element level="4">
            <headline><![CDATA[Luxury Lodges of Australia]]></headline>
            <href><![CDATA[/explore/things-to-do/great-luxury-lodges.xml]]></href>
        </element>

    </breadcrumb>
    <img_background><![CDATA[/contentimages/promotions-luxury-lodges-bg2.jpg]]></img_background>
    <hdl_Title><![CDATA[Luxury Lodges of Australia]]></hdl_Title>
    <img_Banner><![CDATA[]]></img_Banner>
    <img_SearchThumbnail><![CDATA[/thumbnails/best-of-luxury-lodges-search.jpg]]></img_SearchThumbnail>
    <img_Thumbnail><![CDATA[/contentimages/best-of-luxury-lodges-th.jpg]]></img_Thumbnail>
    <opt_HideInBreadcrumbs><![CDATA[Show]]></opt_HideInBreadcrumbs>
    <opt_HidePage><![CDATA[no]]></opt_HidePage>
    <opt_hideTitle><![CDATA[0]]></opt_hideTitle>
    <opt_hide_in_sitemap><![CDATA[no]]></opt_hide_in_sitemap>
    <opt_IncludeVideo><![CDATA[0]]></opt_IncludeVideo>
    <opt_isHubPage><![CDATA[0]]></opt_isHubPage>
    <opt_isNewWindow><![CDATA[_self]]></opt_isNewWindow>
    <opt_PageLayout><![CDATA[]]></opt_PageLayout>
    <opt_PartnerLead><![CDATA[no]]></opt_PartnerLead>
    <stf_description><![CDATA[From luxury bush camps to eco-friendly homesteads, Luxury Lodges of Australia offers unforgettable experiences in inspiring Australian landscapes.]]></stf_description>
    <stf_ExcludedCountries><![CDATA[]]></stf_ExcludedCountries>
    <stf_hideInXmlSitemap><![CDATA[]]></stf_hideInXmlSitemap>
    <stf_ImageLocation><![CDATA[]]></stf_ImageLocation>
    <stf_intro_title><![CDATA[]]></stf_intro_title>
    <stf_IsExternalSiteArticle><![CDATA[]]></stf_IsExternalSiteArticle>
    <stf_IsMobile><![CDATA[n]]></stf_IsMobile>
    <stf_keywords><![CDATA[luxury lodges of australia, luxury camping australia]]></stf_keywords>
    <stf_LinkLearnMore><![CDATA[Learn More]]></stf_LinkLearnMore>
    <stf_NavigationTagLine><![CDATA[]]></stf_NavigationTagLine>
    <stf_PageHeading><![CDATA[]]></stf_PageHeading>
    <stf_TargetedCountries><![CDATA[AU,US,CA,NZ,GB,MY,SG]]></stf_TargetedCountries>
    <stf_TrackingTitle><![CDATA[]]></stf_TrackingTitle>
    <TA_Title><![CDATA[Luxury Lodges of Australia &amp; Luxury Camping - Tourism Australia]]></TA_Title>
    <txt_Intro>
        <![CDATA[]]>
    </txt_Intro>
    <txt_MobileContentOnly>
        <![CDATA[]]>
    </txt_MobileContentOnly>
    <txt_SpotlightTag>
        <![CDATA[]]>
    </txt_SpotlightTag>
    <txt_Teaser>
        <![CDATA[
        Luxury Lodges of Australia is a collection of independently owned and operated luxury lodges and camps offering unforgettable experiences in some of Australia’s most inspiring landscapes.
    ]]>
    </txt_Teaser>
    <con_Body>
        <SubPageLayout isTemplate="1">
    <con_Banner>
        
    </con_Banner>
    <con_RHSModules>
        <Listing isTemplate="1">
<anc_List1><![CDATA[/explore/itineraries-ideas/holiday-ideas.xml]]></anc_List1>
<anc_MoreLink><![CDATA[]]></anc_MoreLink>
<hdl_Title><![CDATA[More Australian Ideas]]></hdl_Title>
<img_Thumbnail><![CDATA[]]></img_Thumbnail>
<med_File><![CDATA[]]></med_File>
<opt_isNewWindow><![CDATA[]]></opt_isNewWindow>
<stf_externalLink><![CDATA[]]></stf_externalLink>
<stf_ExternalLinkTitle><![CDATA[]]></stf_ExternalLinkTitle>
<stf_IsExternalSiteArticle><![CDATA[]]></stf_IsExternalSiteArticle>
<stf_LinkLearnMore><![CDATA[]]></stf_LinkLearnMore>
<txt_Teaser><![CDATA[]]></txt_Teaser>
<opt_national_landscapes_id><![CDATA[]]></opt_national_landscapes_id>
<stf_hideInXmlSitemap><![CDATA[]]></stf_hideInXmlSitemap>
<stf_TargetedCountry><![CDATA[]]></stf_TargetedCountry>
<con_Banner></con_Banner>
<con_Body></con_Body>
<con_RHSModules></con_RHSModules>
<con_Category></con_Category>
<lst_Subpages></lst_Subpages>
</Listing><PlanYourVisit isTemplate="1">
<anc_AccommodationSearch><![CDATA[/AccommodationSearch.ignore]]></anc_AccommodationSearch>
<anc_ASPSearch><![CDATA[/plan/plan-your-trip/find-travel-agent.xml]]></anc_ASPSearch>
<anc_Attraction><![CDATA[/AttractionSearchResults.ignore]]></anc_Attraction>
<anc_Destinfo><![CDATA[/DestinfoSearchResults.ignore]]></anc_Destinfo>
<anc_EventsSearch><![CDATA[/EventsSearch.xml]]></anc_EventsSearch>
<anc_GeneralSearch><![CDATA[/GeneralSearch.ignore]]></anc_GeneralSearch>
<anc_Hire><![CDATA[/Hire.ignore]]></anc_Hire>
<anc_Info><![CDATA[/InfoSearchResults.ignore]]></anc_Info>
<anc_More><![CDATA[]]></anc_More>
<anc_RestaurantSearch><![CDATA[/RestaurantSearch.ignore]]></anc_RestaurantSearch>
<anc_Tour><![CDATA[/TourSearchResults.ignore]]></anc_Tour>
<anc_Transport><![CDATA[/Transport.ignore]]></anc_Transport>
<hdl_Title><![CDATA[Plan Your Visit]]></hdl_Title>
<language><![CDATA[ENA]]></language>
<stf_Accomodation><![CDATA[]]></stf_Accomodation>
<stf_AreaFilter><![CDATA[]]></stf_AreaFilter>
<stf_Attractions><![CDATA[]]></stf_Attractions>
<stf_AussieSpecialist><![CDATA[]]></stf_AussieSpecialist>
<stf_Destinationinfo><![CDATA[]]></stf_Destinationinfo>
<stf_DomesticRegion><![CDATA[]]></stf_DomesticRegion>
<stf_Events><![CDATA[]]></stf_Events>
<stf_Hire><![CDATA[]]></stf_Hire>
<stf_Informationservices><![CDATA[]]></stf_Informationservices>
<stf_PlanYourVisitTitle><![CDATA[Plan Your Visit]]></stf_PlanYourVisitTitle>
<stf_StateFilter><![CDATA[]]></stf_StateFilter>
<stf_Tours><![CDATA[]]></stf_Tours>
<stf_Transport><![CDATA[]]></stf_Transport>
</PlanYourVisit>
    </con_RHSModules>
    <con_Video>
        
    </con_Video>
    <con_Body>
        <TopCategoryHighlights isTemplate="1">
            <stf_Heading><![CDATA[Luxury Lodges of Australia]]></stf_Heading>
            <stf_InformationTitle><![CDATA[]]></stf_InformationTitle>
            <txt_Information><![CDATA[
        Luxury Lodges of Australia is a collection of independently owned and operated luxury lodges and camps offering unforgettable experiences in some of Australia’s most inspiring landscapes.
        <p>Each lodge offers signature experiences and activities to showcase the unique aspects of its region – the natural landscapes, the wildlife, the food and wine. It is these experiences that define the new Australian luxury and showcase Australia’s extraordinary diversity.</p>
        <p>From character-filled bush camps to heritage homesteads and working cattle stations - Australia-wide you’ll find these environmentally-sensitive lodges perched on the edge of national parks; amongst desert sand dunes; overlooking the ocean; on islands fringed by World Heritage coral reefs; and amid pristine rainforests.</p>
        <p>These lodges accommodate just a few guests at one time. You can relax and immerse in Australia’s natural environment, wildlife, and food and wine, while being assured of luxe accommodation and attentive understated Australian hospitality.</p>
    ]]></txt_Information>
            <con_CenterContent>
                <CenterContent isTemplate="1">
                    <hdl_Title><![CDATA[Luxury Lodges in Western Australia]]></hdl_Title>
                    <img_MainImage><![CDATA[]]></img_MainImage>
                    <stf_Caption><![CDATA[]]></stf_Caption>
                    <anc_link><![CDATA[]]></anc_link>
                    <txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[]]>
                    </txt_Information>
                </CenterContent><CenterContent isTemplate="1">
                    <hdl_Title><![CDATA[Cape Lodge]]></hdl_Title>
                    <img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/promotions-luxury-lodges-cape-lodge-hl.jpg" alt="Cape Lodge ">]]></img_MainImage>
                    <stf_Caption><![CDATA[Cape Lodge]]></stf_Caption>
                    <anc_link><![CDATA[]]></anc_link>
                    <txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[
        Located on its own vineyard in Western Australia’s <a href="/explore/states/wa/wa-margaret-river.xml" target="_self">Margaret River wine region</a>, Cape Lodge is like staying at a private country estate, with all the facilities of a world class boutique hotel. It will tempt those seeking a private and sophisticated retreat, and who seek out fine food and wine.
    ]]>
                    </txt_Information>
                </CenterContent><CenterContent isTemplate="1">
                    <hdl_Title><![CDATA[El Questro]]></hdl_Title>
                    <img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/1_ElQuestro_wa_hl.jpg" alt="El Questro">]]></img_MainImage>
                    <stf_Caption><![CDATA[El Questro]]></stf_Caption>
                    <anc_link><![CDATA[]]></anc_link>
                    <txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[
        The luxury of the El Questro Homestead sits in stark contrast to Western Australia's rugged <a href="/explore/icons/kimberley.xml" target="_self">Kimberley</a> landscape. Located amidst one million acres of wilderness park and 100 km from the nearest town, The Homestead offers an exclusive retreat for just 18 guests. Expert guides assist with the exploration of this Australian wilderness – with guided hikes, gorge walks or a dip in thermal springs. Take a scenic flight over the World heritage-listed Bungle Bungle Range in Purnululu national Park. Soak away your cares in the natural hot springs or curl up under a Boab tree with a book.
    ]]>
                    </txt_Information>
                </CenterContent><CenterContent isTemplate="1">
                    <hdl_Title><![CDATA[San Salis]]></hdl_Title>
                    <img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/1_salsalis_wa_hl.jpg" alt="San Salis">]]></img_MainImage>
                    <stf_Caption><![CDATA[San Salis]]></stf_Caption>
                    <anc_link><![CDATA[]]></anc_link>
                    <txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[
        Sal Salis is just a few steps away from Western Australia’s World Heritage-listed <a href="/explore/icons/ningaloo.xml" target="_self">Ningaloo Reef</a>. The nine luxury wilderness tents hidden amongst the sand dunes bring a touch of safari style to this remote and beautiful wilderness. Ningaloo Reef is regarded as one of the best places in the world to swim with the gentle giant whale sharks that migrate here each year. It is also a major breeding area for humpback whales and turtles. Nearby Cape Range National Park abounds with kangaroos, emus and Australian wildlife.
    ]]>
                    </txt_Information>
                </CenterContent><CenterContent isTemplate="1">
                    <hdl_Title><![CDATA[True North]]></hdl_Title>
                    <img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/1_truenorth_wa_hl.jpg" alt="True North">]]></img_MainImage>
                    <stf_Caption><![CDATA[True North]]></stf_Caption>
                    <anc_link><![CDATA[]]></anc_link>
                    <txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[
        In <a href="/explore/states/wa.xml" target="_self">Western Australia</a> you’ll also find luxury on the water. Sailing aboard the 18-cabin adventure cruise ship True North is an unbeatable way to see the rivers, gorges and wilderness of the remote Kimberley coastline of Australia. There is an on-board helicopter and 6 expedition boats, 19 expert crew who provide outstanding service and dining for a maximum of 36 guests. Gain rare insights into this unique landscape with expert guides and varied daily expeditions.
    ]]>
                    </txt_Information>
                </CenterContent><CenterContent isTemplate="1">
                    <hdl_Title><![CDATA[Luxury Lodges in Northern Territory]]></hdl_Title>
                    <img_MainImage><![CDATA[]]></img_MainImage>
                    <stf_Caption><![CDATA[]]></stf_Caption>
                    <anc_link><![CDATA[]]></anc_link>
                    <txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[]]>
                    </txt_Information>
                </CenterContent><CenterContent isTemplate="1">
                    <hdl_Title><![CDATA[Bamurru Plains]]></hdl_Title>
                    <img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/2_bamurruplains_northenrterritory_hl.jpg" alt="Bamurru Plains">]]></img_MainImage>
                    <stf_Caption><![CDATA[Bamurru Plains]]></stf_Caption>
                    <anc_link><![CDATA[]]></anc_link>
                    <txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[
        Bamurru Plains offers an extraordinary luxe bush experience on the edge of <a href="/explore/icons/kakadu.xml" target="_self">Kakadu National Park</a> in Australia’s Northern Territory. This eco-sensitive camp focuses on environmental sustainability and quality service. The exclusive nine bungalow camp offers all the key soft luxury standards – eat well, sleep well and drink well. It’s location right on the Mary River floodplain ensures guests are introduced to the sights and sounds of the Top end in style. Bamurru’s team of passionate field guides offer a variety of activities from the camp, including airboat rides to breathtakingly beautiful locations on the floodplain where submerged melaleuca forests and acres of water lilies fill the horizon, crocodile-spotting and bird-watching tours, fishing trips, four-wheel drive safaris, helicopter flights and guided tours to the rock art galleries of Arnhem Land - Australia’s indigenous heartland. In the evening, guests relax over a gourmet meal and enjoy the ‘wild bush luxury’ that is the Bamurru Plains trademark.
    ]]>
                    </txt_Information>
                </CenterContent><CenterContent isTemplate="1">
                    <hdl_Title><![CDATA[Longitude 131&deg;]]></hdl_Title>
                    <img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/2_longitude_nt_hl.jpg" alt="Longitude 131°">]]></img_MainImage>
                    <stf_Caption><![CDATA[Longitude 131&deg;]]></stf_Caption>
                    <anc_link><![CDATA[]]></anc_link>
                    <txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[
        Luxurious and romantic, Longitude 131&deg; is an iconic eco-sensitive tented camp located in the heart of Australia at the gateway of the dual World Heritage-listed wilderness of Uluru-Kata Tjuta National Park. Each of the 15 permanent eco-sensitive canopied suites has private views of the changing colours of <a href="http://www.australia.com/campaigns/nothinglike/en/uluru.htm" target="_blank">Uluru</a> as the sun rises and sets. Dine in the desert under a glittering canopy of stars with the sounds of the didgeridoo echoing into the desert night. Take an exclusive tour with your Aboriginal guide and discover authentic outback experiences. You’ll learn about the ancient cultures of the traditional owners; see the native flora and fauna and discover a living landscape, rich in history and the spiritual and geographic heart of Australia.
    ]]>
                    </txt_Information>
                </CenterContent><CenterContent isTemplate="1">
                    <hdl_Title><![CDATA[Luxury Lodges in South Australia]]></hdl_Title>
                    <img_MainImage><![CDATA[]]></img_MainImage>
                    <stf_Caption><![CDATA[]]></stf_Caption>
                    <anc_link><![CDATA[]]></anc_link>
                    <txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[]]>
                    </txt_Information>
                </CenterContent><CenterContent isTemplate="1">
                    <hdl_Title><![CDATA[Southern Ocean Lodge]]></hdl_Title>
                    <img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/3_southernoceanlodge_southaustralia_hl.jpg" alt="Southern Ocean Lodge">]]></img_MainImage>
                    <stf_Caption><![CDATA[Southern Ocean Lodge]]></stf_Caption>
                    <anc_link><![CDATA[]]></anc_link>
                    <txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[
        Southern Ocean Lodge on South Australia’s pristine <a href="/explore/icons/kangaroo-island.xml" target="_self">Kangaroo Island</a> offers a fusion of nature and luxury. This multi-award winning lodge is regarded as amongst the finest in the world. Commanding spectacular ocean, beach and wilderness views, all of the 21 luxury suites overlook the rolling waves of the great Southern Ocean. Enjoy exceptional dining highlighting exceptional Kangaroo Island produce, complemented by an exclusively South Australian wine selection. More than one third of Kangaroo Island is dedicated to national and conservation parks. Southern Ocean Lodge’s personalised touring allows for extensive exploration with expert guides. Wander amongst brilliant wild flowers and towering gum trees. Explore the wind-sculpted Remarkable Rocks and Admirals Arch. See lazy sea lions basking on the beach and meet some of Australia’s rare native animals in the bush. Climb to the lighthouse at Cape Borda for some of South Australia’s best views.
    ]]>
                    </txt_Information>
                </CenterContent><CenterContent isTemplate="1">
                    <hdl_Title><![CDATA[The Louise]]></hdl_Title>
                    <img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/3_lousie_sa_hl.jpg" alt="The Louise">]]></img_MainImage>
                    <stf_Caption><![CDATA[The Louise]]></stf_Caption>
                    <anc_link><![CDATA[]]></anc_link>
                    <txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[
        The Louise, surrounded by vineyard in South Australia’s world-renowned Barossa Valley wine region, combines luxury accommodation with one of Australia’s finest regional dining experiences. The Louise boasts 15 luxuriously appointed suites, each with its own terrace overlooking the breathtaking vistas of the surrounding hundreds of acres of vines. Private winemaker introductions and other bespoke activities may be arranged for guests at The Louise. The daily chef's tasting menu of the award-winning signature restaurant Appellation has received national recognition and continues to be a magnet for culinary nomads. The <a href="/explore/states/sa/barossa-valley.xml" target="_self">Barossa Valley</a> is renowned as one of the world's finest wine producing regions. Home to more than 100 wineries and more than 70 with cellar doors, it’s a vibrant community with a rich 150-year old cultural heritage. Enjoy hot air ballooning, scenic helicopter rides, cycling, hiking, relaxing massages, farmers’ markets, or have breakfast with the kangaroos.
    ]]>
                    </txt_Information>
                </CenterContent><CenterContent isTemplate="1">
                    <hdl_Title><![CDATA[Luxury Lodges in Queensland]]></hdl_Title>
                    <img_MainImage><![CDATA[]]></img_MainImage>
                    <stf_Caption><![CDATA[]]></stf_Caption>
                    <anc_link><![CDATA[]]></anc_link>
                    <txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[]]>
                    </txt_Information>
                </CenterContent><CenterContent isTemplate="1">
                    <hdl_Title><![CDATA[Lizard Island]]></hdl_Title>
                    <img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/4_lizardisland_qld_hl.jpg" alt="Lizard Island">]]></img_MainImage>
                    <stf_Caption><![CDATA[Lizard Island]]></stf_Caption>
                    <anc_link><![CDATA[]]></anc_link>
                    <txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[
        Australia’s northern-most island resort, Lizard Island is truly secluded from the rest of the world. Located at the tip of the <a href="/explore/icons/great-barrier-reef.xml" target="_self">Great Barrier Reef</a>, Lizard Island is surrounded by fringing reefs, easily accessible from its 24 white sand beaches, more than 1000 hectares of national park, and ocean views from every angle. Dive or snorkel amongst coral reefs and brightly coloured tropical fish straight from the shore. Stay in one of the 40 private suites of villas and enjoy five star cuisine and indulgent spa treatments. Explore deserted beaches where the only footprints you’ll see in the sand are your own.
    ]]>
                    </txt_Information>
                </CenterContent><CenterContent isTemplate="1">
                    <hdl_Title><![CDATA[qualia, Hamilton Island]]></hdl_Title>
                    <img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/4_qualia_qld_hl.jpg" alt="qualia, Hamilton Island">]]></img_MainImage>
                    <stf_Caption><![CDATA[qualia, Hamilton Island]]></stf_Caption>
                    <anc_link><![CDATA[]]></anc_link>
                    <txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[
        qualia is a place of deep sensory sophistication. Located on the secluded northern tip of Hamilton Island on Australia’s Great Barrier Reef, qualia has a choice of 60 extremely private standalone pavilions, many with private plunge pools and natural outdoor showers. You can join a multitude of water-based activities from paddle-boarding, snorkelling and diving to <a href="/explore/itineraries/qld-whitsundays-sailing.xml" target="_self">sailing the Whitsunday Islands</a>. Indulge and unwind with spa treatments at award-winning Sap qualia or play a round at Australia’s only island championship golf course, the Hamilton Island Golf Club.
    ]]>
                    </txt_Information>
                </CenterContent><CenterContent isTemplate="1">
                    <hdl_Title><![CDATA[Silky Oaks Lodge]]></hdl_Title>
                    <img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/4_silkyoakslodge_qld_hl.jpg" alt="Silky Oaks Lodge">]]></img_MainImage>
                    <stf_Caption><![CDATA[Silky Oaks Lodge]]></stf_Caption>
                    <anc_link><![CDATA[]]></anc_link>
                    <txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[
        On the mainland in Tropical North Queensland, just 20 minutes from Port Douglas is Silky Oaks Lodge. The lodge is set in 80 acres of rainforest bordering the World Heritage Listed <a href="/explore/states/qld/qld-spring-daintree-forest.xml" target="_self">Daintree National Park</a> and overlooking the beautiful Mossman River. The Daintree is noted as the oldest living refugial rainforest on the planet and Silky Oak’s safaris and guided excursions into the rainforest are a mesmerizing part of the experience. Add to that, fine dining in a treehouse overlooking the ancient rainforest, early morning yoga classes, indulging in treatments at the Healing Waters Spa, lazy swims in the Billabong or simply enjoying the stunning forest and river vistas.
    ]]>
                    </txt_Information>
                </CenterContent><CenterContent isTemplate="1">
                    <hdl_Title><![CDATA[Spicers Clovelly Estate]]></hdl_Title>
                    <img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/4_spicersclovelly_qld_hl.jpg" alt="Spicers Clovelly Estate">]]></img_MainImage>
                    <stf_Caption><![CDATA[Spicers Clovelly Estate]]></stf_Caption>
                    <anc_link><![CDATA[]]></anc_link>
                    <txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[
        Spicers Clovelly Estate offers a relaxed environment with 10 exclusive suites nestled amongst 22 acres of lush grounds in the quiet hinterland of Queensland’s Sunshine Coast. Old world charm, French contemporary style, and fine dining are the hallmarks of this romantic manor house.
    ]]>
                    </txt_Information>
                </CenterContent><CenterContent isTemplate="1">
                    <hdl_Title><![CDATA[Spicers Peak Lodge]]></hdl_Title>
                    <img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/4_spicerspeaklodge_qld_hl.jpg" alt="Spicers Peak Lodge">]]></img_MainImage>
                    <stf_Caption><![CDATA[Spicers Peak Lodge]]></stf_Caption>
                    <anc_link><![CDATA[]]></anc_link>
                    <txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[
        Sister property, Spicers Peak Lodge is Queensland’s highest non-alpine mountain lodge, surrounded by 8000 acres of the World Heritage-listed Main Range National Park. Go bushwalking or mountain biking in a tropical rainforest, indulge at the standalone Spa Anise, enjoy outstanding dining at the restaurant or simply take in astounding views of the World Heritage Main Range National Park and surrounds.
    ]]>
                    </txt_Information>
                </CenterContent><CenterContent isTemplate="1">
                    <hdl_Title><![CDATA[Luxury Lodges in New South Wales]]></hdl_Title>
                    <img_MainImage><![CDATA[]]></img_MainImage>
                    <stf_Caption><![CDATA[]]></stf_Caption>
                    <anc_link><![CDATA[]]></anc_link>
                    <txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[]]>
                    </txt_Information>
                </CenterContent><CenterContent isTemplate="1">
                    <hdl_Title><![CDATA[Wolgan Valley Resort and Spa]]></hdl_Title>
                    <img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/5_wolganvalley_nsw_hl.jpg" alt="Wolgan Valley Resort and Spa">]]></img_MainImage>
                    <stf_Caption><![CDATA[Wolgan Valley Resort and Spa]]></stf_Caption>
                    <anc_link><![CDATA[]]></anc_link>
                    <txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[
        Emirates Wolgan Valley Resort and Spa is located within its own private conservation and wildlife reserve between two national parks in the spectacular bush setting of the World Heritage-listed Greater <a href="/explore/icons/blue-mountains.xml" target="_self">Blue Mountains</a>. The lodge has 40 individual suites with private swimming pools, distinctive dining, and luxurious facilities set amidst 4,000 acres of natural bushland. The resort actively protects its surrounding habitat and native wildlife while delivering the first-class standards and quality expected by high end experience seeking travellers from around the globe. Enjoy a range of nature based activities including four wheel drives, heritage tours, nature walks, wildlife spotting and horse riding. Don’t miss spotting one of the very rare albino wallaroos on the property as they emerge from hiding around dusk.
    ]]>
                    </txt_Information>
                </CenterContent><CenterContent isTemplate="1">
                    <hdl_Title><![CDATA[Capella Lodge]]></hdl_Title>
                    <img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/5_capella_nsw_hl.jpg" alt="Capella Lodge">]]></img_MainImage>
                    <stf_Caption><![CDATA[Capella Lodge]]></stf_Caption>
                    <anc_link><![CDATA[]]></anc_link>
                    <txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[
        A short flight from Australia’s east coast transports you to a real ‘treasure island’. <a href="/explore/states/nsw/nsw-lord-howe-island.xml" target="_self">Lord Howe Island</a> is a paradise lost in time and perfectly preserved. Capella Lodge has nine contemporary beach suites overlooking romantic Lovers Bay, with the striking twin mountains Mount Gower and Mount Lidgebird rising dramatically above and spectacular views of the surrounding ocean. Fine dining in the Lodge Restaurant showcases a bounty of local seafood and fresh regional produce. Unwind in the petit spa with its menu of signature treatments for complete relaxation. Explore rainforest tracks, white-sand beaches and the world’s most southerly coral reef. Remote rocky coves are alive with magnificent birdlife and wildlife, much of it endemic to the island, and valleys overflow with ancient plants. Climb to the summit of Mt Gower, rated as one of the world’s best day walks.
    ]]>
                    </txt_Information>
                </CenterContent><CenterContent isTemplate="1">
                    <hdl_Title><![CDATA[Luxury Lodges in Victoria]]></hdl_Title>
                    <img_MainImage><![CDATA[]]></img_MainImage>
                    <stf_Caption><![CDATA[]]></stf_Caption>
                    <anc_link><![CDATA[]]></anc_link>
                    <txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[]]>
                    </txt_Information>
                </CenterContent><CenterContent isTemplate="1">
                    <hdl_Title><![CDATA[Lake House]]></hdl_Title>
                    <img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/6_lakehouse_victoria_hl.jpg" alt="Lake House">]]></img_MainImage>
                    <stf_Caption><![CDATA[Lake House]]></stf_Caption>
                    <anc_link><![CDATA[]]></anc_link>
                    <txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[
        Lake House lays on the shores of idyllic Lake Daylesford in the heart of Victoria’s Spa Country just an hour and a half from <a href="/explore/cities/melbourne.xml" target="_self">Melbourne</a>. Boasting one of Australia's most revered regional restaurants and an award winning wine list with around 10,000 choices, Lake House is at the heart of modern Australian cuisine featuring the fresh seasonal produce. A diverse mix of artists’ studios, cafes, excellent restaurants, boutique day spas and holistic healing centres gives Daylesford its sophisticated bohemian feel. The Lake House’s 33 rooms are individually furnished with original artworks from the culturally rich region. Daylesford has more mineral springs than anywhere else in the Southern Hemisphere and the property’s day spa offers an indulgent way to experience the healing waters through a range of hydrotherapy treatments.
    ]]>
                    </txt_Information>
                </CenterContent><CenterContent isTemplate="1">
                    <hdl_Title><![CDATA[Luxury Lodges in Tasmania]]></hdl_Title>
                    <img_MainImage><![CDATA[]]></img_MainImage>
                    <stf_Caption><![CDATA[]]></stf_Caption>
                    <anc_link><![CDATA[]]></anc_link>
                    <txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[]]>
                    </txt_Information>
                </CenterContent><CenterContent isTemplate="1">
                    <hdl_Title><![CDATA[Saffire]]></hdl_Title>
                    <img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/7_saffice_tas_hl.jpg" alt="Saffire">]]></img_MainImage>
                    <stf_Caption><![CDATA[Saffire]]></stf_Caption>
                    <anc_link><![CDATA[]]></anc_link>
                    <txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[
        <a href="http://www.australia.com/campaigns/nothinglike/en/freycinet-product1.htm" target="_self">Saffire</a>, a sanctuary on <a href="/explore/itineraries/tas-east-coast.xml" target="_self">Tasmania’s east coast</a>, blends barefoot luxury with the breathtaking natural beauty of the Hazards Mountains and pristine waters of Great Oyster Bay and the Freycinet Peninsula. Featuring 20 luxurious suites and a day spa, Saffire is a celebration of the art of service, wellbeing, local culinary delights, ancient landscapes and abundant wildlife. Explore by boat and discover deserted islands, wild bushland and secluded beaches on the lodge’s signature Schouten Island Experience. Hike the pink granite mountains and rich coastal forests to the pure white sand beaches of <a href="/explore/icons/freycinet/tas-wineglass-bay.xml" target="_self">Wineglass Bay</a> and further afield through the <a href="/explore/icons/freycinet.xml" target="_self">Freycinet</a> National Park. Join one of Saffire’s guides for an easy two-hour walk to the Cape Tourville lighthouse. Kayak, fish or go bird-watching around the calm waters in front of the resort. Don't miss the Marine Farm signature experience, a unique way to discover the ways of oysters up close.<br />
        
    ]]>
                    </txt_Information>
                </CenterContent>
            </con_CenterContent>
        </TopCategoryHighlights>
    </con_Body>
</SubPageLayout>
    </con_Body>
    <lst_Subpages>
    </lst_Subpages>
</ConsumerBaseFoundation>