<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<ConsumerBaseFoundation pageID="23025" isTemplate="1">
    <breadcrumb>
        <element level="1">
            <headline><![CDATA[Homepage ]]></headline>
            <href><![CDATA[/index.xml]]></href>
        </element>
<element level="2">
            <headline><![CDATA[Tools and Campaigns]]></headline>
            <href><![CDATA[/tools-campaigns.xml]]></href>
        </element>
<element level="4">
            <headline><![CDATA[SG]]></headline>
            <href><![CDATA[/15317.ignore]]></href>
        </element>
<element level="5">
            <headline><![CDATA[Best of Australian Roadtrips]]></headline>
            <href><![CDATA[/self-drive-sg.xml]]></href>
        </element>
<element level="6">
            <headline><![CDATA[Great Southern Touring Route]]></headline>
            <href><![CDATA[/self-drive-vic-sg.xml]]></href>
        </element>
<element level="7">
            <headline><![CDATA[Great Southern Touring Route - 7 days]]></headline>
            <href><![CDATA[/self-drive-vic-7days-sg.xml]]></href>
        </element>

    </breadcrumb>
    <img_background><![CDATA[/contentimages/explore-states-vic-twelve-apostles.jpg]]></img_background>
    <hdl_Title><![CDATA[Great Southern Touring Route - 7 days]]></hdl_Title>
    <img_Banner><![CDATA[]]></img_Banner>
    <img_SearchThumbnail><![CDATA[/thumbnails/explore-states-vic-twelve-apostles-search.jpg]]></img_SearchThumbnail>
    <img_Thumbnail><![CDATA[/contentimages/about-key-facts-weather-sydney-th.jpg]]></img_Thumbnail>
    <opt_HideInBreadcrumbs><![CDATA[Show]]></opt_HideInBreadcrumbs>
    <opt_HidePage><![CDATA[no]]></opt_HidePage>
    <opt_hideTitle><![CDATA[0]]></opt_hideTitle>
    <opt_hide_in_sitemap><![CDATA[no]]></opt_hide_in_sitemap>
    <opt_IncludeVideo><![CDATA[0]]></opt_IncludeVideo>
    <opt_isHubPage><![CDATA[0]]></opt_isHubPage>
    <opt_isNewWindow><![CDATA[_self]]></opt_isNewWindow>
    <opt_PageLayout><![CDATA[]]></opt_PageLayout>
    <opt_PartnerLead><![CDATA[no]]></opt_PartnerLead>
    <stf_description><![CDATA[]]></stf_description>
    <stf_ExcludedCountries><![CDATA[]]></stf_ExcludedCountries>
    <stf_hideInXmlSitemap><![CDATA[]]></stf_hideInXmlSitemap>
    <stf_ImageLocation><![CDATA[Twelve Apostles, Victoria]]></stf_ImageLocation>
    <stf_intro_title><![CDATA[]]></stf_intro_title>
    <stf_IsExternalSiteArticle><![CDATA[]]></stf_IsExternalSiteArticle>
    <stf_IsMobile><![CDATA[n]]></stf_IsMobile>
    <stf_keywords><![CDATA[]]></stf_keywords>
    <stf_LinkLearnMore><![CDATA[Learn More]]></stf_LinkLearnMore>
    <stf_NavigationTagLine><![CDATA[]]></stf_NavigationTagLine>
    <stf_PageHeading><![CDATA[]]></stf_PageHeading>
    <stf_TargetedCountries><![CDATA[]]></stf_TargetedCountries>
    <stf_TrackingTitle><![CDATA[]]></stf_TrackingTitle>
    <TA_Title><![CDATA[Best of Australian Roadtrips: Great Southern Touring Route - 7 days]]></TA_Title>
    <txt_Intro>
        <![CDATA[]]>
    </txt_Intro>
    <txt_MobileContentOnly>
        <![CDATA[]]>
    </txt_MobileContentOnly>
    <txt_SpotlightTag>
        <![CDATA[]]>
    </txt_SpotlightTag>
    <txt_Teaser>
        <![CDATA[]]>
    </txt_Teaser>
    <con_Body>
        <StandardCampaignLayout isTemplate="1">
    <opt_national_landscapes_id><![CDATA[]]></opt_national_landscapes_id>
    <hdl_Title><![CDATA[]]></hdl_Title>
    <stf_hideInXmlSitemap><![CDATA[]]></stf_hideInXmlSitemap>
    <stf_TargetedCountry><![CDATA[]]></stf_TargetedCountry>
    <con_Banner></con_Banner>
    <con_Body><TopCategoryHighlights isTemplate="1">
            <stf_Heading><![CDATA[Great Southern Touring Route - 7 Days]]></stf_Heading>
            <stf_InformationTitle><![CDATA[]]></stf_InformationTitle>
            <txt_Information><![CDATA[
        <table width="100%">
            <tbody>
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top">
                    <p>The Great Southern Touring Route connects some of Victoria's most scenic locations - dramatic landscapes and native flora and fauna - with the history of white settlement and the Gold Rush.</p>
                    <br />
                    <table width="100%" style="padding: 10px; border: 1px solid rgb(204, 204, 204);">
                        <tbody>
                            <tr>
                                <td>
                                <p><span style="font-size: 13px;"><strong>Key Facts</strong></span></p>
                                <p><strong>Distance:</strong> 780 km<br />
                                <strong>Duration:</strong> 7 days<br />
                                <strong>States covered:</strong> Victoria<br />
                                <strong>Challenge Level:<strong> </strong><img alt="" src="/contentimages/icon-star01.png" /><img alt="" src="/contentimages/icon-star01.png" /><img alt="" src="/contentimages/icon-star02.png" /><img alt="" src="/contentimages/icon-star02.png" /></strong><br />
                                <strong>Flight gateway:</strong> Melbourne<br />
                                <strong>Highlights:</strong> Beautiful coastal scenery, pristine nature and wildlife encounters</p>
                                </td>
                            </tr>
                        </tbody>
                    </table>
                    </td>
                    <!--   <td valign="top" style="padding-top: 5px; padding-left: 20px;">
                    <p><iframe width="300" height="250" src="https://maps.google.com.au/?ie=UTF8&amp;t=m&amp;ll=-33.797409,150.921936&amp;spn=0.570608,0.826721&amp;z=9&amp;output=embed" frameborder="0" marginwidth="0" marginheight="0" scrolling="no"></iframe><br />
                    <small><a href="https://maps.google.com.au/?ie=UTF8&t=m&ll=-33.797409,150.921936&spn=0.570608,0.826721&z=9&source=embed" style="text-align: left;">View Larger Map</a></small></p>
                    </td> -->
                </tr>
            </tbody>
        </table>
        <br />
        <table width="100%">
            <tbody>
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top" colspan="2">
                    <p style="text-align: center;"><a href="#day1" target="_self">Day 1</a> │ <a href="#day2" target="_self">Day 2</a> │ <a href="#day3" target="_self">Day 3</a> │ <a href="#day4" target="_self">Day 4</a> │ <a href="#day5" target="_self">Day 5</a> │ <a href="#day6" target="_self">Day 6</a> │ <a href="#day7" target="_self">Day 7</a></p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-top: 5px; padding-bottom: 20px;" colspan="2">
                    <p style="text-align: center;"><img alt="" src="/contentimages/horizontal-line-grey.jpg" /></p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-top: 5px; padding-right: 10px;">
                    <p><img alt="Geelong" src="/contentimages/Campaigns/campaigns-sg-self-drive-vic-7days-hl01-1.jpg" /></p>
                    <p style="text-align: center;"><span style="color: rgb(105, 105, 105); font-size: 10px;">Geelong</span></p>
                    </td>
                    <td valign="top">
                    <p><a name="day1"></a><span style="font-size: 13px;"><strong>Day 01</strong></span></p>
                    <br />
                    <p><span style="font-size: 13px;"><strong>Melbourne to Apollo Bay</strong></span></p>
                    <p><span style="font-size: 13px;"></span>Depart Melbourne via the West Gate Bridge and follow the Princes Highway towards Werribee. Visit the zoo where animals from Africa, Asia, North America and Australia roam in open grasslands. Continue to Geelong, Victoria's second-largest city, and explore its historic waterfront; a lively area filled with restaurants and caf&eacute;s. The Geelong waterfront with its colourful bollards and yachts is a sight to behold. Call into the Bellarine Peninsula and get to the wild heart of Port Phillip Bay with a visit to the habitat of dolphins, seals, whales, penguins and sea birds.</p>
                    <p>From here, a short drive to Torquay - the official start of the spectacular coastal drive along the Great Ocean Road. Along with Bells Beach, Torquay is recognised among the world's premier surf locations. Time permitting, you can learn to surf with the experts.</p>
                    <p>Continue on through the townships of Anglesea and Aireys Inlet to Lorne, a resort-style town combining restaurants and shops with historic properties and natural attractions. The stretch between Lorne and Apollo Bay is considered by many to be the most picturesque section of the Great Ocean Road. The highway is carved into sheer cliffs that drop away into the ocean, offering commanding views of the waves swelling and crashing onto the rocks and beaches below.</p>
                    <p>This small fishing and farming village is also an excellent base for exploring the waterfalls and rainforests in the Otway National Park whilst enjoying the fresh seafood and local produce. Not to be missed is dinner at award-wining restaurants overlooking Apollo Bay.</p>
                    <p>Overnight: Apollo Bay</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-top: 5px; padding-bottom: 10px;" colspan="2">
                    <p style="text-align: center;"><img alt="" src="/contentimages/horizontal-line-grey.jpg" /></p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-top: 5px; padding-right: 10px;">
                    <p><img alt="Otway Fly Treetop Walk, Otway National Park, Victoria" src="/contentimages/Campaigns/campaigns-sg-self-drive-vic-7days-hl01.jpg" /></p>
                    <p style="text-align: center;"><span style="color: rgb(105, 105, 105); font-size: 10px;">Otway Fly Treetop Walk,<br />
                    Otway National Park</span></p>
                    </td>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-top: 5px; padding-right: 10px;">
                    <p><a name="day2"></a><strong><span style="font-size: 13px;">Day 02</span></strong></p>
                    <br />
                    <p><span style="font-size: 13px;"><strong>Apollo Bay to Warrnambool<br />
                    </strong></span><strong>Distance:</strong> 169 km, <strong>Approx. travel time:</strong> 2 hrs 30 min</p>
                    <p>Continue your journey west from Apollo Bay and walk through breathtaking wilderness, explore secluded beaches or the forest canopy via the Otway Fly Tree Top Walk in the Otway National Park.</p>
                    <p>Thereafter, drive to Port Campbell National Park to witness nature's marvellous rock formations. This is the most famous section of the Great Ocean Road featuring an amazing collection of rock formations known as the Twelve Apostles - carved out of the headland by the fierce waves of the southern ocean. Spectacular shapes in the nearby cliffs, including Loch Ard Gorge, the Arch, the Blowhole and London Bridge as well as Wreck Beach are also not to be missed.</p>
                    <p>Adventurous sightseers can take the boardwalks that lead to lookouts and great views of the coastline, which is dotted with plaques and signs that mark the places where more than 160 ships floundered along the aptly named Shipwreck Coast.</p>
                    <p>An exhilarating helicopter experience over the coastline and rock formations will mark an unforgettable experience!</p>
                    <p>This leg of the journey ends at Warrnambool, the only city on the Shipwreck Coast. Set on the edge of Lady Bay, Warrnambool boasts a colourful history, which can be explored at the Flagstaff Hill Maritime Museum. Whales migrate along the part of the coastline and can be spotted from lookouts and on boat trips between May and October.</p>
                    <p>Overnight: Warrnambool</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-top: 5px; padding-bottom: 10px;" colspan="2">
                    <p style="text-align: center;"><img alt="" src="/contentimages/horizontal-line-grey.jpg" /></p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-top: 5px; padding-right: 10px;">
                    <p style="text-align: center;"><span style="color: rgb(105, 105, 105); font-size: 10px;"><img alt="Mount William Ranges, Halls Gap" src="/contentimages/Campaigns/campaigns-sg-self-drive-vic-7days-hl02.jpg" /></span></p>
                    <p style="text-align: center;"><span style="color: rgb(105, 105, 105); font-size: 10px;">Mount William Ranges, Halls Gap</span></p>
                    </td>
                    <td valign="top">
                    <p><a name="day3"></a><strong><span style="font-size: 13px;">Day 03</span></strong></p>
                    <br />
                    <p><strong><span style="font-size: 13px;">Warrnambool to Halls Gap</span></strong><br />
                    <strong>Distance:</strong> 158 km, <strong>Approx. travel time:</strong> 2 hrs 30 min</p>
                    <p>Head to the quaint fishing township of Port Fairy from Warrnambool for morning tea. Discover more about maritime history at Port Fairy, a busy fishing port and one of the state's earliest settled coastal villages. Take the time to explore the town's streets and over 50 nineteenth-century buildings classified by the National Trust. From Port Fairy, the Great Southern Touring Route turns north, away from the coast and towards the natural beauty of the Grampians mountain range.</p>
                    <p>Dunkeld is a beautiful village on the edge of the Grampians. The Grampians National Park is famous for some of the most spectacular scenery in Australia and is the perfect place for both relaxation and adventure. Walk to cascading waterfalls or lookouts overlooking rugged mountain ranges and impressive rock formations, and explore bushland and discover the diverse wildlife of the region and a wide variety of birds.</p>
                    <p>For the more adventurous, try rock climbing or abseiling on the cliffs, pinnacles and bluffs of the Grampians. Guides and equipment are available, so even a novice can give it a go. Along with its natural beauty, the Grampians are home to the largest collection of Aboriginal rock paintings in Victoria.</p>
                    <p>The town of Halls Gap is the tourist hub of the region. Surrounded by the Wonderland and Mount William ranges, it is a great place to base yourself as you explore the Grampians. It offers accommodation ranging from 5-star villas to basic camping grounds and is close to many of the Grampians' major attractions, including Boroka and Reed's lookouts, McKenzie Falls, Lake Bellfield and Zumsteins.</p>
                    <p>Overnight: Halls Gap</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-top: 5px; padding-bottom: 20px;" colspan="2">
                    <p style="text-align: center;"><img alt="" src="/contentimages/horizontal-line-grey.jpg" /></p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-top: 5px; padding-right: 10px;">
                    <p><img alt="Grampains National Park" src="/contentimages/Campaigns/campaigns-sg-self-drive-vic-7days-hl03.jpg" /></p>
                    <p style="text-align: center;"><span style="color: rgb(105, 105, 105); font-size: 10px;">Grampians National Park</span></p>
                    </td>
                    <td valign="top">
                    <p><a name="day4"></a><strong><span style="font-size: 13px;">Day 04</span></strong></p>
                    <br />
                    <p><strong><span style="font-size: 13px;">Halls Gap</span></strong></p>
                    <p><strong><span style="font-size: 13px;"></span></strong>Halls Gap nestles right in the heart of the majestic Grampians National Park with its wildflowers and waterfalls, alongside local village stores, alluring wineries and colourful galleries.</p>
                    <p>Explore the scenic drives, lookouts, and waterfalls in the beautiful Grampians National Park. Brambuk, a National Park &amp; Cultural Centre located 2.5 kilometres South of Halls Gap shops, is a good starting point for anyone interested in exploring the park.</p>
                    <p>Learn about the diverse culture of the indigenous people at Brambuk and join a tour of the many ancient aboriginal rock art sites in the area.</p>
                    <p>Explore the park by foot and choose from an extensive network of trails criss-crossing the area. Walks such as Venus Baths, Boronia Peak and Chatauqua start from Halls Gap. Alternatively, drive to walks such as MacKenzie Falls, Hollow Mountain and The Pinnacle which offer a wonderful variety of vegetation and landscapes.</p>
                    <p>View Australian native animals in the wild throughout the Grampians National Park or visit the Halls Gap Zoo on Halls Gap-Ararat Road. You will get to see kangaroos, wallabies, koalas, wombats, emus, possums and dingoes. Don't miss exotic animals like meerkats, giraffe and red pandas in a bushland setting.</p>
                    <p>Overnight: Halls Gap</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-top: 5px; padding-bottom: 20px;" colspan="2">
                    <p style="text-align: center;"><img alt="" src="/contentimages/horizontal-line-grey.jpg" /></p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-top: 5px; padding-right: 10px;">
                    <p><img alt="Sovereign Hill, Ballarat, Victoria" src="/contentimages/Campaigns/campaigns-sg-self-drive-vic-7days-hl04.jpg" /></p>
                    <p style="text-align: center;"><span style="color: rgb(105, 105, 105); font-size: 10px;">Sovereign Hill, Ballarat</span></p>
                    </td>
                    <td valign="top">
                    <p><a name="day5"></a><strong><span style="font-size: 13px;">Day 05</span></strong></p>
                    <br />
                    <p><strong><span style="font-size: 13px;">Halls Gap to Ballarat</span></strong><br />
                    <strong>Distance:</strong> 185 km, <strong>Approx. travel time:</strong> 2 hrs 30 min</p>
                    <p>Leaving the Grampians, the Great Southern Touring Route heads north towards the Goldfields. Call into one of the many wineries in the township of Great Western where wine has been produced for over 150 years. Take a tour of the 3km of underground cellars at Seppelt.</p>
                    <p>South-east of Stawell is Ararat, a thriving community settled during the gold rush of the 1800s. Visit the former gaol for the criminally insane, heritage centre and museum, which commemorate the history and culture of the Chinese immigrants who settled in the region to seek their fortune.</p>
                    <p>From here the route turns east to Ballarat, one of Victoria's largest cities. Built with the wealth of the gold rush, much of the opulence of the era is still on display in the grand public buildings, hotels and historic streetscapes. Ballarat was the site of the world's largest deposit of alluvial gold and also of the Eureka Stockade - the famous uprising of miners against the government licensing system.</p>
                    <p>Step back to the gold-mining era of the 1850s at Sovereign Hill. See blacksmiths at work, people dressed in Victorian costumes, pan for gold or go down an underground mine. Get up close with Australian wildlife at the wildlife park.</p>
                    <p>Overnight: Ballarat</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-top: 5px; padding-bottom: 10px;" colspan="2">
                    <p style="text-align: center;"><img alt="" src="/contentimages/horizontal-line-grey.jpg" /></p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-top: 5px; padding-right: 10px;">
                    <p><img alt="Daylesford, Victoria" src="/contentimages/Campaigns/campaigns-sg-self-drive-vic-7days-hl05.jpg" /></p>
                    <p style="text-align: center;"><span style="color: rgb(105, 105, 105); font-size: 10px;">Daylesford, Victoria</span></p>
                    </td>
                    <td valign="top">
                    <p><a name="day6"></a><strong><span style="font-size: 13px;">Day 06</span></strong></p>
                    <br />
                    <p><strong><span style="font-size: 13px;">Ballarat to Daylesford</span></strong></p>
                    <p>With Australia's largest concentration of naturally occurring mineral springs, a visit to the heart of Spa Country refreshes both body and soul. You can also get to discover natural waters straight from the spring. Just look out for signs pointing to townships like Daylesford, Hepburn Springs, Kyneton and Blackwood. Make time for some soothing and pampering treatments at one of the many day spas. Book ahead to enjoy the myriad of spa options at the twin towns of Daylesford and Hepburn Springs.</p>
                    <p>A stroll along the main street of Daylesford reveals a good selection of caf&eacute;s, restaurants, pubs, and takeaway fares. The superb quality of restaurants and local produce in the area have made the place a favourite weekend retreat for Melburnians. For art lovers, you will be delighted to know that a diverse community of artists call this region home. It is easy to discover unique, locally made arts and crafts here. Wearable art and decorative pieces are created in the studios of jewellery makers, silversmiths, glass blowers and ceramists. Glass artists, painters, printmakers, Koori artists, mural painters, textile artists and potters also add to the colour and texture of this vibrant, artistic region.</p>
                    <p>For a leisurely afternoon, consider the many antique stores and galleries in the area displaying sculpture, fine art, pottery, antiques, local fare and jewellery. Don't miss the lavender farms, where you can find premium lavender, oils and grapes. Italian-speaking Swiss, who came to Daylesford in search of gold, built the stone farm buildings in the 1850s. You can take a walk through neatly patterned lavender fields, herb and cottage gardens. Enjoy browsing through a large range of home grown lavender products in the shop. Alternatively, enjoy light lunches and delicious teas made from their own and other local produce.</p>
                    <p>Overnight: Daylesford</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-top: 5px; padding-bottom: 10px;" colspan="2">
                    <p style="text-align: center;"><img alt="" src="/contentimages/horizontal-line-grey.jpg" /></p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-top: 5px; padding-right: 10px;">
                    <p><img alt="Lake Daylesford, Victoria" src="/contentimages/Campaigns/campaigns-sg-self-drive-vic-7days-hl07-1.jpg" /></p>
                    <p style="text-align: center;"><span style="color: rgb(105, 105, 105); font-size: 10px;">Lake Daylesford, Victoria</span></p>
                    </td>
                    <td valign="top">
                    <p><a name="day7"></a><span style="font-size: 13px;"><strong>Day 07</strong></span></p>
                    <br />
                    <p><strong><span style="font-size: 13px;">Daylesford to Melbourne<br />
                    </span></strong><strong>Distance:</strong> 170 km, <strong>Approx. travel time:</strong> 1 hr 30 min</p>
                    <p>Spend time taking in the pleasures of the local hot springs before making the journey back to Melbourne. Spoil yourself with a luxurious private mineral spa bathing experience before spending the night enjoying the myriad of delights that romantic Melbourne has to offer.</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-top: 30px;" colspan="2">
                    <p style="text-align: right;"> <a href="#top">Back to Top</a></p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
            </tbody>
        </table>
    ]]></txt_Information>
            
        </TopCategoryHighlights></con_Body>
    <con_RHSModules><AtaGlance isTemplate="1">
<hdl_Title><![CDATA[Best of Australian Roadtrips]]></hdl_Title>
<img_Map><![CDATA[]]></img_Map>
<stf_Title1><![CDATA[]]></stf_Title1>
<stf_Title2><![CDATA[]]></stf_Title2>
<stf_Title3><![CDATA[]]></stf_Title3>
<stf_Title4><![CDATA[]]></stf_Title4>
<stf_Title5><![CDATA[]]></stf_Title5>
<txt_Description1><![CDATA[
        <table>
            <tbody>
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-top: 1px; padding-right: 10px;">
                    <p><a name="top"></a><img alt="" src="/contentimages/arrow-green.png" /></p>
                    </td>
                    <td valign="top">
                    <p><a href="/self-drive-sg.xml" target="_self">Home</a></p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-top: 1px; padding-right: 10px;">
                    <p><img alt="" src="/contentimages/arrow-green.png" /></p>
                    </td>
                    <td valign="top">
                    <p><a href="/self-drive-sa-sg.xml" target="_self">Adelaide's Nature &amp; Sea Vine Trail</a> </p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-top: 1px; padding-right: 10px;">
                    <p><img alt="" src="/contentimages/arrow-green.png" /></p>
                    </td>
                    <td valign="top">
                    <p>
                    <a href="/self-drive-wa-sg.xml" target="_self">Great Southern &amp; Golden Outback</a></p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-top: 1px; padding-right: 10px;">
                    <p><img alt="" src="/contentimages/arrow-green.png" /></p>
                    </td>
                    <td valign="top">
                    <p> <a href="/self-drive-vic-sg.xml" target="_self">Great Southern Touring Route</a></p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-top: 1px; padding-right: 10px;">
                    <p><img alt="" src="/contentimages/arrow-green.png" /></p>
                    </td>
                    <td valign="top">
                    <p><a href="/self-drive-qld-sg.xml" target="_self">Southern Queensland</a></p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-top: 1px; padding-right: 10px;">
                    <p><img alt="" src="/contentimages/arrow-green.png" /></p>
                    </td>
                    <td valign="top">
                    <p> <a href="/self-drive-tas-sg.xml" target="_self">Tasmanian Food &amp; Nature Trail</a></p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-top: 1px; padding-right: 10px;">
                    <p><img alt="" src="/contentimages/arrow-green.png" /></p>
                    </td>
                    <td valign="top">
                    <p> <a href="/self-drive-nsw-sg.xml" target="_self">The Legendary Pacific Coast</a></p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-top: 1px; padding-right: 10px;">
                    <p><img alt="" src="/contentimages/arrow-green.png" /></p>
                    </td>
                    <td valign="top">
                    <p> <a href="/self-drive-nt-sg.xml" target="_self">Nature's Way</a></p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-top: 1px; padding-right: 10px;">
                    <p><img alt="" src="/contentimages/arrow-green.png" /></p>
                    </td>
                    <td valign="top">
                    <p><a href="/self-drive-offers-sg.xml" target="_self">Offers</a></p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
            </tbody>
        </table>
        <br />
    ]]></txt_Description1>
<txt_Description2><![CDATA[]]></txt_Description2>
<txt_Description3><![CDATA[]]></txt_Description3>
<txt_Description4><![CDATA[]]></txt_Description4>
<txt_Description5><![CDATA[]]></txt_Description5>
</AtaGlance><AtaGlance isTemplate="1">
<hdl_Title><![CDATA[Offers]]></hdl_Title>
<img_Map><![CDATA[]]></img_Map>
<stf_Title1><![CDATA[See the best of Australia, with Singapore Airlines]]></stf_Title1>
<stf_Title2><![CDATA[Take a Roadtrip with HERTZ]]></stf_Title2>
<stf_Title3><![CDATA[STA Travel]]></stf_Title3>
<stf_Title4><![CDATA[PriceBreaker]]></stf_Title4>
<stf_Title5><![CDATA[MISA Travel]]></stf_Title5>
<txt_Description1><![CDATA[
        <p style="text-align: left;"><a href="http://www.singaporeair.com/jsp/cms/en_UK/promotions/tourism-australia.jsp" onclick="ntptEventTag('ev=PartnerLead&amp;PartnerId=singaporeair');" target="_blank"><img alt="" style="padding-top: 5px; padding-right: 10px; padding-bottom: 30px; float: left;" src="/contentimages/Campaigns/campaigns-sg-self-drive-rhs-singaporeairlines-hl.jpg" /></a>Whether it’s indulging in the flavours of a culinary paradise, or simply waking up to a breathtaking sunrise, there’s no better time to visit Australia than now. En-route, choose from a wide range of entertainment options and enjoy the inflight service even other airlines talk about.</p>
        <table>
            <tbody>
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-top: 3px; padding-right: 10px;">
                    <p><img alt="" src="/contentimages/arrow-green.png" /></p>
                    </td>
                    <td valign="middle">
                    <p><a href="http://www.singaporeair.com/jsp/cms/en_UK/promotions/tourism-australia.jsp" onclick="ntptEventTag('ev=PartnerLead&amp;PartnerId=singaporeair');" target="_blank">Find Out More</a></p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
            </tbody>
        </table>
    ]]></txt_Description1>
<txt_Description2><![CDATA[
        <p style="text-align: left;"><a href="http://www.hertz.com.sg/rentacar/specialoffers/index.jsp?targetPage=specialOffersPerCategoryView.jsp&Category=U " onclick="ntptEventTag('ev=PartnerLead&amp;PartnerId=hertz');" target="_blank"><img alt="" style="padding-top: 5px; padding-right: 10px; padding-bottom: 30px; float: left;" src="/contentimages/Campaigns/campaigns-sg-self-drive-rhs-hertz-hl.jpg" /></a> Experience the freedom of exploring Australia on wheels with HERTZ. Take advantage of our time-limited offers today to stretch your dollars.</p>
        <table>
            <tbody>
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-top: 3px; padding-right: 10px;">
                    <p><img alt="" src="/contentimages/arrow-green.png" /></p>
                    </td>
                    <td valign="middle">
                    <p><a href="http://www.hertz.com.sg/rentacar/specialoffers/index.jsp?targetPage=specialOffersPerCategoryView.jsp&Category=U " onclick="ntptEventTag('ev=PartnerLead&amp;PartnerId=hertz');" target="_blank">Find Out More</a></p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
            </tbody>
        </table>
    ]]></txt_Description2>
<txt_Description3><![CDATA[
        <br />
        <p><a href="http://www.statravel.com.sg/australia" onclick="ntptEventTag('ev=PartnerLead&amp;PartnerId=statravel');" target="_blank"><img alt="" style="border: 0px solid currentcolor; padding-top: 5px; padding-right: 10px; padding-bottom: 70px; float: left;" src="/contentimages/Campaigns/campaigns-sg-self-drive-rhs-offer01.jpg" /></a>STA Travel knows Australia &amp; campervans! Road trips are a must-do when heading down under. All you need is some friends, maybe a surfboard and prepare for a road trip of a lifetime!  </p>
        <table>
            <tbody>
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-top: 3px; padding-right: 10px;">
                    <p><img alt="" src="/contentimages/arrow-green.png" /></p>
                    </td>
                    <td valign="middle">
                    <p><a href="http://www.statravel.com.sg/australia" onclick="ntptEventTag('ev=PartnerLead&amp;PartnerId=statravel');" target="_blank">Find Out More</a></p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
            </tbody>
        </table>
        <br />
    ]]></txt_Description3>
<txt_Description4><![CDATA[
        <br />
        <p><a href="http://pricebreaker.travel/PBHolidayDeals.aspx?dest=Australia" onclick="ntptEventTag('ev=PartnerLead&amp;PartnerId=pricebreaker');" target="_blank"><img alt="" style="border: 0px solid currentcolor; padding-top: 5px; padding-right: 10px; padding-bottom: 15px; float: left;" src="/contentimages/Campaigns/campaigns-sg-self-drive-rhs-offer02.jpg" /></a>Explore Australia at your own pace with PriceBreaker. Book by 31 Oct and enjoy $100 off per couple.</p>
        <table>
            <tbody>
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-top: 3px; padding-right: 10px;">
                    <p><img alt="" src="/contentimages/arrow-green.png" /></p>
                    </td>
                    <td valign="middle">
                    <p><a href="http://pricebreaker.travel/PBHolidayDeals.aspx?dest=Australia" onclick="ntptEventTag('ev=PartnerLead&amp;PartnerId=pricebreaker');" target="_blank">Find Out More</a></p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
            </tbody>
        </table>
        <br />
    ]]></txt_Description4>
<txt_Description5><![CDATA[
        <br />
        <p><a href="http://www.airfares.com.sg/promotions/australia-hero-route/index.htm" onclick="ntptEventTag('ev=PartnerLead&amp;PartnerId=airfares');" target="_blank"><img alt="" style="border: 0px solid currentcolor; padding-top: 5px; padding-right: 10px; padding-bottom: 15px; float: left;" src="/contentimages/Campaigns/campaigns-sg-self-drive-rhs-offer03.jpg" /></a> Come onboard a wondrous self-drive journey of a life time with MISA Travel!</p>
        <table>
            <tbody>
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-top: 3px; padding-right: 10px;">
                    <p><img alt="" src="/contentimages/arrow-green.png" /></p>
                    </td>
                    <td valign="middle">
                    <p><a href="http://www.airfares.com.sg/promotions/australia-hero-route/index.htm" onclick="ntptEventTag('ev=PartnerLead&amp;PartnerId=airfares');" target="_blank">Find Out More</a></p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
            </tbody>
        </table>
        <br />
    ]]></txt_Description5>
</AtaGlance></con_RHSModules>
    <con_Category></con_Category>
    <lst_Subpages>
    </lst_Subpages>
</StandardCampaignLayout>
    </con_Body>
    <lst_Subpages>
    </lst_Subpages>
</ConsumerBaseFoundation>