<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<ConsumerBaseFoundation pageID="15260" isTemplate="1">
    <breadcrumb>
        <element level="1">
            <headline><![CDATA[Homepage ]]></headline>
            <href><![CDATA[/index.xml]]></href>
        </element>
<element level="2">
            <headline><![CDATA[Tools and Campaigns]]></headline>
            <href><![CDATA[/tools-campaigns.xml]]></href>
        </element>
<element level="4">
            <headline><![CDATA[IN]]></headline>
            <href><![CDATA[/15223.ignore]]></href>
        </element>
<element level="5">
            <headline><![CDATA[Traveller Testimonials]]></headline>
            <href><![CDATA[/traveller-testimonials-in.xml]]></href>
        </element>
<element level="6">
            <headline><![CDATA[Great Stories About Australia]]></headline>
            <href><![CDATA[/traveller-testimonials-more-in.xml]]></href>
        </element>

    </breadcrumb>
    <img_background><![CDATA[/contentimages/Campaigns/campaigns-sydney2.jpg]]></img_background>
    <hdl_Title><![CDATA[Great Stories About Australia]]></hdl_Title>
    <img_Banner><![CDATA[]]></img_Banner>
    <img_SearchThumbnail><![CDATA[/thumbnails/campaigns-sydney2-search.jpg]]></img_SearchThumbnail>
    <img_Thumbnail><![CDATA[/contentimages/about-key-facts-weather-sydney-th.jpg]]></img_Thumbnail>
    <opt_HideInBreadcrumbs><![CDATA[Show]]></opt_HideInBreadcrumbs>
    <opt_HidePage><![CDATA[no]]></opt_HidePage>
    <opt_hideTitle><![CDATA[0]]></opt_hideTitle>
    <opt_hide_in_sitemap><![CDATA[no]]></opt_hide_in_sitemap>
    <opt_IncludeVideo><![CDATA[0]]></opt_IncludeVideo>
    <opt_isHubPage><![CDATA[0]]></opt_isHubPage>
    <opt_isNewWindow><![CDATA[_self]]></opt_isNewWindow>
    <opt_PageLayout><![CDATA[]]></opt_PageLayout>
    <opt_PartnerLead><![CDATA[no]]></opt_PartnerLead>
    <stf_description><![CDATA[]]></stf_description>
    <stf_ExcludedCountries><![CDATA[]]></stf_ExcludedCountries>
    <stf_hideInXmlSitemap><![CDATA[]]></stf_hideInXmlSitemap>
    <stf_ImageLocation><![CDATA[]]></stf_ImageLocation>
    <stf_intro_title><![CDATA[]]></stf_intro_title>
    <stf_IsExternalSiteArticle><![CDATA[]]></stf_IsExternalSiteArticle>
    <stf_IsMobile><![CDATA[n]]></stf_IsMobile>
    <stf_keywords><![CDATA[]]></stf_keywords>
    <stf_LinkLearnMore><![CDATA[Learn More]]></stf_LinkLearnMore>
    <stf_NavigationTagLine><![CDATA[]]></stf_NavigationTagLine>
    <stf_PageHeading><![CDATA[Traveller Testimonials]]></stf_PageHeading>
    <stf_TargetedCountries><![CDATA[]]></stf_TargetedCountries>
    <stf_TrackingTitle><![CDATA[]]></stf_TrackingTitle>
    <TA_Title><![CDATA[Traveller Testimonials: Great Stories About Australia]]></TA_Title>
    <txt_Intro>
        <![CDATA[]]>
    </txt_Intro>
    <txt_MobileContentOnly>
        <![CDATA[]]>
    </txt_MobileContentOnly>
    <txt_SpotlightTag>
        <![CDATA[]]>
    </txt_SpotlightTag>
    <txt_Teaser>
        <![CDATA[]]>
    </txt_Teaser>
    <con_Body>
        <SubPageLayout isTemplate="1">
    <con_Banner>
        
    </con_Banner>
    <con_RHSModules>
        <AtaGlance isTemplate="1">
<hdl_Title><![CDATA[More Testimonials]]></hdl_Title>
<img_Map><![CDATA[]]></img_Map>
<stf_Title1><![CDATA[]]></stf_Title1>
<stf_Title2><![CDATA[]]></stf_Title2>
<stf_Title3><![CDATA[]]></stf_Title3>
<stf_Title4><![CDATA[]]></stf_Title4>
<stf_Title5><![CDATA[]]></stf_Title5>
<txt_Description1><![CDATA[
        <table border="0" cellspacing="0" cellpadding="0" width="100%">
            <tbody>
                <tr>
                    <td>
                    <p><img alt="" src="http://www.australia.com/contentimages/arrow.gif" /></p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                    <p><a href="/traveller-testimonials-in.xml" target="_self"><strong>Home</strong></a></p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
            </tbody>
        </table>
        <br />
    ]]></txt_Description1>
<txt_Description2><![CDATA[]]></txt_Description2>
<txt_Description3><![CDATA[]]></txt_Description3>
<txt_Description4><![CDATA[]]></txt_Description4>
<txt_Description5><![CDATA[]]></txt_Description5>
</AtaGlance>
    </con_RHSModules>
    <con_Video>
        
    </con_Video>
    <con_Body>
        <TopCategoryHighlights isTemplate="1">
            <stf_Heading><![CDATA[Great Stories About Australia]]></stf_Heading>
            <stf_InformationTitle><![CDATA[]]></stf_InformationTitle>
            <txt_Information><![CDATA[
        <a name="aditya"></a><br />
    ]]></txt_Information>
            <con_CenterContent>
                <CenterContent isTemplate="1">
                    <hdl_Title><![CDATA[Aditya Bhat]]></hdl_Title>
                    <img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/Campaigns/campaigns-in-testimonials-aditya-bhat.jpg" alt="Aditya Bhat">]]></img_MainImage>
                    <stf_Caption><![CDATA[Aditya Bhat]]></stf_Caption>
                    <anc_link><![CDATA[]]></anc_link>
                    <txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[
        I had the opportunity of Producing 2 special shows for Tourism Australia – An episode dedicated to Sydney and one dedicated to Melbourne. I had been to 22 countries earlier, but let me tell you that this country had more to offer in one destination. Sydney was a super mix of Adventure, Sightseeing, night life, food and fashion, while Melbourne was beautiful fauna, wildlife and culture. The people were extremely warm and large hearted and my experience was less of a work environment and more of an actual holiday while I was on shoot. 
        <p>The journey by Qantas was extremely comfortable and overall stay was indeed very memorable. My only regret being that I could just visit Sydney and Melbourne, and Australia has so much more to offer in other parts. Looking forward to visiting Queensland – where I want to try my hand at world class adventure. To summarize – Australia is the BEST Holiday destination, which has got everything for every member of the family! </p>
        <p style="text-align: right;"><span style="font-size: 9px;"><a href="#top">Back To Top</a></span></p>
    ]]>
                    </txt_Information>
                </CenterContent><CenterContent isTemplate="1">
                    <hdl_Title><![CDATA[Aparna Pednekar]]></hdl_Title>
                    <img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/Campaigns/campaigns-in-testimonials-aparna-pednekar.jpg" alt="Aparna Pednekar">]]></img_MainImage>
                    <stf_Caption><![CDATA[Aparna Pednekar]]></stf_Caption>
                    <anc_link><![CDATA[]]></anc_link>
                    <txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[
        I visited Australia for the first time in the spring of 2009, and was struck by the beauty and variety of sights/activities the continent had to offer. For me, weather is a make-or-breaker and Australia’s delightful, sunny climate was an instant thumbs up. I’m happy my first encounter with Australia included slightly unusual suspects – Perth, Adelaide and Hobart. The interactions with Tourism Australia officials at each destination were warm, informal and professional. This is a happy country; the people are chilled out, the natural sights are expansive and breathtaking, urban life is boho-chic. But I have to admit, the highlight was the food and wine. From Greek, Italian, Indian, Chinese, to the local wines and cheeses (the ewe milk cheeses at Hobart stood out!) Australia is a must-visit for foodies. There’s so much yet to see and experience. I’d hop over again anytime!
        <p style="text-align: right;"><span style="font-size: 9px;"><a href="#top">Back To Top</a></span></p>
        <a name="ashish"></a>
    ]]>
                    </txt_Information>
                </CenterContent><CenterContent isTemplate="1">
                    <hdl_Title><![CDATA[Ashish Bhasin]]></hdl_Title>
                    <img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/Campaigns/campaigns-in-testimonials-ashish-bhasin.jpg" alt="Ashish Bhasin">]]></img_MainImage>
                    <stf_Caption><![CDATA[Ashish Bhasin]]></stf_Caption>
                    <anc_link><![CDATA[]]></anc_link>
                    <txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[
        Our Australia holiday was one of the best we ever had. The natural beauty was stunning and as a family we did things we had never done before……from feeding wallabies and kangaroos to watching penguins come back home in the night. The Great Ocean Drive was breathtaking. From the sophistication of Sydney to the natural beauty in Victoria, Australia offered us all we wanted. Will definitely go back soon!
        <p style="text-align: right;"><span style="font-size: 9px;"><a href="#top">Back To Top</a></span></p>
        <a name="aspi"></a>
    ]]>
                    </txt_Information>
                </CenterContent><CenterContent isTemplate="1">
                    <hdl_Title><![CDATA[Aspi Sarkari]]></hdl_Title>
                    <img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/Campaigns/campaigns-in-testimonials-aspi-sarkari.jpg" alt="Aspi Sarkari">]]></img_MainImage>
                    <stf_Caption><![CDATA[Aspi Sarkari]]></stf_Caption>
                    <anc_link><![CDATA[]]></anc_link>
                    <txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[
        If I have to list one of my most favorite holiday destinations, I would definitely vote for Australia! A melting pot filled with an array of activities, Australia has something in store for every traveler. I was floored by the multi cultural cosmopolitan cities and quaint countryside co existing harmoniously. I also have very fond memories of visiting Cairns &amp; Gold Coast! The enormous Great Barrier Reef with its untouched natural beauty left me completely mesmerized. 
        <p>It’s hard to summarize the wonders of Australia – right from the iconic attractions, delicious food and a scintillating beach and night life! I have my calendar marked for my next trip and would highly recommend for all to discover and experience Australia in all its splendour!</p>
        <p style="text-align: right;"><span style="font-size: 9px;"><a href="#top">Back To Top</a></span></p>
        <a name="Bakshish"></a>
    ]]>
                    </txt_Information>
                </CenterContent><CenterContent isTemplate="1">
                    <hdl_Title><![CDATA[Bakshish Dean]]></hdl_Title>
                    <img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/Campaigns/campaigns-in-testimonials-bakshish-dean.jpg" alt="Bakshish Dean">]]></img_MainImage>
                    <stf_Caption><![CDATA[Bakshish Dean]]></stf_Caption>
                    <anc_link><![CDATA[]]></anc_link>
                    <txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[
        Australia tops the list of my favorite countries in the world...the food, culture and wine is simply awe inspiring. I especially enjoyed the Longest Lunch at Melbourne's food and wine festival last year. Look forward to exploring more in the future...wild life also being one of my interests.
        <p style="text-align: right;"><span style="font-size: 9px;"><a href="#top">Back To Top</a></span></p>
        <a name="Farzana"></a>
    ]]>
                    </txt_Information>
                </CenterContent><CenterContent isTemplate="1">
                    <hdl_Title><![CDATA[Farzana Suri]]></hdl_Title>
                    <img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/Campaigns/campaigns-in-testimonials-farzana-suri.jpg" alt="Farzana Suri">]]></img_MainImage>
                    <stf_Caption><![CDATA[Farzana Suri]]></stf_Caption>
                    <anc_link><![CDATA[]]></anc_link>
                    <txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[
        Australia was the 40th destination in my ‘must-see-countries’ list. In fact, I was quite disappointed that during November, the only countries I could travel to were Australia, NZ and SA. Who wanted to go to a land of desert and loud people!!
        <p>I chose Australia albeit reluctantly as I had a friend in Sydney. At least that would be a highpoint – visiting him after many years!</p>
        <p>I must confess – I was surprised on my visit to Australia. I visited Gold Coast, Cairns, Melbourne and Sydney. The people are fantastic! Very friendly with a superb sense of humour. I mean, after the kind of stories the media was brandishing about how Indians were badly treated, I was a tad apprehensive. But, this is all false! One incident or a couple of incidents do not make it a regular happening.  Australians are a truly chilled out lot.</p>
        <p>And Australia is soooooo green and beautiful! It could put the Europeans to shame with its lovely meadows, forests, vineyards, gardens, the wildlife, the pan global food….I could simply go on. Lovely beaches…one of the best in the world. Makes the South of France seem like a poor cousin! Pardonnez moi.</p>
        <p>Please visit Oz. Am certainly planning to visit again to explore the Outback and the West Coast.</p>
        <p style="text-align: right;"><span style="font-size: 9px;"><a href="#top">Back To Top</a></span></p>
        <a name="Jaspreet"></a>
    ]]>
                    </txt_Information>
                </CenterContent><CenterContent isTemplate="1">
                    <hdl_Title><![CDATA[Jaspreet &amp; Manvir Chopra]]></hdl_Title>
                    <img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/Campaigns/campaigns-in-testimonials-jaspreet-manvir-chopra.jpg" alt="Jaspreet & Manvir Chopra">]]></img_MainImage>
                    <stf_Caption><![CDATA[Jaspreet &amp; Manvir Chopra]]></stf_Caption>
                    <anc_link><![CDATA[]]></anc_link>
                    <txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[
        Australia : We love A U S T R A L I A because,
        <p>A : Absolute fun</p>
        <p>U : down Under</p>
        <p>S : beautiful Sun n Sand</p>
        <p>T : Trendy shopping</p>
        <p>R : great Restaurants</p>
        <p>A : lots of soft Adventure</p>
        <p>L : Lovely friendly people</p>
        <p>I : easily available Indian food</p>
        <p>A : All-in-one destination !!</p>
        <p style="text-align: right;"><span style="font-size: 9px;"><a href="#top">Back To Top</a></span></p>
        <a name="Joan"></a>
    ]]>
                    </txt_Information>
                </CenterContent><CenterContent isTemplate="1">
                    <hdl_Title><![CDATA[Joan Pinto ]]></hdl_Title>
                    <img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/Campaigns/campaigns-in-testimonials-joan-pinto.jpg" alt="Joan Pinto">]]></img_MainImage>
                    <stf_Caption><![CDATA[Joan Pinto ]]></stf_Caption>
                    <anc_link><![CDATA[]]></anc_link>
                    <txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[
        What most fascinates me about Melbourne is its energy. Most evident in the cafes, the architecture, and the public art.  From the whimsical and iconic street sculpture, The Purse to eye-opening, story-telling wall art in inconspicuous lanes all over the city, to the eclectic food –sushi, pumpkin flower tempura, ash cheese … Melbourne exudes culture. And I loved inhaling every breath of it. Especially the Queen Victoria market with its aromas, color and history.
        <p>The Yarra valley was a heady experience in many ways. A ride in a hot air balloon that sails over vineyards -  what better story to tell back home. Oh yes, that you tasted some of the best wines in the world; some bubbly at Dom Perignon, some red at Bertolli.</p>
        <p>Our days in Cairns were like a commune with nature: Swimming with fish at the Great Barrier Reef,discovering a whole city of coral underwater, watching crocodiles jump several feet…Patting a python at the Tropical Night zoo was an experience that I’ll show off about. </p>
        <p style="text-align: right;"><span style="font-size: 9px;"><a href="#top">Back To Top</a></span></p>
        <a name="Krishna"></a>
    ]]>
                    </txt_Information>
                </CenterContent><CenterContent isTemplate="1">
                    <hdl_Title><![CDATA[Krishna Bheda]]></hdl_Title>
                    <img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/Campaigns/campaigns-in-testimonials-krishna-bheda.jpg" alt="Krishna Bheda">]]></img_MainImage>
                    <stf_Caption><![CDATA[Krishna Bheda]]></stf_Caption>
                    <anc_link><![CDATA[]]></anc_link>
                    <txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[
        Zoommm........  The plane arrives at Melbourne Airport and I get to see this beautiful city. Melbourne CBD not only shows an essence of British architecture but is also carved with a great combination of architectural styles with a contemporary look. Yarra flows through the city, embellishing it with a scenic view. The city has got major attractions starting from the Federation square, Melbourne Cricket Ground, Victoria market, Old Melbourne Gaol, Melbourne Immigration Museum, Royal Melbourne Zoo and much more........ I loved the fireworks happening in the city at each hour and the sound of guitar played by street musicians soothes you completely. I also loved the fact that every next outlet I could see was either a lip-smacking Cafe or a prettifying Salon or of Sushi!
        <p style="text-align: right;"><span style="font-size: 9px;"><a href="#top">Back To Top</a></span></p>
        <a name="Kushroo"></a>
    ]]>
                    </txt_Information>
                </CenterContent><CenterContent isTemplate="1">
                    <hdl_Title><![CDATA[Kushroo]]></hdl_Title>
                    <img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/Campaigns/campaigns-in-testimonials-kushroo.jpg" alt="Kushroo">]]></img_MainImage>
                    <stf_Caption><![CDATA[Kushroo]]></stf_Caption>
                    <anc_link><![CDATA[]]></anc_link>
                    <txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[
        I fell in love with Australia when I was about 15. It might have been the koalas, kangaroos, the white beaches or pictures of the Opera House. Ever since I remember, I had an obsession with the land down under and a strong desire to travel there.  The city and people are so easy going that I wasn’t even worried about travelling there on my own.  Now, I have been there numerous times and hopefully have a lot more visits in the pipeline!
        <p style="text-align: right;"><span style="font-size: 9px;"><a href="#top">Back To Top</a></span></p>
        <a name="Magandeep"></a>
    ]]>
                    </txt_Information>
                </CenterContent><CenterContent isTemplate="1">
                    <hdl_Title><![CDATA[Magandeep Singh]]></hdl_Title>
                    <img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/Campaigns/campaigns-in-testimonials-magandeep-singh.jpg" alt="Magandeep Singh">]]></img_MainImage>
                    <stf_Caption><![CDATA[Magandeep Singh]]></stf_Caption>
                    <anc_link><![CDATA[]]></anc_link>
                    <txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[
        My trips to Australia have been truly memorable. The food and the wine was fantastic, the weather, perfect, and the people, friendly. I had a great time taking in the local sites and flavors – from Perth to Brisbane. Sydney was vibrant and Adelaide, peacefully calm and beautiful. The vastness of the country and the inherent diversity was truly humbling and it was with a promise to return that I started my journey back home.  
        <p style="text-align: right;"><span style="font-size: 9px;"><a href="#top">Back To Top</a></span></p>
        <a name="Marcellus"></a>
    ]]>
                    </txt_Information>
                </CenterContent><CenterContent isTemplate="1">
                    <hdl_Title><![CDATA[Marcellus Baptista]]></hdl_Title>
                    <img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/Campaigns/campaigns-in-testimonials-marcellus-baptista.jpg" alt="Marcellus Baptista">]]></img_MainImage>
                    <stf_Caption><![CDATA[Marcellus Baptista]]></stf_Caption>
                    <anc_link><![CDATA[]]></anc_link>
                    <txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[
        Sights, sounds and spirits!
        <p>My adventure in Australia was awesome. You could call it spiritual tourism! Yes, I was not only soaking in the sights and sounds but also sipping and savouring some of the best beers and wines in the land. This was at Tasmania, the island of temptation, under the land down under. It was hic, hic, hooray in Hobart, capital of Tasmania – starting the day with a glass of beer! The historic Cascade Brewery was the picturesque venue for this cheer. And the good life continued with fine wines at Moorilla Estate and Meadowbank Estateand whisky at Lark Distillery. Of course, good food at some of the finest restaurants and strolling at the Salamanca market on a Saturday added to the exciting experience. My Australia trip included a visit to Perth with a view of Sculptures by the Sea on Cottesloe beach, the Captain Cook cruise on the Swan River and beer at the Feral microbrewery. Cheers!</p>
        <p style="text-align: right;"><span style="font-size: 9px;"><a href="#top">Back To Top</a></span></p>
        <a name="nagsri"></a>
    ]]>
                    </txt_Information>
                </CenterContent><CenterContent isTemplate="1">
                    <hdl_Title><![CDATA[Nagsri Prasad]]></hdl_Title>
                    <img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/Campaigns/campaigns-in-testimonials-nagsri-prasad.jpg" alt="Nagsri Prasad">]]></img_MainImage>
                    <stf_Caption><![CDATA[Nagsri Prasad]]></stf_Caption>
                    <anc_link><![CDATA[]]></anc_link>
                    <txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[
        Australia is an extremely diverse country and caters to all ages, I love it for its rugged natural beauty, its adventure options, the wildlife parks, the food, its warm and friendly people and the list goes on.... It’s a fantastic destination for Honeymooners and Family holidays alike.
        <p>Australia Rocks !!!!</p>
        <p style="text-align: right;"><span style="font-size: 9px;"><a href="#top">Back To Top</a></span></p>
        <a name="nargis"></a>
    ]]>
                    </txt_Information>
                </CenterContent><CenterContent isTemplate="1">
                    <hdl_Title><![CDATA[Nargis S]]></hdl_Title>
                    <img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/Campaigns/campaigns-in-testimonials-nargis-s.jpg" alt="Nargis S">]]></img_MainImage>
                    <stf_Caption><![CDATA[Nargis S]]></stf_Caption>
                    <anc_link><![CDATA[]]></anc_link>
                    <txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[
        Australia has been one of my all time favorite destinations. The country just soaks you in its splendor. I visited the cities of Sydney &amp; Melbourne and completely fell in love with them. I was totally awestruck by the majestic Opera House and Sydney Harbour Bridge. Sydney boasts of rich lifestyles, shopping, nightlife and iconic attractions. Melbourne has one of the best nightlife, music, food and people. I loved my trip to Yarra Valley; the hot air balloon ride over vineyards was an out of the world experience. I have such fond memories of Australia and I know I’m going to come back for more!
        <p style="text-align: right;"><span style="font-size: 9px;"><a href="#top">Back To Top</a></span></p>
        <a name="Renita"></a>
    ]]>
                    </txt_Information>
                </CenterContent><CenterContent isTemplate="1">
                    <hdl_Title><![CDATA[Renita]]></hdl_Title>
                    <img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/Campaigns/campaigns-in-testimonials-renita.jpg" alt="Renita">]]></img_MainImage>
                    <stf_Caption><![CDATA[Renita]]></stf_Caption>
                    <anc_link><![CDATA[]]></anc_link>
                    <txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[
        Even while travelling I believe in going to the best of places. Sometimes, I travel for adventure and sometimes just to relax and Australia has never disappointed me.  Very few places manage to combine a relaxed pace with oodles of fun things to see and do like shopping, nightlife, amazing clean beaches, wonderful friendly people…I can go on.  It’s amazing how you can go to the same country again and again, yet experience something completely varied and different.  I definitely recommend a visit at least once in a lifetime.
        <p style="text-align: right;"><span style="font-size: 9px;"><a href="#top">Back To Top</a></span></p>
        <a name="Rupali"></a>
    ]]>
                    </txt_Information>
                </CenterContent><CenterContent isTemplate="1">
                    <hdl_Title><![CDATA[Rupali Dean ]]></hdl_Title>
                    <img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/Campaigns/campaigns-in-testimonials-rupali-dean.jpg" alt="Rupali Dean">]]></img_MainImage>
                    <stf_Caption><![CDATA[Rupali Dean ]]></stf_Caption>
                    <anc_link><![CDATA[]]></anc_link>
                    <txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[
        I am a diehard fan of Australia and can never get tired of visiting the country. I love it for everything...be it the food...wine...Culture.  In a few words Australia rocks!
        <p style="text-align: right;"><span style="font-size: 9px;"><a href="#top">Back To Top</a></span></p>
        <a name="Sangeeta"></a>
    ]]>
                    </txt_Information>
                </CenterContent><CenterContent isTemplate="1">
                    <hdl_Title><![CDATA[Sangeeta Berera]]></hdl_Title>
                    <img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/Campaigns/campaigns-in-testimonials-sangeeta-berera.jpg" alt="Sangeeta Berera">]]></img_MainImage>
                    <stf_Caption><![CDATA[Sangeeta Berera]]></stf_Caption>
                    <anc_link><![CDATA[]]></anc_link>
                    <txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[
        I like (love!) Australia because it's made up of people from all over the world so it's very diverse and interesting. they  also have a very laid back culture and generally everyone is very friendly and willing to help each other out when it really counts. So I would have to say that what I like so much about Australia is the people.
        <p>There are many things I love about Australia. I love the landscape, the people, the animals, the weather - the list goes on and on. I love the landscape, the 'land of sweeping plains, of rugged mountain ranges, of droughts and flooding rains". </p>
        <p style="text-align: right;"><span style="font-size: 9px;"><a href="#top">Back To Top</a></span></p>
        <a name="Sonia"></a>
    ]]>
                    </txt_Information>
                </CenterContent><CenterContent isTemplate="1">
                    <hdl_Title><![CDATA[Sonia Nazareth ]]></hdl_Title>
                    <img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/Campaigns/campaigns-in-testimonials-sonia-nazareth.jpg" alt="Sonia Nazareth">]]></img_MainImage>
                    <stf_Caption><![CDATA[Sonia Nazareth ]]></stf_Caption>
                    <anc_link><![CDATA[]]></anc_link>
                    <txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[
        Whichever way I look at it - the vast island continent that is Australia has touched me, run its delicate hands over me. Being so vast and diverse a terrain, it’s hard to pinpoint what exactly calls me to re-visit. Perhaps it is the seaplane ride over glamorous Sydney or the quirky art beat of Melbourne. Or the penguins’ procession on Phillip Island or the verdant vineyards of the Yarra Valley. Or even perhaps the anticipation of activities that fall in the varied landscape between the cities - in the deserts, coastal villages, forests and outback communities. Whatever it is, I always leave Australia with the feeling that it’s impossible to re-visit and not fall a bit more in love.
        <p style="text-align: right;"><span style="font-size: 9px;"><a href="#top">Back To Top</a></span></p>
        <a name="Sudhanshu"></a>
    ]]>
                    </txt_Information>
                </CenterContent><CenterContent isTemplate="1">
                    <hdl_Title><![CDATA[Sudhanshu Jaipuria]]></hdl_Title>
                    <img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/Campaigns/campaigns-in-testimonials-sudhanshu-jaipuria.jpg" alt="Sudhanshu Jaipuria">]]></img_MainImage>
                    <stf_Caption><![CDATA[Sudhanshu Jaipuria]]></stf_Caption>
                    <anc_link><![CDATA[]]></anc_link>
                    <txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[
        Australia is one such country that is beautiful in its diversity. With cosmopolitan cities on one side and thrilling outdoors on the other; it has something for even the most discerning traveller.
        <p style="text-align: right;"><span style="font-size: 9px;"><a href="#top">Back To Top</a></span></p>
        <a name="Tanushree"></a>
    ]]>
                    </txt_Information>
                </CenterContent><CenterContent isTemplate="1">
                    <hdl_Title><![CDATA[Tanushree Podder]]></hdl_Title>
                    <img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/Campaigns/campaigns-in-testimonials-tanushree-podder.jpg" alt="Tanushree Podder">]]></img_MainImage>
                    <stf_Caption><![CDATA[Tanushree Podder]]></stf_Caption>
                    <anc_link><![CDATA[]]></anc_link>
                    <txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[
        Blame it on the hours I spent watching Animal Planet. My longing to touch kangaroos, hold koalas and feed sea lions had almost turned into an obsession. It is said that when you want a thing badly, nature conspires to give it to you. That belief definitely came true in my case when I received an invitation to visit the Kangaroo Island, home to many gorgeous animal.
        <p>It was a surreal experience; miles and miles of territory with no carbon footprints and no pollution. It was like being on a different planet altogether. In fact, I think everyone would agree that there is nothing more heartwarming than the sight of the cute koala bears hugging trees. In a distance, we saw the kangaroos leaping around with abandon...It was the first time I was seeing them up close.</p>
        <p>The drive towards the Remarkable Rocks was a silent one. The Rocks seemed to spring out of the waters like giant formations. I sat there staring at the sea for a long time, unwilling to move. I saw kangaroos, sea lions, seals, wallabies, koalas, pelicans, echidnas and a host of birds. And there is more - the Pamdana Wildlife Park, KI Marine<br />
        Centre Pelican Feeding, Kelly Hill Caves, Emu Ridge and Admiral's Arch - but that would require another visit. My friend was right - KI is an unforgettable place.</p>
        <p style="text-align: right;"><span style="font-size: 9px;"><a href="#top">Back To Top</a></span></p>
        <a name="veneeta"></a>
    ]]>
                    </txt_Information>
                </CenterContent><CenterContent isTemplate="1">
                    <hdl_Title><![CDATA[Veneeta Rawat]]></hdl_Title>
                    <img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/Campaigns/campaigns-in-testimonials-veneeta-rawat.jpg" alt="Veneeta Rawat">]]></img_MainImage>
                    <stf_Caption><![CDATA[Veneeta Rawat]]></stf_Caption>
                    <anc_link><![CDATA[]]></anc_link>
                    <txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[
        I was taking a vacation after 10 years, and all what I wanted on my vacation, was relaxation. So, I decided to visit my friend who just purchased a new house in Melbourne, Victoria, Australia. We had decided it was a girls catch-up-trip and all what we wanted to do was enjoy some retail therapy, spa getaways and me-time. We had just the plan – we enjoyed a weekend at Daylesford – the spa town and enjoyed some amazing treatments at Peppers Springs Retreat &amp;Spa situated at Hepburn Springs, around 5 minutes from Daylesford. The perfect way to end our day after such luxurious treatments was to unwind with some great food and wine (both available a plenty, especially at small owner driven cafes – all fresh produce and organic). Another highlight of my driving jaunts, was a little known place – Erskine falls (aboriginal name Kitjarra Ngitj/Ngatanwarr) – this little waterfall, tucked away in the beautiful Great Otway National Park is a big draw with locals. During the summer the waterfall area and surrounds is dotted with family picnic makers and is a great place to unwind. Small treks can also be enjoyed from here.
        <p>Definitely one of my most memorable vacations, lots of laughter and fun.</p>
        <p style="text-align: right;"><span style="font-size: 9px;"><a href="#top">Back To Top</a></span></p>
    ]]>
                    </txt_Information>
                </CenterContent>
            </con_CenterContent>
        </TopCategoryHighlights>
    </con_Body>
</SubPageLayout>
    </con_Body>
    <lst_Subpages>
    </lst_Subpages>
</ConsumerBaseFoundation>