<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<BEBaseFoundation pageID="20752" isTemplate="1">
    <breadcrumb>
        <element level="1">
            <headline><![CDATA[Homepage ]]></headline>
            <href><![CDATA[/index.xml]]></href>
        </element>
<element level="2">
            <headline><![CDATA[Business Events]]></headline>
            <href><![CDATA[/21974.ignore]]></href>
        </element>
<element level="4">
            <headline><![CDATA[Where to go]]></headline>
            <href><![CDATA[/businessevents/where-to-go.xml]]></href>
        </element>
<element level="5">
            <headline><![CDATA[Perth]]></headline>
            <href><![CDATA[/businessevents/where-to-go/perth.xml]]></href>
        </element>
<element level="6">
            <headline><![CDATA[Itineraries]]></headline>
            <href><![CDATA[/businessevents/where-to-go/perth/itineraries.xml]]></href>
        </element>
<element level="7">
            <headline><![CDATA[Teambuilding and Wine Tasting ]]></headline>
            <href><![CDATA[/businessevents/where-to-go/perth/teambuilding-and-wine-tasting.xml]]></href>
        </element>

    </breadcrumb>
    <hdlPageTitle><![CDATA[Teambuilding and Wine Tasting ]]></hdlPageTitle>
    <img_background><![CDATA[]]></img_background>
    <opt_HideInBreadcrumbs><![CDATA[Show]]></opt_HideInBreadcrumbs>
    <opt_not_in_sitemap><![CDATA[No]]></opt_not_in_sitemap>
    <opt_show_in_navigation><![CDATA[Show]]></opt_show_in_navigation>
    <stf_MetaKeywords><![CDATA[]]></stf_MetaKeywords>
    <stf_meta_keywords><![CDATA[]]></stf_meta_keywords>
    <stf_meta_description><![CDATA[]]></stf_meta_description>
    <stf_NavSubHeader><![CDATA[]]></stf_NavSubHeader>
    <stf_NavTitle><![CDATA[Teambuilding and Wine Tasting ]]></stf_NavTitle>
    <stf_PageTitle><![CDATA[Teambuilding and Wine Tasting ]]></stf_PageTitle>
    <conMainContent>
        <BELayoutT8 isTemplate="1">
    <hdl_headline><![CDATA[Layout - T8 2644]]></hdl_headline>
    <stf_Title><![CDATA[Teambuilding and Wine Tasting ]]></stf_Title> 
    <opt_display_content_full_width><![CDATA[]]></opt_display_content_full_width>
    <con_sidebar>
        
    </con_sidebar> 
    <con_content>
        <BEGenericHeaderAndConentBody isTemplate="1">
    <hdl_headline><![CDATA[Generic - Header and Content Body 2645]]></hdl_headline>
    <img_DateIcon><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/business-events/iconStar.png" width="18" height="15">]]></img_DateIcon> 
    <img_DestinationIcon><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/business-events/iconWorld.png" width="18" height="15">]]></img_DestinationIcon>
    <img_EventTypeIcon><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/business-events/iconStar.png" width="18" height="15">]]></img_EventTypeIcon> 
    <img_DurationIcon><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/business-events/iconPax.png" width="18" height="15">]]></img_DurationIcon> 
    <opt_CaseStudy><![CDATA[0]]></opt_CaseStudy> 
    <stf_author><![CDATA[]]></stf_author>
    <stf_DateText><![CDATA[]]></stf_DateText>
    <stf_DelegatesText><![CDATA[]]></stf_DelegatesText>
    <stf_DestinationText><![CDATA[]]></stf_DestinationText>
    <stf_EventTypeText><![CDATA[]]></stf_EventTypeText>
    <stf_Header><![CDATA[]]></stf_Header>
    <stf_quote><![CDATA[]]></stf_quote>
    <stf_Title><![CDATA[]]></stf_Title>
    <txt_HTML><![CDATA[<strong>Day 1</strong>: Enjoy a tour of Perth on foot, taking in the Perth Mint and the Perth Concert Hall, before a delicious lunch at Barrack St Jetty, where you can take in the views of the sparkling Swan River and across the city from The Bell Tower. After lunch, visit Government House, Stirling Gardens, and the Old Court House Law Museum. That evening, take in the colours of sunset over the city skyline from Kings Park before indulging in fresh local produce and award winning Western Australian wines for dinner at Fraser’s Restaurant in Kings Park overlooking the lights of the city of Perth.
        <p><strong>Day 2</strong>: Thrill seekers can start the day with a Swan Jet Adventures high speed jet-boat ride on the Swan River - or if you’d like to take it easier, set sail from the Royal Perth Yacht Club and race against the clock with your team.</p>
        <p>Recharge over lunch with a gourmet picnic at the Quarry Amphitheatre, just 10 minutes from Perth’s city centre and renowned for its ambience and natural bushland location. The limestone walls and open views east to the city skyline and Darling Ranges add to its outstanding appeal.</p>
        <p>Pull on your gardening gloves for ‘green’ teambuilding at the Perth Cultural Centre’s Urban Orchard. Discover the magical views across Perth’s Indian Ocean coastline along the Cottesloe Beach scenic drive. Watch the sunset over a menu of Western Australia’s finest seafood.</p>
        <p><strong>Day 3</strong>: Journey to the Swan Valley, Western Australia’s oldest wine growing region and just 30 minutes from the centre of Perth. Enjoy samples of premium wines and produce from the local chocolate company, nougat factory and micro breweries.</p>
        <p>Take a tour through the working winery and barrel rooms of Sandalford Wines and test your team at blending their own red wine under the guidance of expert winemakers.</p>
        <p>Following lunch at the winery, meet the koalas at Caversham Wildlife Park along with other Australian wildlife, including the cassowary, dingo and flying fox.</p>
        <p><strong>Day 4</strong>: Give yourself time to give yourself time to relax, refresh and indulge over a leisurely breakfast. Shop at Perth’s finest boutiques, from King Street to Wolfe Lane, and be sure to pass by one of Perth’s new laneway bars for a light tapas lunch and glass of wine or freshly brewed coffee. Take a stroll along the Swan River before flying home.</p>]]></txt_HTML> 
</BEGenericHeaderAndConentBody>
    </con_content>
</BELayoutT8>
    </conMainContent>
    <lstNavigation>
    </lstNavigation>
</BEBaseFoundation>