<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<BEBaseFoundation pageID="20749" isTemplate="1">
    <breadcrumb>
        <element level="1">
            <headline><![CDATA[Homepage ]]></headline>
            <href><![CDATA[/index.xml]]></href>
        </element>
<element level="2">
            <headline><![CDATA[Business Events]]></headline>
            <href><![CDATA[/21974.ignore]]></href>
        </element>
<element level="4">
            <headline><![CDATA[Where to go]]></headline>
            <href><![CDATA[/businessevents/where-to-go.xml]]></href>
        </element>
<element level="5">
            <headline><![CDATA[Perth]]></headline>
            <href><![CDATA[/businessevents/where-to-go/perth.xml]]></href>
        </element>
<element level="6">
            <headline><![CDATA[Itineraries]]></headline>
            <href><![CDATA[/businessevents/where-to-go/perth/itineraries.xml]]></href>
        </element>
<element level="7">
            <headline><![CDATA[Wineries, Old Growth Forests and Coast ]]></headline>
            <href><![CDATA[/businessevents/where-to-go/perth/wineries-old-growth-forests-and-coast.xml]]></href>
        </element>

    </breadcrumb>
    <hdlPageTitle><![CDATA[Wineries, Old Growth Forests and Coast ]]></hdlPageTitle>
    <img_background><![CDATA[]]></img_background>
    <opt_HideInBreadcrumbs><![CDATA[Show]]></opt_HideInBreadcrumbs>
    <opt_not_in_sitemap><![CDATA[No]]></opt_not_in_sitemap>
    <opt_show_in_navigation><![CDATA[Show]]></opt_show_in_navigation>
    <stf_MetaKeywords><![CDATA[]]></stf_MetaKeywords>
    <stf_meta_keywords><![CDATA[]]></stf_meta_keywords>
    <stf_meta_description><![CDATA[]]></stf_meta_description>
    <stf_NavSubHeader><![CDATA[]]></stf_NavSubHeader>
    <stf_NavTitle><![CDATA[Wineries, Old Growth Forests and Coast ]]></stf_NavTitle>
    <stf_PageTitle><![CDATA[Wineries, Old Growth Forests and Coast ]]></stf_PageTitle>
    <conMainContent>
        <BELayoutT8 isTemplate="1">
    <hdl_headline><![CDATA[Layout - T8 2665]]></hdl_headline>
    <stf_Title><![CDATA[Wineries, Old Growth Forests and Coast ]]></stf_Title> 
    <opt_display_content_full_width><![CDATA[]]></opt_display_content_full_width>
    <con_sidebar>
        
    </con_sidebar> 
    <con_content>
        <BEGenericHeaderAndConentBody isTemplate="1">
    <hdl_headline><![CDATA[Generic - Header and Content Body 2666]]></hdl_headline>
    <img_DateIcon><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/business-events/iconStar.png" width="18" height="15">]]></img_DateIcon> 
    <img_DestinationIcon><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/business-events/iconWorld.png" width="18" height="15">]]></img_DestinationIcon>
    <img_EventTypeIcon><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/business-events/iconStar.png" width="18" height="15">]]></img_EventTypeIcon> 
    <img_DurationIcon><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/business-events/iconPax.png" width="18" height="15">]]></img_DurationIcon> 
    <opt_CaseStudy><![CDATA[0]]></opt_CaseStudy> 
    <stf_author><![CDATA[]]></stf_author>
    <stf_DateText><![CDATA[]]></stf_DateText>
    <stf_DelegatesText><![CDATA[]]></stf_DelegatesText>
    <stf_DestinationText><![CDATA[]]></stf_DestinationText>
    <stf_EventTypeText><![CDATA[]]></stf_EventTypeText>
    <stf_Header><![CDATA[]]></stf_Header>
    <stf_quote><![CDATA[]]></stf_quote>
    <stf_Title><![CDATA[]]></stf_Title>
    <txt_HTML><![CDATA[Voted as one of Lonely Planet’s top 10 must visit holiday destinations for 2010, Australia’s South West will surprise and delight the most discerning business traveller, with its boutique wineries, majestic old growth forests and stretches of unspoilt coastline. The region can easily accommodate small corporate retreats or larger conferences, events and incentive groups of up to 500 delegates.
        <p><strong>Day 1</strong>: The warm Mediterranean climate and fertile soils of the South West Region create the perfect environment to produce Cabernet, Merlot, Shiraz, Chardonnay, Semillon and Sauvignon Blanc wines. Sample some of the region’s impressive wines, then follow with a wine master class or group blending activity to produce your own wine with the winemaker at Vasse Felix, the region's oldest vineyard.</p>
        <p>For an exclusive activity, join the Executive Chef at Cape Lodge for a gourmet cooking master class and lunch to follow. Take a relaxing afternoon tour through the region before dinner at Quay West Resort Bunker Bay’s ‘Other Side of the Moon’ Restaurant, which enjoys spectacular ocean views. <br />
        <br />
        <strong>Day 2</strong>: Start the morning with an invigorating walk down the Cape to Cape track. Take in the spectacular coastal scenery and perhaps a swim in the Indian Ocean. For a real team building challenge, abseil 40 metres down into Brides Cave, only accessible by rope, and into the ‘Great Hall’. Enjoy the view of incredibly ancient, fragile straw formations and the pure white decorations.</p>
        <p>Or if it’s motorsport that gets you going, send the team out to try rally driving. The winter months offer the challenge of all the mud, crud and sludge your car can handle on a tailored rally driver’s course through the same area undertaken by the Rally Australia Drivers.</p>
        <p>After a gourmet picnic lunch on the beach, spend an afternoon of aquatic adventures. From the beginner to the more experienced surfer, everyone can enjoy the ultimate surfing experience in Australia’s South West. For a great team building activity, why not learn to surf?</p>
        <p>The waters of the Indian Ocean and the cooler depths of the Southern Ocean also offer spectacular snorkelling and diving. A guided snorkelling tour is a great way to experience the jewels of the sea. Or you can combine soft adventure including canoeing and caving followed by local bushtucker in an organised group tour.</p>
        <p>To top off an action-packed day, head to the Duckstein Brewery and Saracen Estate for a hearty meal and locally brewed beer.</p>
        <p><strong>Day 3</strong>: It’s time to relax. Visit one of the many local day spas for a relaxing massage or beauty treatment. Perhaps a round of golf is more your style? Try the greens at Dunsborough Lakes Golf course.</p>
        <p>Take a scenic drive further south to visit the largest producer of fresh truffles in the southern hemisphere. The Wine &amp; Truffle Co is one of the few truffi&egrave;res in the world where you can participate in the excitement of a guided truffle hunt. Discover how to locate the rare and wondrous black truffle, which is often referred to as ‘black gold’ or ‘black diamond’.</p>
        <p>Savour lunch in the gourmet Truffle Caf&eacute; before a scenic coach trip back up to Perth.</p>]]></txt_HTML> 
</BEGenericHeaderAndConentBody>
    </con_content>
</BELayoutT8>
    </conMainContent>
    <lstNavigation>
    </lstNavigation>
</BEBaseFoundation>