<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<ConsumerBaseFoundation pageID="7189" isTemplate="1">
	<breadcrumb>
		<element level="1">
			<headline><![CDATA[Homepage ]]></headline>
			<href><![CDATA[/index.xml]]></href>
		</element>
		<element level="2">
			<headline><![CDATA[About]]></headline>
			<href><![CDATA[/about.xml]]></href>
		</element>
		<element level="4">
			<headline><![CDATA[Australia's Beaches]]></headline>
			<href><![CDATA[/about/australias-landscapes/australian-beaches.xml]]></href>
		</element>

	</breadcrumb>
	<img_background><![CDATA[/contentimages/about-australias-landscapes-coastal-australian-beaches.jpg]]></img_background>
	<hdl_Title><![CDATA[Australia's Beaches]]></hdl_Title>
	<img_Banner><![CDATA[]]>
	</img_Banner>
	<img_SearchThumbnail><![CDATA[/thumbnails/about-australias-landscapes-coastal-australian-beaches-search.jpg]]></img_SearchThumbnail>
	<img_Thumbnail><![CDATA[/contentimages/about-australias-landscapes-coastal-australian-beaches-th.jpg]]></img_Thumbnail>
	<opt_HideInBreadcrumbs><![CDATA[Show]]></opt_HideInBreadcrumbs>
	<opt_HidePage><![CDATA[no]]></opt_HidePage>
	<opt_hideTitle><![CDATA[0]]></opt_hideTitle>
	<opt_hide_in_sitemap><![CDATA[no]]></opt_hide_in_sitemap>
	<opt_IncludeVideo><![CDATA[0]]></opt_IncludeVideo>
	<opt_isHubPage><![CDATA[0]]></opt_isHubPage>
	<opt_isNewWindow><![CDATA[_self]]></opt_isNewWindow>
	<opt_PageLayout><![CDATA[]]>
	</opt_PageLayout>
	<opt_PartnerLead><![CDATA[no]]></opt_PartnerLead>
	<stf_description><![CDATA[With 50,000 kilometres of coastline, Australia offers everything from iconic surf beaches and palm-topped islands to secret coves and sheltered bays. ]]></stf_description>
	<stf_ExcludedCountries><![CDATA[]]>
	</stf_ExcludedCountries>
	<stf_hideInXmlSitemap><![CDATA[]]>
	</stf_hideInXmlSitemap>
	<stf_ImageLocation><![CDATA[Bargara Beach, Bundaberg, QLD. &copy; Tourism Queensland]]></stf_ImageLocation>
	<stf_intro_title><![CDATA[]]>
	</stf_intro_title>
	<stf_IsExternalSiteArticle><![CDATA[]]>
	</stf_IsExternalSiteArticle>
	<stf_IsMobile><![CDATA[n]]></stf_IsMobile>
	<stf_keywords><![CDATA[Australia's beaches, Australian beaches, Beaches Australia, Beach holiday Australia, Australia's landscapes]]></stf_keywords>
	<stf_LinkLearnMore><![CDATA[Learn More]]></stf_LinkLearnMore>
	<stf_NavigationTagLine><![CDATA[]]>
	</stf_NavigationTagLine>
	<stf_PageHeading><![CDATA[]]>
	</stf_PageHeading>
	<stf_TargetedCountries><![CDATA[]]>
	</stf_TargetedCountries>
	<stf_TrackingTitle><![CDATA[]]>
	</stf_TrackingTitle>
	<TA_Title><![CDATA[Australia's Beaches]]></TA_Title>
	<txt_Intro>
        <![CDATA[]]>
	</txt_Intro>
	<txt_MobileContentOnly>
        <![CDATA[]]>
	</txt_MobileContentOnly>
	<txt_SpotlightTag>
        <![CDATA[]]>
	</txt_SpotlightTag>
	<txt_Teaser>
        <![CDATA[With 50,000 kilometres of coastline, Australia offers everything from iconic surf beaches and palm-topped islands to secret coves and sheltered bays. ]]>
	</txt_Teaser>
	<con_Body>
		<SubPageLayout isTemplate="1">
			<con_Banner>

			</con_Banner>
			<con_RHSModules>
				<ExperienceLocationMap isTemplate="1">
					<!-- no user content -->
				</ExperienceLocationMap>
			</con_RHSModules>
			<con_Video>

			</con_Video>
			<con_Body>
				<TopCategoryHighlights isTemplate="1">
					<stf_Heading><![CDATA[Australia's Beaches]]></stf_Heading>
					<stf_InformationTitle><![CDATA[]]>
					</stf_InformationTitle>
					<txt_Information><![CDATA[Craving an Australian beach holiday?  <P>Learn about some of our iconic beach destinations. There’s Victoria’s Great Ocean Road, which links famous surf beaches, tranquil seaside towns, whale lookouts and the Twelve Apostles. In Tasmania’s Freycinet National Park, you can swim, fish and kayak against a backdrop of dusky pink mountains, blue-green sea and white sand.</P> <P>Australia has many spectacular coastal journeys. Sail through the Whitsundays or hike the pristine coastline of Victoria’s Wilsons Promontory. Drive from Sydney to Cairns along the breathtaking Pacific Coast Touring Route. In Western Australia, the Indian Ocean Drive links white beaches, coral reefs, fishing towns and national parks. The South West Beaches and Goldfields Drive meanders through Margaret River to the beach-blessed southern coast. </P> <P>For more beach holiday ideas, read about Sydney’s sparkling beaches and the cliff-hugging Bondi to Bronte coastal walk. We can guide you on Australia’s surf beaches to help you plan your holiday to surf Australia!&nbsp;&nbsp; <BR></P> ]]></txt_Information>
					<con_CenterContent>
						<CenterContent isTemplate="1">
							<hdl_Title><![CDATA[Australia's Coast]]></hdl_Title>
							<img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/11.5.1_australias_beaches_highlight1.jpg" alt="Australia's Coast">]]></img_MainImage>
							<stf_Caption><![CDATA[Australia's Coast]]></stf_Caption>
							<anc_link><![CDATA[/about/australias-landscapes/coastal.xml]]></anc_link>
							<txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[
        Find out more about Australia’s 50,000 kilometres of spellbinding coastline.<br />
        Wherever you find them, our white, sandy beaches are just as you imagine - uncrowded, unspoilt and utterly enticing. You can marvel at World Heritage-listed wonders, chill out at a beach retreat or just enjoy fish and chips on the shore. However you experience our coastline, the crashing waves and gentle sea breeze are all part of a lifestyle that you won’t want to leave behind.
    ]]>
							</txt_Information>
						</CenterContent>
						<CenterContent isTemplate="1">
							<hdl_Title><![CDATA[Great Ocean Road, Victoria]]></hdl_Title>
							<img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/11.5.1_australias_beaches_highlight4.jpg" alt="Great Ocean Road, VIC">]]></img_MainImage>
							<stf_Caption><![CDATA[Great Ocean Road, VIC]]></stf_Caption>
							<anc_link><![CDATA[/explore/icons/great-ocean-road.xml]]></anc_link>
							<txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[
        Take a ride through nature on the spectacular <a href="/explore/icons/great-ocean-road.xml" target="_self">Great Ocean Road</a>, which winds alongside the wild and windswept Southern Ocean from Geelong to Portland. This diverse and dramatic region takes in surf beaches, historic ports, whale lookouts, breathtaking mountain ranges, rainforests and national parks. See monster waves at <a href="/explore/states/vic/vic-torquay.xml" target="_self">Bells Beach</a> and laze on the golden sands of Lorne. Visit an important Aboriginal site near Tower Hill or spot shipwrecks near the charming fishing village of Port Fairy. Of course, you can’t miss the <a href="/explore/states/vic/vic-12-apostles.xml" target="_self">Twelve Apostles</a> - craggy limestone stacks rising majestically from the Southern Ocean.
    ]]>
							</txt_Information>
						</CenterContent>
						<CenterContent isTemplate="1">
							<hdl_Title><![CDATA[Pacific Coast Touring Route, Queensland]]></hdl_Title>
							<img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/11.5.1_australias_beaches_highlight5.jpg" alt="Fraser Island, QLD">]]></img_MainImage>
							<stf_Caption><![CDATA[Fraser Island, QLD]]></stf_Caption>
							<anc_link><![CDATA[/explore/itineraries/qld-pacific-coast.xml]]></anc_link>
							<txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[
        Capture some of Queensland’s biggest coastal attractions– from the World Heritage-listed Great Barrier Reef to the pristine islands and rainforest national parks. Four wheel drive <a href="/explore/icons/fraser-island.xml" target="_self">Fraser Island</a>, the world’s largest sand island and see manta rays and turtles at Mon Repos, near <a href="/explore/cities/regional-cities/bundaberg-natural-attraction.xml" target="_self">Bundaberg</a>. Stay in Rockhampton and visit Great Keppel Island and the Capricorn Caves. Snorkel or dive reefs and shipwrecks near Mackay and go sailing in the postcard-perfect <a href="/explore/icons/great-barrier-reef/whitsundays-islands.xml" target="_self">Whitsundays</a>. Walk the white sand of <a href="/explore/icons/great-barrier-reef/magnetic-island.xml" target="_self">Magnetic Island</a>, near <a href="/explore/states/qld/townsville.xml" target="_self">Townsville</a> and further north visit <a href="/explore/itineraries/hinchinbrook-island.xml" target="_self">Hinchinbrook</a>, Australia’s largest island national park. The vivid colours, smells and sounds of this splendid coastline will stay with you long after your journey ends in <a href="/explore/cities/cairns.xml" target="_self">Cairns</a>, at the gateway to Queensland’s tropical north.
    ]]>
							</txt_Information>
						</CenterContent>
						<CenterContent isTemplate="1">
							<hdl_Title><![CDATA[Pacific Coast Touring Route, New South Wales]]></hdl_Title>
							<img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/11.5.1_australias_beaches_highlight6.jpg" alt="Port Stephens, NSW">]]></img_MainImage>
							<stf_Caption><![CDATA[Port Stephens, NSW]]></stf_Caption>
							<anc_link><![CDATA[/explore/itineraries/nsw-pacific-coast-touring-route.xml]]></anc_link>
							<txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[
        Explore the sparkling beaches and lush hinterland of the Central Coast, the wineries of the <a href="/explore/states/nsw/hunter-valley.xml" target="_self">Hunter Valley</a> and the picturesque inlets of Port Stephens. Work on your swing in a rainforest <a href="/explore/things-to-do/great-golf-courses.xml" target="_self">golf course</a> on the Coffs Coast and your aura on the beach in <a href="/judy-baileys-australia-byron-bay.xml" target="_self">Byron Bay</a>. Dive with brightly coloured fish in Solitary Islands Marine Park or into the bright lights of the Gold Coast. This scenic drive takes you from Sydney to Brisbane, offering sweeping beaches, sleepy villages, mossy rainforests, adventure and relaxation along the way.
    ]]>
							</txt_Information>
						</CenterContent>
						<CenterContent isTemplate="1">
							<hdl_Title><![CDATA[Great Southern Touring Route, Victoria]]></hdl_Title>
							<img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/11.5.1_australias_beaches_highlight7.jpg" alt="Bells Beach, VIC">]]></img_MainImage>
							<stf_Caption><![CDATA[Bells Beach, VIC]]></stf_Caption>
							<anc_link><![CDATA[/explore/itineraries/vic-great-southern-touring-route.xml]]></anc_link>
							<txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[
        The Great Southern Touring Route turns the romance of the road trip into a grand love affair. Drive along the <a href="/explore/icons/great-ocean-road.xml" target="_self">Great Ocean Road</a> past the iconic surf spots of Torquay and <a href="/explore/states/vic/vic-torquay.xml" target="_self">Bells Beach</a>, then onto the holiday haven of Lorne and the magnificent Twelve Apostles. Walk through waterfalls and lush forest in Otway National Park and watch whales from the historic town of Warrnambool. Stretch out your journey with a stay in any of the many scenic seaside towns, from Apollo Bay to Port Fairy. Away from the wild and windswept Southern Ocean, you can explore Aboriginal history in the <a href="/explore/states/vic/vic-grampians.xml" target="_self">Grampians</a> and gold rush heritage in Ballarat.
    ]]>
							</txt_Information>
						</CenterContent>
						<CenterContent isTemplate="1">
							<hdl_Title><![CDATA[South-West, Beaches and Goldfields, Western Australia]]></hdl_Title>
							<img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/11.5.1_australias_beaches_highlight8.jpg" alt="Margaret River, WA">]]></img_MainImage>
							<stf_Caption><![CDATA[Margaret River, WA]]></stf_Caption>
							<anc_link><![CDATA[/explore/itineraries/wa-south-west-beaches-goldfields.xml]]></anc_link>
							<txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[
        Discover the diverse and theatrical landscapes of Australia’s south-west corner. Drive from <a href="/explore/cities/perth.xml" target="_self">Perth</a> through the buzzing historic port of <a href="/explore/cities/perth/wa-fremantle.xml" target="_self">Fremantle</a> and swim with dolphins in Mandurah and Bunbury. Explore wineries, surf beaches, ancient limestone caves and towering karri forests in the <a href="/judy-baileys-australia-margaret-river.xml" target="_self">Margaret River</a> region. Walk through a canopy of sky-scraping trees in the <a href="/explore/states/wa/wa-valley-of-the-giants-story.xml" target="_self">Valley of the Giants</a>, near Walpole. Swim and surf from Esperance’s clean, empty white beaches and cruise to the pristine islands of the Recherche Archipelago. Soak up gold fever in Kalgoorlie-Boulder and trace the path of pioneers on <a href="/explore/states/wa/wa-kalgoorlie.xml" target="_self">historic gold trails</a>. Watch golden sand morph to green valley as you drive back into Perth.
    ]]>
							</txt_Information>
						</CenterContent>
						<CenterContent isTemplate="1">
							<hdl_Title><![CDATA[Broome, Western Australia]]></hdl_Title>
							<img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/destinations_cities_broome_hl.jpg" alt="Cable Beach, WA">]]></img_MainImage>
							<stf_Caption><![CDATA[Cable Beach, WA]]></stf_Caption>
							<anc_link><![CDATA[/explore/cities/broome.xml]]></anc_link>
							<txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[
        Meet camels and characters in Broome, an exotic pearling town that sits at the gateway to <a href="/nationallandscapes/the-kimberley.xml" target="_self">the Kimberley</a>. Buy pearls and soak up the melting pot of nationalities in Chinatown, once the bustling hub of billiard saloons and opium dens. Ride a camel along the white sand of <a href="/explore/cities/broome/wa-cable-beach.xml" target="_self">Cable Beach</a>, the place to watch a blazing sun sink into the Indian Ocean. Check out dinosaur footprints preserved in rock and birdwatch from Roebuck Bay. Between March and October, you can catch the romantic magic of ‘Staircase to the Moon’, a silvery illusion created by the reflection of a rising moon.
    ]]>
							</txt_Information>
						</CenterContent>
						<CenterContent isTemplate="1">
							<hdl_Title><![CDATA[Bells Beach, Victoria]]></hdl_Title>
							<img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/11.5.1_australias_beaches_highlight3.jpg" alt="Bells Beach, VIC">]]></img_MainImage>
							<stf_Caption><![CDATA[Bells Beach, VIC]]></stf_Caption>
							<anc_link><![CDATA[/explore/states/vic/vic-torquay.xml]]></anc_link>
							<txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[
        Soak up surf culture, sunshine and holiday fun on the surf beaches around Torquay. You can have all kinds of seaside sun in Torquay, but this picturesque holiday town is most famous for the <a href="/explore/things-to-do/australian-adventure/nat-surfing.xml" target="_self">surf beaches</a> that surround it. Sitting south-west of <a href="/explore/cities/melbourne.xml" target="_self">Melbourne</a> at the gateway to the Great Ocean Road, Torquay is fringed by some fantastic breaks with fairytale names.
    ]]>
							</txt_Information>
						</CenterContent>
						<CenterContent isTemplate="1">
							<hdl_Title><![CDATA[Sydney’s Beaches Beckon]]></hdl_Title>
							<img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/11.5.1_australias_beaches_highlight2.jpg" alt="Bondi Beach, NSW">]]></img_MainImage>
							<stf_Caption><![CDATA[Bondi Beach, NSW]]></stf_Caption>
							<anc_link><![CDATA[/explore/cities/sydney/nsw-sydney-beaches.xml]]></anc_link>
							<txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[
        Discover some of <a href="/explore/cities/sydney.xml" target="_self">Sydney</a>’s 70 sparkling beaches, from secluded bays to world-famous strips of sand. Sydney’s beaches will be beckoning before you even land in Botany. You might see them flying in – a long, golden chain split across both sides of the harbour and fringed by green bush and sea. Or the welcome video on the plane might start famous images of <a href="/explore/cities/sydney/nsw-bondi-beach.xml" target="_self">Bondi Beach</a> repeating in your head. If you’re an avid surfer, sun-worshipper or just love the sea, you’ll be itching to get onto the waves, smelling the salt air or nestled nicely on the sand.
    ]]>
							</txt_Information>
						</CenterContent>
						<CenterContent isTemplate="1">
							<hdl_Title><![CDATA[Bondi to Bronte, Sydney, NSW]]></hdl_Title>
							<img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/explore-cities-sydney-bondi-to-bronte-hl.jpg" alt="Bronte Beach, NSW">]]></img_MainImage>
							<stf_Caption><![CDATA[Bronte Beach, NSW]]></stf_Caption>
							<anc_link><![CDATA[/explore/cities/sydney/nsw-bondi-bronte.xml]]></anc_link>
							<txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[
        Sydney in summertime is all about its coastline, and few stretches are as iconic as the sea-sculpted section from <a href="/explore/cities/sydney/nsw-bondi-beach.xml" target="_self">Bondi</a> to Bronte. Learn to surf at Bondi, join the beautiful people in Tamarama and swim in Bronte’s family-friendly rock pool.  See all three beaches on the Bondi to Bronte walk - a short, spectacular coastal trail along epic sandstone cliffs.
    ]]>
							</txt_Information>
						</CenterContent>
					</con_CenterContent>
				</TopCategoryHighlights>
			</con_Body>
		</SubPageLayout>
	</con_Body>
	<lst_Subpages>
	</lst_Subpages>
</ConsumerBaseFoundation>