<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<BEBaseFoundation pageID="23495" isTemplate="1">
    <breadcrumb>
        <element level="1">
            <headline><![CDATA[Homepage ]]></headline>
            <href><![CDATA[/index.xml]]></href>
        </element>
<element level="2">
            <headline><![CDATA[Business Events]]></headline>
            <href><![CDATA[/21974.ignore]]></href>
        </element>
<element level="4">
            <headline><![CDATA[Associations]]></headline>
            <href><![CDATA[/businessevents/associations.xml]]></href>
        </element>
<element level="5">
            <headline><![CDATA[Association Case Studies]]></headline>
            <href><![CDATA[/businessevents/associations/case-studies.xml]]></href>
        </element>
<element level="6">
            <headline><![CDATA[Case study - Melbourne choice for science and medical ]]></headline>
            <href><![CDATA[/businessevents/associations/case-study-melbourne-choice-for-science-and-medical.xml]]></href>
        </element>

    </breadcrumb>
    <hdlPageTitle><![CDATA[Case study - Melbourne choice for science and medical ]]></hdlPageTitle>
    <img_background><![CDATA[]]></img_background>
    <opt_HideInBreadcrumbs><![CDATA[Show]]></opt_HideInBreadcrumbs>
    <opt_not_in_sitemap><![CDATA[No]]></opt_not_in_sitemap>
    <opt_show_in_navigation><![CDATA[Show]]></opt_show_in_navigation>
    <stf_MetaKeywords><![CDATA[]]></stf_MetaKeywords>
    <stf_meta_keywords><![CDATA[]]></stf_meta_keywords>
    <stf_meta_description><![CDATA[]]></stf_meta_description>
    <stf_NavSubHeader><![CDATA[]]></stf_NavSubHeader>
    <stf_NavTitle><![CDATA[Melbourne a destination of choice]]></stf_NavTitle>
    <stf_PageTitle><![CDATA[Melbourne a destination of choice for scientific and medical association events]]></stf_PageTitle>
    <conMainContent>
        <BELayoutT8 isTemplate="1">
    <hdl_headline><![CDATA[BE - Layout - T8 23502]]></hdl_headline>
    <stf_Title><![CDATA[Melbourne - where great minds meet]]></stf_Title> 
    <opt_display_content_full_width><![CDATA[]]></opt_display_content_full_width>
    <con_sidebar>
        <BENavPanelPageLinks isTemplate="1">
    <anc_links>
        <anc_link>
            <url><![CDATA[/businessevents/associations/learn-about-australia.xml]]></url>
            <stf_NavTitle><![CDATA[Learn about Australia]]></stf_NavTitle> 
            <stf_NavSubHeader><![CDATA[]]></stf_NavSubHeader>
        </anc_link>
        <anc_link>
            <url><![CDATA[/businessevents/associations/case-studies.xml]]></url>
            <stf_NavTitle><![CDATA[Case Studies]]></stf_NavTitle> 
            <stf_NavSubHeader><![CDATA[]]></stf_NavSubHeader>
        </anc_link>
        <anc_link>
            <url><![CDATA[/businessevents/associations/here-to-help.xml]]></url>
            <stf_NavTitle><![CDATA[Here to help]]></stf_NavTitle> 
            <stf_NavSubHeader><![CDATA[]]></stf_NavSubHeader>
        </anc_link>
        <anc_link>
            <url><![CDATA[/businessevents/associations/venues.xml]]></url>
            <stf_NavTitle><![CDATA[Association venues]]></stf_NavTitle> 
            <stf_NavSubHeader><![CDATA[]]></stf_NavSubHeader>
        </anc_link>
    </anc_links>
</BENavPanelPageLinks>
    </con_sidebar> 
    <con_content>
        <BEGenericHeaderAndConentBody isTemplate="1">
    <hdl_headline><![CDATA[Generic - Header and Content Body 23497]]></hdl_headline>
    <img_DateIcon><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/business-events/iconStar.png" width="18" height="15">]]></img_DateIcon> 
    <img_DestinationIcon><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/business-events/iconWorld.png" width="18" height="15">]]></img_DestinationIcon>
    <img_EventTypeIcon><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/business-events/iconStar.png" width="18" height="15">]]></img_EventTypeIcon> 
    <img_DurationIcon><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/business-events/iconPax.png" width="18" height="15">]]></img_DurationIcon> 
    <opt_CaseStudy><![CDATA[0]]></opt_CaseStudy> 
    <stf_author><![CDATA[]]></stf_author>
    <stf_DateText><![CDATA[]]></stf_DateText>
    <stf_DelegatesText><![CDATA[]]></stf_DelegatesText>
    <stf_DestinationText><![CDATA[]]></stf_DestinationText>
    <stf_EventTypeText><![CDATA[]]></stf_EventTypeText>
    <stf_Header><![CDATA[]]></stf_Header>
    <stf_quote><![CDATA[]]></stf_quote>
    <stf_Title><![CDATA[]]></stf_Title>
    <txt_HTML><![CDATA[We take a closer look at the Australian city of Melbourne to find out why it is becoming the destination of choice for scientific and medical association events.<BR><BR>Widely regarded as Australia’s capital of culture, Melbourne is a vibrant city with surprises around every corner. With an abundance of hidden laneways and rooftop venues to explore, it is renowned for its mix of cutting edge urban cool where music, fashion, art and a sophisticated dining scene come together to form an eclectic blend of entertainment options.<BR><BR>Consistently ranked as one of the most livable cities in the world, as evidenced by taking the top spot in the Economist Intelligence Unit’s livability survey for the last two years, Melbourne offers a wide range of leisure options for delegates.<BR><BR>The city’s love affair with all things culinary and cultural is matched only by its voracious appetite for sports of all kinds. Events such as the international test series cricket at the Melbourne Cricket Ground, the Australian Open Tennis Championships and the Australian Formula 1 Grand Prix make the city an ideal destination for sports enthusiasts.<BR><BR>However, there is much more to the city than leisure and lifestyle. Melbourne effortlessly combines work and play, and is widely regarded as a centre of excellence for knowledge, research and innovation in the medical, science, business and financial industries. <BR><BR>These attributes, as well as Melbourne’s state-of-the-art infrastructure and accessibility, have seen the city acclaimed as one of the world’s premier conference destinations.<BR><BR>At the heart of Melbourne’s world-class business events infrastructure is the Melbourne Convention and Exhibition Centre (MCEC), a state-of-the-art centre offering the most flexible, integrated and comprehensive meeting facilities in the Southern Hemisphere. The world’s first ‘Six Star Green Star’ environmentally-rated convention centre, a short drive from Melbourne Airport, boasts the latest technology, award-winning food and wine and has over 5,400 hotel rooms within walking distance, with a further 20,000 rooms located within the city.<BR><BR>The calibre of major international conferences being held at the MCEC is outstanding, with the city attracting some of the world’s largest and most prestigious medical and science events. Major association events such as the International Congress of Pediatrics 2013, the 22nd World Diabetes Congress 2013, the Pharmaceutical Sciences World Congress 2014 and the International AIDS Conference 2014 will bring more than 30,000 delegates in to the city who are expected to contribute in excess of A$1 billion to the Victorian economy.<BR><BR>Melbourne’s status as a world class destination for association events is demonstrated by the International Council of Nurses Federation (ICN) choosing the city as the destination for their 25th Quadrennial Congress. This high profile event provides a global platform for the dissemination of nursing knowledge and leadership across specialties, cultures and countries. Simultaneously conducted in English, French and Spanish, the event is anticipated to attract in excess of 5,000 delegates who will converge on the MCEC to listen to prominent guest speakers and debate the most pressing and timely topics of interest in nursing. <BR><BR>A critical component in securing events of this stature is Melbourne’s standing as a world-leader in science and medicine, which has yielded four Nobel Prize winners in medicine and physiology. Home to 263 biotechnology companies, 13 major medical research institutes and seven teaching hospitals, the city has a robust biotechnology sector that attracts eminent researchers from around the world. <BR><BR>Melbourne is globally renowned for its expertise in stem cell, infectious diseases, cancer research, neuroscience, clinical trials and agricultural biotechnology, making it a perfect destination for medical and scientific association events. The high concentration of major research institutions ensures that scientific conferences and medical conventions attract leaders in their respective fields. <BR><BR>Combine the world’s leading minds with some of Australia’s most desirable urban and regional experiences and Melbourne gives you the perfect choice to inspire delegates at your next association event.]]></txt_HTML> 
</BEGenericHeaderAndConentBody>
    </con_content>
</BELayoutT8>
    </conMainContent>
    <lstNavigation>
    </lstNavigation>
</BEBaseFoundation>