<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<ConsumerBaseFoundation pageID="24751"
	isTemplate="1">
	<breadcrumb>
		<element level="1">
			<headline><![CDATA[Homepage ]]></headline>
			<href><![CDATA[/index.xml]]></href>
		</element>
		<element level="2">
			<headline><![CDATA[Tools and Campaigns]]></headline>
			<href><![CDATA[/tools-campaigns.xml]]></href>
		</element>
		<element level="4">
			<headline><![CDATA[AU]]></headline>
			<href><![CDATA[/12026.ignore]]></href>
		</element>
		<element level="5">
			<headline><![CDATA[The Australian Tourism Awards 2013]]></headline>
			<href><![CDATA[/nta13-au.xml]]></href>
		</element>

	</breadcrumb>
	<img_background><![CDATA[/contentimages/Campaigns/campaigns-au-nta-bg.jpg]]></img_background>
	<hdl_Title><![CDATA[The Australian Tourism Awards 2013]]></hdl_Title>
	<img_Banner><![CDATA[]]>
	</img_Banner>
	<img_SearchThumbnail><![CDATA[/thumbnails/campaigns-au-nta-search.jpg]]></img_SearchThumbnail>
	<img_Thumbnail><![CDATA[/contentimages/Campaigns/campaigns-au-nta-th.jpg]]></img_Thumbnail>
	<opt_HideInBreadcrumbs><![CDATA[Show]]></opt_HideInBreadcrumbs>
	<opt_HidePage><![CDATA[no]]></opt_HidePage>
	<opt_hideTitle><![CDATA[0]]></opt_hideTitle>
	<opt_hide_in_sitemap><![CDATA[no]]></opt_hide_in_sitemap>
	<opt_IncludeVideo><![CDATA[0]]></opt_IncludeVideo>
	<opt_isHubPage><![CDATA[0]]></opt_isHubPage>
	<opt_isNewWindow><![CDATA[_self]]></opt_isNewWindow>
	<opt_PageLayout><![CDATA[]]>
	</opt_PageLayout>
	<opt_PartnerLead><![CDATA[no]]></opt_PartnerLead>
	<stf_description><![CDATA[The Australian Tourism Awards 2013]]></stf_description>
	<stf_ExcludedCountries><![CDATA[]]>
	</stf_ExcludedCountries>
	<stf_hideInXmlSitemap><![CDATA[]]>
	</stf_hideInXmlSitemap>
	<stf_ImageLocation><![CDATA[]]>
	</stf_ImageLocation>
	<stf_intro_title><![CDATA[]]>
	</stf_intro_title>
	<stf_IsExternalSiteArticle><![CDATA[]]>
	</stf_IsExternalSiteArticle>
	<stf_IsMobile><![CDATA[y]]></stf_IsMobile>
	<stf_keywords><![CDATA[The Australian Tourism Awards 2013]]></stf_keywords>
	<stf_LinkLearnMore><![CDATA[Learn More]]></stf_LinkLearnMore>
	<stf_NavigationTagLine><![CDATA[]]>
	</stf_NavigationTagLine>
	<stf_PageHeading><![CDATA[]]>
	</stf_PageHeading>
	<stf_TargetedCountries><![CDATA[]]>
	</stf_TargetedCountries>
	<stf_TrackingTitle><![CDATA[]]>
	</stf_TrackingTitle>
	<TA_Title><![CDATA[The Australian Tourism Awards 2013 - Tourism Australia]]></TA_Title>
	<txt_Intro>
        <![CDATA[]]>
	</txt_Intro>
	<txt_MobileContentOnly>
        <![CDATA[<!-- IMAGE GALLERY SNIPPET (UPDATED) -->
<div class="flexslider">
<ul class="slides">
    <li><img alt="" src="http://www.australia.com/campaigns/mobile/au/nta12/nta12-hero.jpg" />
    <div class="titleArea"><span class="title">The Australian Tourism Awards</span> <span class="subTitle">The Australian Tourism Awards are the tourism industry's peak Awards</span> </div>
    </li>
</ul>
</div>
<!-- END OF IMAGE GALLERY SNIPPET (UPDATED) --><!-- INTRO AREA (UNCHANGED) -->
<div class="introBox">
<div class="introTitle" data-title="ReadMoreIntro">The Australian Tourism Awards</div>
<div class="content-img"><img alt="The Australian Tourism Awards" src="http://www.australia.com/campaigns/mobile/au/nta12/campaigns-au-nta-logo.jpg" /></div>
<p>The Australian Tourism Awards are the tourism industry's peak Awards – recognising and promoting excellence in tourism. Whether it's exploring iconic Uluru-Kata Tjuta National Park, cruising with Bruny Island Cruises in Tasmania, kicking up your heels at the Tamworth Country Music Festival or cycling around Rottnest Island, the experiences below will inspire you to discover why there's nothing like Australia.</p>
</div>
<a href="javascript:void(0);" class="readMoreTrigger"><span id="lblReadMore">Read more</span> <span id="lblReadLess">Read less</span> </a>
<div class="clear"></div>
<!-- END OF INTRO AREA (UNCHANGED) --><!-- ACCORDIAN OFFERS AREA SNIPPET (UNCHANGED) -->
<div class="accordion" data-corners="false" data-collapsed="false" data-role="collapsible-set">
<div data-role="collapsible">
<h3>Uluru-Kata Tjuta National Park</h3>
<div>
<div class="content-img"><img alt="Uluru-Kata Tjuta National Park" src="http://www.australia.com/campaigns/mobile/au/nta12/nta-uluru-kata-tjuta-national-park-th1.jpg" /></div>
<p><em><strong>2012 Winner for Major Tourist Attractions</strong></em><br />
International and national tourists visiting Uluru-Kata Tjuta National Park experience one of Australia's most iconic World Heritage sites and an outstanding hallmark attraction. 300,000 tourists a year receive world class tourism experiences through the unique natural and cultural offerings at the park. Tourists are inspired by the visual immensity and powerful spirituality of Uluru and Kata Tjuta. This ancient land has been actively managed by generations of Anangu, the Aboriginal traditional owners, and continues to hold powerful cultural connections today. Anangu welcome visitors to their land to share their knowledge of Tjukurpa, ancestors and culture.</p>
<p><a href="http://www.environment.gov.au/parks/uluru/index.html" class="campaign-extlink" target="_blank" data-partnerid="moersmedia" data-ev="PartnerLead"><strong>Find Out More</strong></a></p>
</div>
</div>
<div data-role="collapsible">
<h3>Bruny Island Cruises</h3>
<div>
<div class="content-img"><img alt="Bruny Island Cruises" src="http://www.australia.com/campaigns/mobile/au/nta12/nta-bruny-island-cruises-th2.jpg" /></div>
<p><em><strong>2012 Winner for Tourist Attractions and 2012 Winner for Ecotourism</strong></em><br />
Since its inception in 1999, Bruny Island Cruises has become one of Tasmania's iconic attractions. Over 200,000 guests have joined the infectious, enthusiastic crew on the custom-built yellow boats for the 50km journey along Bruny Island's spectacular coastline, with its towering sea cliffs, deep sea caves and abundant wildlife. The business invests considerable resources into publicity and this has brought significant benefit to Bruny Island and surrounding regions through increased visitation, employment, local purchasing and community support. Bruny Island Cruises supports a range of conservation and humanitarian projects and it has won many state and national awards.</p>
<p><a href="http://www.brunycruises.com.au/" class="campaign-extlink" target="_blank" data-partnerid="moersmedia" data-ev="PartnerLead"><strong>Find Out More</strong></a></p>
</div>
</div>
<div data-role="collapsible">
<h3>2012 Tamworth Country Music Festival</h3>
<div>
<div class="content-img"><img alt="2012 Tamworth Country Music Festival" src="http://www.australia.com/campaigns/mobile/au/nta12/nta-tamworth-country-music-festival-th3.jpg" /></div>
<p><em><strong>2012 Winner for Major Festivals and Events</strong></em><br />
In 2012 we celebrated the 40th Tamworth Country Music Festival, an iconic annual event recognised as one of the top Ten Music Festivals in the world. The 2012 Tamworth Country Music Festival commenced on Friday 20 January and concluded on Sunday 29 January, with over 55,000 people travelling to Tamworth from all around Australia and the world to attend. Tamworth Regional Council has carriage of the event, however the Festival is a truly community-based, organic Festival. The 2012 TCMF was bigger and better than ever, with over 2,500 events and 4,000 different performances in 80 different venues.</p>
<p><a href="http://www.tcmf.com.au/" class="campaign-extlink" target="_blank" data-partnerid="moersmedia" data-ev="PartnerLead"><strong>Find Out More</strong></a></p>
</div>
</div>
<div data-role="collapsible">
<h3>Deni Ute Muster</h3>
<div>
<div class="content-img"><img alt="Deni Ute Muster" src="http://www.australia.com/campaigns/mobile/au/nta12/nta-deni-ute-festival-th4.jpg" /></div>
<p><em><strong>2012 Winner for Festivals and Events</strong></em><br />
The Deniliquin Ute Muster and Play on the Plains Festival is one of Australia's largest rural and Australian themed festivals. The idea for a festival celebrating the Australian icon of the Ute, and Australia's rural identity, was created in 1999 to encourage tourist visitation on the NSW Labour Day long weekend. In 2011, despite being severely rain affected, the Festival was hugely successful when it attracted almost 20,000 people to the two and a half-day event.</p>
<p><a href="http://www.deniutemuster.com.au/" class="campaign-extlink" target="_blank" data-partnerid="moersmedia" data-ev="PartnerLead"><strong>Find Out More</strong></a></p>
</div>
</div>
<div data-role="collapsible">
<h3>Venture North Australia</h3>
<div>
<div class="content-img"><img alt="Venture North Australia" src="http://www.australia.com/campaigns/mobile/au/nta12/nta-venture-north-th5.jpg" /></div>
<p><em><strong>2012 Winner for Heritage and Cultural Tourism</strong></em><br />
Venture North Australia specialises in high-quality, small group cultural and nature based 4WD tours of the Northern Territory. They hold a number of special entry permits which allows them unparalleled access into many restricted regions of the NT including Arnhem Land, the Cobourg Peninsula and even parts of Kakadu National Park. Tour guests are escorted by expert guides and learn not only about Indigenous culture but also the Macassan traders, early missionaries, buffalo shooters and the fascinating history of the British settlement, all of which have contributed to the NT's rich heritage.</p>
<p><a href="http://www.venturenorth.com.au/" class="campaign-extlink" target="_blank" data-partnerid="moersmedia" data-ev="PartnerLead"><strong>Find Out More</strong></a></p>
</div>
</div>
<div data-role="collapsible">
<h3>RT Tours</h3>
<div>
<div class="content-img"><img alt="RT Tours" src="http://www.australia.com/campaigns/mobile/au/nta12/nta-rt-tours-th6.jpg" /></div>
<p><em><strong>2012 Winner for Indigenous Tourism</strong></em><br />
The tour begins with welcoming people to country and starts at the old Arrernte meeting place, Mbantua (Alice Springs historical reserve). Here visitors learn about its Aboriginal and Australian history. In the park people get to see flora and fauna that are the bush foods that sustained a population for more than 50,000 years. Tours travel to Simpson's Gap along the majestic Western McDonnell Ranges, following the path of the sacred caterpillars. The product has been designed so visitors can enjoy and engage in food culture and country in a relaxing and non confronting way, leaving them with a truly memorable Central Australian experience.</p>
<p><a href="http://rttoursaustralia.com.au/" class="campaign-extlink" target="_blank" data-partnerid="moersmedia" data-ev="PartnerLead"><strong>Find Out More</strong></a></p>
</div>
</div>
<div data-role="collapsible">
<h3>Northern Territory Library</h3>
<div>
<div class="content-img"><img alt="Northern Territory Library" src="http://www.australia.com/campaigns/mobile/au/nta12/nta-northern-territory-library-th7.jpg" /></div>
<p><em><strong>2012 Winner for Specialised Tourism Services</strong></em><br />
The Northern Territory Library is located inside Parliament House in Darwin's State Square. The Library provides space for clients to seek information in relaxed and comfortable surroundings, seven days a week. NTL has been in operation for over 30 years. Visitors to the Northern Territory come to NTL to find information that adds value to their experience of the Territory. Access to information about the Northern Territory's history and culture gives tourists a greater sense of place, helping to enhance their visit. NTL inspires visitors to learn more about the NT by showcasing the Territory's people, history and culture.</p>
<p><a href="http://artsandmuseums.nt.gov.au/northern-territory-library" class="campaign-extlink" target="_blank" data-partnerid="moersmedia" data-ev="PartnerLead"><strong>Find Out More</strong></a></p>
</div>
</div>
<div data-role="collapsible">
<h3>Frankston Visitor Information Centre</h3>
<div>
<div class="content-img"><img alt="Frankston Visitor Information Centre" src="http://www.australia.com/campaigns/mobile/au/nta12/nta-frankston-visitor-information-th8.jpg" /></div>
<p><em><strong>2012 Winner for Visitor Information and Services</strong></em><br />
A finalist for the past four years in the Victorian Tourism Awards, the Frankston Visitor Information Centre is the jewel in the crown of the $25 million Frankston Waterfront precinct. With approximately 746,000 visitors to Frankston each year and a local population of 126,000, the FVIC services over 90,000 people annually either in person, email or phone and receives over 102,000 website visits. Owned and managed by Frankston City Council, the Centre offers a one stop shop with an accommodation, tour and event booking service, local knowledge, and an impressive range of regional produce and Australian made souvenirs and gifts.</p>
<p><a href="http://www.visitfrankston.com/" class="campaign-extlink" target="_blank" data-partnerid="moersmedia" data-ev="PartnerLead"><strong>Find Out More</strong></a></p>
</div>
</div>
<div data-role="collapsible">
<h3>Hamilton Island Conferences</h3>
<div>
<div class="content-img"><img alt="Hamilton Island Conferences" src="http://www.australia.com/campaigns/mobile/au/nta12/nta-hamilton-island-conference-th9.jpg" /></div>
<p><em><strong>2012 Winner for Business Tourism</strong></em><br />
Hosting more than 100 business events a year, Hamilton Island is the most versatile venue in the Whitsunday region, with the ability to cater for 10 to 1,000 delegates. The Hamilton Island Conference Team offer one-stop conferencing, taking care of every detail from the moment of booking until the last delegate leaves the island. The island's unique event venues and facilities include two bespoke conference centres, airport hangars, wide streets, tropical gardens and lawns and a choice of waters-edge venues including marina piers, poolside marquees and beaches, each providing a unique backdrop for signature 'wow factor' events and business meetings.</p>
<p><a href="http://www.hamiltonisland.com.au/conferences/" class="campaign-extlink" target="_blank" data-partnerid="moersmedia" data-ev="PartnerLead"><strong>Find Out More</strong></a></p>
</div>
</div>
<div data-role="collapsible">
<h3>Yellow Water Cruises</h3>
<div>
<div class="content-img"><img alt="Yellow Water Cruises" src="http://www.australia.com/campaigns/mobile/au/nta12/nta-travel-yellow-water-cruises-th10.jpg" /></div>
<p><em><strong>2012 Winner for Major Tour and/or Transport Operator</strong></em><br />
Yellow Water Cruises is an Indigenous-owned tour guiding operation that gives visitors to Kakadu National Park the exclusive opportunity to explore the breathtakingly beautiful Yellow Water Billabong year round. The Yellow Water Cruise experience dramatically illustrates to visitors why Kakadu National Park is triple World Heritage-listed. Yellow Water Cruises has successfully operated since 1970 and currently employs 15 staff.</p>
<p><a href="http://www.gagudju-dreaming.com/Cruises.aspx" class="campaign-extlink" target="_blank" data-partnerid="moersmedia" data-ev="PartnerLead"><strong>Find Out More</strong></a></p>
</div>
</div>
<div data-role="collapsible">
<h3>Ocean Rafting</h3>
<div>
<div class="content-img"><img alt="Ocean Rafting" src="http://www.australia.com/campaigns/mobile/au/nta12/nta-ocean-rafting-th11.jpg" /></div>
<p><em><strong>2012 Winner for Tour and/or Transport Operator</strong></em><br />
Ocean Rafting offers two exciting tour options, the Northern Exposure and Southern Lights, with each tour offering an exhilarating ride to Whitehaven Beach, pristine snorkelling reefs and guided National Parks walks. Ocean Rafting has access to the stunning and iconic Hill Inlet, and snorkel sites at Hook Island and Border Island ensure a memorable underwater experience. The semi rigid inflatable vessels are super fast, allowing guests to experience a fun ride, adventure and education amongst the beauty of the Whitsundays. The Skipper and Eco Host ensure guests have a fun filled adventure while exploring some of the best Whitsunday destinations.</p>
<p><a href="http://www.oceanrafting.com.au/" class="campaign-extlink" target="_blank" data-partnerid="moersmedia" data-ev="PartnerLead"><strong>Find Out More</strong></a></p>
</div>
</div>
<div data-role="collapsible">
<h3>The Maria Island Walk</h3>
<div>
<div class="content-img"><img alt="The Maria Island Walk" src="http://www.australia.com/campaigns/mobile/au/nta12/nta-maria-island-walk-th12.jpg" /></div>
<p><em><strong>2012 Winner for Adventure Tourism</strong></em><br />
The Maria Island Walk is a beautiful four day guided walk on the World Heritage Maria Island National Park off the east coast of Tasmania. Starting and finishing in Hobart, small groups of eight guests and two guides trek the length of the island exploring World Heritage history and rare wildlife by day and enjoy candlelit dining in exclusive accommodation at night. The Maria Island Walk is a Tasmanian family-owned and operated tourism business that showcases the area's unique wilderness and wildlife, gourmet delights and wine and warm hospitality.</p>
<p><a href="http://www.mariaisland.com.au/?gclid=COGq9OroyLUCFUlcpQodTBoAkg" class="campaign-extlink" target="_blank" data-partnerid="moersmedia" data-ev="PartnerLead"><strong>Find Out More</strong></a></p>
</div>
</div>
<div data-role="collapsible">
<h3>Rottnest Island</h3>
<div>
<div class="content-img"><img alt="Rottnest Island" src="http://www.australia.com/campaigns/mobile/au/nta12/nta-rottnest-tourism-th13.jpg" /></div>
<p><em><strong>2012 Winner for Tourism Marketing</strong></em><br />
In a climate of global financial jitters, fierce overseas competition and a flat domestic tourism market, Rottnest Island has invested heavily in marketing in conjunction with its business partners. The vibrant new brand, Love My Rotto, has featured heavily in print media and TV promotional campaigns, reconnecting the public of Western Australia to their favourite holiday island. Innovative mixed-use in low season, discounted accommodation packages and a winter campaign driven largely through e- and social marketing has enabled the island to maintain higher than industry norm year-round occupancy levels, as well as achieving outstanding visitor satisfaction levels.</p>
<p><a href="http://www.rottnestisland.com/" class="campaign-extlink" target="_blank" data-partnerid="moersmedia" data-ev="PartnerLead"><strong>Find Out More</strong></a></p>
</div>
</div>
<div data-role="collapsible">
<h3>Travel 21fiftythree, Western Sydney Institute, TAFE NSW</h3>
<div>
<div class="content-img"><img alt="Travel 21fiftythree, Western Sydney Institute, TAFE NSW" src="http://www.australia.com/campaigns/mobile/au/nta12/nta-travel-21fiftythree-th14.jpg" /></div>
<p><em><strong>2012 Winner for Tourism Education and Training</strong></em><br />
Passionate and enthusiastic industry specialists have been delivering Travel 21fiftythree's tourism training programs in a flexible, nurturing and award winning environment for 20 years. Providing the best solution for up-skilling existing employees by recognising life skills or for new entrants to the industry, the courses range from Skillsets and Traineeships to Diploma and Advanced Diploma level courses. Travel 21fiftythree at the Hills College specialises in tour guiding, holiday parks and resorts, retail travel, wholesaling, visitor information services, cruise passenger logistics, indigenous tourism, tourism and event management.</p>
<p><a href="http://www.survey.bmtafe.com/website/index.php" class="campaign-extlink" target="_blank" data-partnerid="moersmedia" data-ev="PartnerLead"><strong>Find Out More</strong></a></p>
</div>
</div>
<div data-role="collapsible">
<h3>Margan Restaurant</h3>
<div>
<div class="content-img"><img alt="Margan Restaurant" src="http://www.australia.com/campaigns/mobile/au/nta12/nta-margan-th15.jpg" /></div>
<p><em><strong>2012 Winner for Tourism Restaurants and Catering Services</strong></em><br />
Margan Restaurant is one part of the Margan Family Wines business owned by husband and wife team, Lisa and Andrew Margan. The business is based in the beautiful Broke Fordwich wine sub-region of New South Wales' Hunter Valley and includes 100 hectares of vineyards, a state of the art winery, the Margan Restaurant and Margan Cellar Door. Margan aims to provide customers with a unique and complete food and wine tourism experience. The restaurant continues along the company's line of estate grown-estate made, sourcing produce locally and from the extensive one-acre 'Margan Kitchen Garden' for its modern Mediterranean inspired menu.</p>
<p><a href="http://www.margan.com.au/" class="campaign-extlink" target="_blank" data-partnerid="moersmedia" data-ev="PartnerLead"><strong>Find Out More</strong></a></p>
</div>
</div>
<div data-role="collapsible">
<h3>Wyndham Estate Winery</h3>
<div>
<div class="content-img"><img alt="Wyndham Estate Winery" src="http://www.australia.com/campaigns/mobile/au/nta12/nta-wyndham-estate-th16.jpg" /></div>
<p><em><strong>2012 Winner for Tourism Wineries, Distilleries and Breweries</strong></em><br />
Established in 1828, Wyndham Estate sits peacefully on the banks of the Hunter River surrounded by undulating vineyard and quiet countryside. It offers visitors a range of experiences including intimate tastings of one of Australia's favourite wine brands, leisurely afternoons in The Olive Tree restaurant, relaxing picnics with family and friends, spectacular outdoor concerts, or the serenity of a stroll through picturesque vineyards back to a simpler time. The Wyndham Estate function centre caters for weddings, dinners, and parties in the gentle ambience of the century old winery. Great food, great wine, family, friends and good times.</p>
<p><a href="http://www.wyndhamestate.com/gateway.aspx" class="campaign-extlink" target="_blank" data-partnerid="moersmedia" data-ev="PartnerLead"><strong>Find Out More</strong></a></p>
</div>
</div>
<div data-role="collapsible">
<h3>BIG4 Adventure Whitsunday Resort</h3>
<div>
<div class="content-img"><img alt="BIG4 Adventure Whitsunday Resort" src="http://www.australia.com/campaigns/mobile/au/nta12/nta-big-adventure-holiday-parks-th17.jpg" /></div>
<p><em><strong>2012 Winner for Tourist and Caravan Parks</strong></em><br />
Owned and operated by the McKinnon family for 19 years, BIG4 Adventure Whitsunday Resort has developed an enviable reputation as one of the state's leading resort caravan parks. Whilst the facilities have positioned the resort as a holiday destination in its own right, it is the resort's commitment to customer service that really sets it apart. BIG4 Adventure Whitsunday Resort has built its reputation on providing a level of service that truly exceeds expectation. The resort offers an atmosphere that is genuinely warm, friendly, relaxed and welcoming with an incredibly dedicated team of staff who share the McKinnon family's passion and vision. They live and breathe the business and this is what keeps guests coming back time and time again.</p>
<p><a href="http://www.adventurewhitsunday.com.au/" class="campaign-extlink" target="_blank" data-partnerid="moersmedia" data-ev="PartnerLead"><strong>Find Out More</strong></a></p>
</div>
</div>
<div data-role="collapsible">
<h3>Sydney Harbour YHA</h3>
<div>
<div class="content-img"><img alt="Sydney Harbour YHA" src="http://www.australia.com/campaigns/mobile/au/nta12/nta-sydney-harbour-yha-th18.jpg" /></div>
<p><em><strong>2012 Winner for Backpacker Accommodation</strong></em><br />
Sydney Harbour YHA is the only backpacker accommodation in Sydney's historic Rocks precinct. This purpose-built, 354-bed hostel combines T-QUAL accredited facilities with an environmentally sustainable design, and a unique Australian heritage experience, to set a new benchmark in backpacker accommodation. Built above an archaeological dig site, the YHA features en suite multi-share, double/twin, and family rooms, plus added extras such as WiFi, tour desk, activities, coffee bar and stunning Harbour views from the terrace. Priced from $39 per person per night, Sydney Harbour YHA provides affordable accommodation for budget travellers in a priceless location.</p>
<p><a href="http://www3.yha.com.au/Hostels/NSW/Sydney-Surrounds/Sydney-Harbour/" class="campaign-extlink" target="_blank" data-partnerid="moersmedia" data-ev="PartnerLead"><strong>Find Out More</strong></a></p>
</div>
</div>
<div data-role="collapsible">
<h3>Narrows Escape Rainforest Retreat</h3>
<div>
<div class="content-img"><img alt="Narrows Escape Rainforest Retreat" src="http://www.australia.com/campaigns/mobile/au/nta12/nta-narrows-escape-rainforest-retreat-th19.jpg" /></div>
<p><em><strong>2012 Winner for Hosted Accommodation</strong></em><br />
Narrows Escape Rainforest Retreat is a romantic hideaway designed for couples set in pristine rainforest in the Sunshine Coast hinterland. Joanne and Mark Skinner, owner-operators of this magnificent retreat, live onsite and provide guests with an exclusive and welcoming greeting to their very special part of the world. Multi-award winning, rated 41/2 star by AAA Tourism, and eco-accredited for the last 2 years, visitors and guests of this luxurious retreat are treated to 'the little things' that impress even the toughest of critics. Hosts Joanne and Mark delight in continuous quality improvement and in surpassing their guests' expectations.</p>
<p><a href="http://www.narrowsescape.com.au/" class="campaign-extlink" target="_blank" data-partnerid="moersmedia" data-ev="PartnerLead"><strong>Find Out More</strong></a></p>
</div>
</div>
<div data-role="collapsible">
<h3>Rocky Hills Retreat</h3>
<div>
<div class="content-img"><img alt="Rocky Hills Retreat" src="http://www.australia.com/campaigns/mobile/au/nta12/nta-rocky-hills-retreat-th20.jpg" /></div>
<p><em><strong>2012 Winner for Unique Accommodation</strong></em><br />
Rocky Hills Retreat is a completely private, elegant and intimate space for two, high on a hill overlooking Great Oyster Bay and Maria Island. The retreat provides a luscious platform on 300 acres of Tasmanian bush from which to engage with nature, watch the weather roll in, the sun dancing on the sea, the amazing gentle light in the valley at dusk and the stars looking as though they have been lowered to greet guests. Guests love the hand crafted Huon Pine bath on the evening deck and playing in the fully equipped art studio, just a short wander away.</p>
<p><a href="http://www.rockyhillsretreat.com.au/" class="campaign-extlink" target="_blank" data-partnerid="moersmedia" data-ev="PartnerLead"><strong>Find Out More</strong></a></p>
</div>
</div>
<div data-role="collapsible">
<h3>Narnu Farm</h3>
<div>
<div class="content-img"><img alt="Narnu Farm" src="http://www.australia.com/campaigns/mobile/au/nta12/nta-narnu-farm-th21.jpg" /></div>
<p><em><strong>2012 Winner for Standard Accommodation</strong></em><br />
Narnu Farm, located on Hindmarsh Island, is the perfect family getaway. Seven three-star self-contained cottages and a unique Bunkhouse are available for hire for family groups and schools camps. Guest activities include farm animal feeding, hand cow milking, horse riding, truck rides and much more, ideal for families with children.</p>
<p><a href="http://www.narnufarm.com.au/" class="campaign-extlink" target="_blank" data-partnerid="moersmedia" data-ev="PartnerLead"><strong>Find Out More</strong></a></p>
</div>
</div>
<div data-role="collapsible">
<h3>Emaroo Port Hughes</h3>
<div>
<div class="content-img"><img alt="Emaroo Port Hughes" src="http://www.australia.com/campaigns/mobile/au/nta12/nta-emaroo-port-hughes-deluxe-accommodation-th22.jpg" /></div>
<p><em><strong>2012 Winner for Deluxe Accommodation</strong></em><br />
Emaroo is a 4-star, two-storey, superbly equipped luxurious accommodation on the Yorke Peninsula. It can cater for up to ten people and features spectacular living areas and a games room, plus all the little extra touches to make guests' stay a memorable one. Guests can take advantage of the unique deals available including professional catering, fish cleaning and charter boat cruises as well as exclusive discounts and packages with local tourism and hospitality providers. Emaroo is just a short stroll to the beautiful South Beach, a five minute walk to the jetty and boat ramp and only 168km drive from Adelaide.</p>
<p><a href="http://www.emaroocottages.com.au/index.htm" class="campaign-extlink" target="_blank" data-partnerid="moersmedia" data-ev="PartnerLead"><strong>Find Out More</strong></a></p>
</div>
</div>
<div data-role="collapsible">
<h3>Emporium Hotel</h3>
<div>
<div class="content-img"><img alt="Emporium Hotel" src="http://www.australia.com/campaigns/mobile/au/nta12/nta-emporium-hotel-th23.jpg" /></div>
<p><em><strong>2012 Winner for Luxury Accommodation</strong></em><br />
Emporium Hotel opened its doors in June 2007 as a luxury boutique property focused on delivering the unanticipated in enchanting hospitality, exquisite design, opulence and elegance. The Emporium Hotel's philosophy ensures every guest experience will be remembered as an exquisite stay, from a martini in the eclectic cocktail bar to advice from concierge. This property is a statement of luxurious interior design featuring 102 suites, rooftop terrace, contemporary function centre and Belle Epoque French Patisserie. As an independently owned and managed property, the Emporium Hotel has driven new thinking in the industry and benchmarked what is possible when a team of passionate professionals focus on pushing traditional hospitality boundaries.</p>
<p><a href="http://www.emporiumhotel.com.au/" class="campaign-extlink" target="_blank" data-partnerid="moersmedia" data-ev="PartnerLead"><strong>Find Out More</strong></a></p>
</div>
</div>
<div data-role="collapsible">
<h3>Madame Tussauds Sydney</h3>
<div>
<div class="content-img"><img alt="Madame Tussauds Sydney" src="http://www.australia.com/campaigns/mobile/au/nta12/nta-madame-tussauds-th24.jpg" /></div>
<p><em><strong>2012 Winner for New Tourism Development</strong></em><br />
Madame Tussauds Sydney is a new highly interactive immersive attraction where its customers are able to get up close and personal with the people they really want to meet. The attraction is heavily geared towards Australian icons from diverse areas including Australian history, world leaders, sports, music, culture, science, TV, film and A-list celebrities. Being a brand new attraction in Darling Harbour and a product of a quality that has not existed in Australia before, Madame Tussauds Sydney is a key new addition to Australian tourism.</p>
<p><a href="http://www.madametussauds.com/sydney/" class="campaign-extlink" target="_blank" data-partnerid="moersmedia" data-ev="PartnerLead"><strong>Find Out More</strong></a></p>
</div>
</div>
<div data-role="collapsible">
<h3>Pennicott Wilderness Journeys</h3>
<div>
<div class="content-img"><img alt="Pennicott Wilderness Journeys" src="http://www.australia.com/campaigns/mobile/au/nta12/nta-pennicott-wilderness-journeys-th25.jpg" /></div>
<p><em><strong>2012 Winner for Qantas Award for Excellence in Sustainable Tourism</strong></em><br />
Pennicott Wilderness Journeys provides eco-cruise experiences showcasing the spectacular coastal wilderness of Southern Tasmania. Both its Bruny Island and Tasman Island Cruises feature the highest sea cliffs in the southern hemisphere, deep sea caves and abundant sea and coastal wildlife. Sustainable business practices are core to the business's success, through careful planning and investment, environmental impact minimisation and maximisation of benefits to the local community. Pennicott Wilderness Journeys is Advanced Ecotourism Accredited, 100% carbon offset and Earthcheck Assessed, achieving Best Practice scores for all measurements. A significant portion of the business profits are donated towards important conservation and humanitarian projects.</p>
<p><a href="http://www.pennicottjourneys.com.au/" class="campaign-extlink" target="_blank" data-partnerid="moersmedia" data-ev="PartnerLead"><strong>Find Out More</strong></a></p>
</div>
</div>
</div>]]>
	</txt_MobileContentOnly>
	<txt_SpotlightTag>
        <![CDATA[]]>
	</txt_SpotlightTag>
	<txt_Teaser>
        <![CDATA[
        Explore the best Australia has to offer.
    ]]>
	</txt_Teaser>
	<con_Body>
		<StandardCampaignLayout isTemplate="1">
			<opt_national_landscapes_id><![CDATA[]]>
			</opt_national_landscapes_id>
			<hdl_Title><![CDATA[]]>
			</hdl_Title>
			<stf_hideInXmlSitemap><![CDATA[]]>
			</stf_hideInXmlSitemap>
			<stf_TargetedCountry><![CDATA[]]>
			</stf_TargetedCountry>
			<con_Banner></con_Banner>
			<con_Body>
				<TopCategoryHighlights isTemplate="1">
					<stf_Heading><![CDATA[The Australian Tourism Awards 2013]]></stf_Heading>
					<stf_InformationTitle><![CDATA[]]>
					</stf_InformationTitle>
					<txt_Information><![CDATA[
        <table>
            <tbody>
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-right: 20px;">
                    <p><img alt="" src="/contentimages/Campaigns/campaigns-au-tourismaus-award13-page01-logo.jpg" /></p>
                    </td>
                    <td valign="top">
                    <p>The Australian Tourism Awards are the tourism industry’s peak awards – recognising and promoting excellence in tourism. Whether it is visiting the animals at Taronga Zoo in Sydney, cruising with Bruny Island Cruises in Tasmania, diving with Great Whites in South Australia or enjoying the spectacle that is the Melbourne Cup Carnival, the experiences below will inspire you to discover why there’s nothing like Australia.</p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
            </tbody>
        </table>
        <br />
        <br />
        <table>
            <tbody>
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-top: 3px; padding-right: 5px;">
                    <p><a href="http://taronga.org.au/taronga-zoo" onclick="ntptEventTag('ev=PartnerLead&amp;PartnerId=taronga');" target="_blank"><img alt="" src="/contentimages/Campaigns/campaigns-au-tourismaus-award13-page01-hl1.jpg" /></a></p>
                    </td>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-bottom: 20px;">
                    <p><span style="color: rgb(51, 51, 51); font-size: 13px;"><strong><a name="1"></a>Taronga Zoo, NSW<br />
                    </strong></span><span style="color: rgb(102, 102, 102); font-size: 11px;"><strong>2013 Winner for Major Tourist Attractions<br />
                    </strong></span></p>
                    <p>Taronga Zoo, named after the Aboriginal word for beautiful view, is situated in Mosman, Sydney NSW, with an unrivalled position overlooking one of the most beautiful harbours in the world. Opening in 1916, Taronga has welcomed over 95 million visitors during its history and is home to 4,000 animals and over 360 species.As the most visited paid attraction in Sydney for the last four years, the zoo is a leading wildlife conservation organisation, committed to saving endangered species such as the Tasmanian Devil while creating amazing and informative experiences that showcase the wonders of wildlife to visitors. </p>
                    <p><img alt="" src="/contentimages/arrow-red.png" />    <a href="http://taronga.org.au/taronga-zoo" onclick="ntptEventTag('ev=PartnerLead&amp;PartnerId=taronga');" target="_blank">Find Out More</a></p>
                    <p style="text-align: right;"><a href="#top">Back To Top</a></p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-top: 3px; padding-right: 5px;">
                    <p><a href="http://taronga.org.au/taronga-western-plains-zoo" onclick="ntptEventTag('ev=PartnerLead&amp;PartnerId=tarongawesternplainszoo'');" target="_blank"><img alt="" src="/contentimages/Campaigns/campaigns-au-tourismaus-award13-page01-hl2.jpg" /></a></p>
                    </td>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-bottom: 20px;">
                    <p><span style="color: rgb(51, 51, 51); font-size: 13px;"><strong><a name="2"></a>Taronga Western Plains Zoo, NSW<br />
                    </strong></span><span style="color: rgb(102, 102, 102); font-size: 11px;"><strong>2013 Winner for Tourist Attractions<br />
                    </strong></span></p>
                    <p>Taronga Western Plains Zoo in Dubbo, NSW is a 300 hectare open range ‘Zoo fari’ that undertakes a vital role in national and international conservation programs for rare and endangered species, as well as being regional NSW largest visitor attraction. The Zoo is home to over 700 animals viewed from a 6km circuit that can be traversed by car, bike, electric safari cart or on foot. Entry over two days, offers visitors a unique range of activities including keeper presentations, tours and encounters. The Zoo is home to the award winning Zoofari Lodge and the brand new Billabong Camp.</p>
                    <p><img alt="" src="/contentimages/arrow-red.png" />    <a href="http://taronga.org.au/taronga-western-plains-zoo" onclick="ntptEventTag('ev=PartnerLead&amp;PartnerId=tarongawesternplainszoo'');" target="_blank">Find Out More</a></p>
                    <p style="text-align: right;"><a href="#top">Back To Top</a></p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-top: 3px; padding-right: 5px;">
                    <p><a href="http://www.flemington.com.au" onclick="ntptEventTag('ev=PartnerLead&amp;PartnerId=flemington');" target="_blank"><img alt="" src="/contentimages/Campaigns/campaigns-au-tourismaus-award13-page01-hl3.jpg" /></a></p>
                    </td>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-bottom: 20px;">
                    <p><span style="color: rgb(51, 51, 51); font-size: 13px;"><strong><a name="3"></a>Melbourne Cup Carnival, VIC<br />
                    </strong></span><span style="color: rgb(102, 102, 102); font-size: 11px;"><strong>2013 Winner for Major Festivals &amp; Events<br />
                    </strong></span></p>
                    <p>Melbourne is one of the world's greatest sporting cities, and the Melbourne Cup Carnival is the jewel in its calendar of major events.The Emirates Melbourne Cup “a unique sporting, social and cultural phenomenon“ is representative of the city which bears its name; it is the 'Race that Stops a Nation'. No other event provides the unique combination of sport, culture, food and wine, and fashion as the Melbourne Cup Carnival. For this reason, the four fabulous days at Flemington remain unmatched as a destination for business and social interaction, networking and branding opportunities.</p>
                    <p><img alt="" src="/contentimages/arrow-red.png" />    <a href="http://www.flemington.com.au" onclick="ntptEventTag('ev=PartnerLead&amp;PartnerId=flemington');" target="_blank">Find Out More</a></p>
                    <p style="text-align: right;"><a href="#top">Back To Top</a></p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-top: 3px; padding-right: 5px;">
                    <p><a href="http://www.bgpa.wa.gov.au/kings-park" onclick="ntptEventTag('ev=PartnerLead&amp;PartnerId=bgpa');" target="_blank"><img alt="" src="/contentimages/Campaigns/campaigns-au-tourismaus-award13-page01-hl4.jpg" /></a></p>
                    </td>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-bottom: 20px;">
                    <p><span style="color: rgb(51, 51, 51); font-size: 13px;"><strong><a name="4"></a>Kings Park Festival, WA<br />
                    </strong></span><span style="color: rgb(102, 102, 102); font-size: 11px;"><strong>2013 Winner for Festivals &amp; Events </strong></span></p>
                    <p>For the past 50 years, each September Western Australia's spectacular and unique wildflowers take centre stage at the Kings Park Festival. First held in 1965, the Festival has become a long-running tradition to celebrate spring and the wonderful wildflowers that appear throughout the south west of Western Australia. From humble beginnings with plant specimens in jars on trestle tables the Festival has blossomed into a month long celebration of floral displays, live music, exhibitions, workshops, interpretive artworks, guided walks and family activities. Held against a stunning backdrop of wildflowers the 2012 festival attracted over 600,000 local, intrastate and interstate visitors.</p>
                    <p><img alt="" src="/contentimages/arrow-red.png" />    <a href="http://www.bgpa.wa.gov.au/kings-park" onclick="ntptEventTag('ev=PartnerLead&amp;PartnerId=bgpa');" target="_blank">Find Out More</a><span style="color: rgb(128, 128, 128);"></span></p>
                    <p style="text-align: right;"><a href="#top">Back To Top</a></p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-top: 3px; padding-right: 5px;">
                    <p><a href="http://www.pennicottjourneys.com.au" onclick="ntptEventTag('ev=PartnerLead&amp;PartnerId=pennicottjourneys');" target="_blank"><img alt="" src="/contentimages/Campaigns/campaigns-au-tourismaus-award13-page01-hl5.jpg" /></a></p>
                    </td>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-bottom: 20px;">
                    <p><span style="color: rgb(51, 51, 51); font-size: 13px;"><strong><a name="5"></a>Bruny Island Cruises, TAS<br />
                    </strong></span><span style="color: rgb(102, 102, 102); font-size: 11px;"><strong>2013 Winner for Ecotourism<br />
                    </strong></span></p>
                    <p>Bruny Island Cruises provides three hour eco-cruises exploring the rugged coastline and abundant wildlife of Bruny Island in southern Tasmania.</p>
                    <p><img alt="" src="/contentimages/arrow-red.png" />    <a href="http://www.pennicottjourneys.com.au" onclick="ntptEventTag('ev=PartnerLead&amp;PartnerId=pennicottjourneys');" target="_blank">Find Out More</a></p>
                    <p style="text-align: right;"><a href="#top">Back To Top</a></p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-top: 3px; padding-right: 5px;">
                    <p><a href="http://www.jenolancaves.org.au" onclick="ntptEventTag('ev=PartnerLead&amp;PartnerId=jenolancaves');" target="_blank"><img alt="" src="/contentimages/Campaigns/campaigns-au-tourismaus-award13-page01-hl6.jpg" /></a></p>
                    </td>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-bottom: 20px;">
                    <p><span style="color: rgb(51, 51, 51); font-size: 13px;"><strong><a name="6"></a>Jenolan Caves: Written In Stone, NSW<br />
                    </strong></span><span style="color: rgb(102, 102, 102); font-size: 11px;"><strong>2013 Winner for Heritage &amp; Cultural Tourism<br />
                    </strong></span></p>
                    <p>Jenolan Caves is Australia’s premier tourist cave destination. Known by the Gundungurra people as ‘Binoomea’, this crystal wonderland is listed on the State Heritage Register and is Advanced Ecotourism accredited. With the appointment of the first government ‘keeper’ in 1866, Jenolan is Australia’s longest continually operating tourist destination. Jenolan has a rich tradition of technical innovation, scientific discovery and cultural connection to generations of visitors. This heritage is very much alive, and passed on by a dedicated and passionate staff through a variety of interpretive activities, a range of cultural festivals, living history tours, concerts and theatrical events in the caves.</p>
                    <p><img alt="" src="/contentimages/arrow-red.png" />    <a href="http://www.jenolancaves.org.au" onclick="ntptEventTag('ev=PartnerLead&amp;PartnerId=jenolancaves');" target="_blank">Find Out More</a></p>
                    <p style="text-align: right;"><a href="#top">Back To Top</a></p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-top: 3px; padding-right: 5px;">
                    <p><a href="http://www.tristate.com.au" onclick="ntptEventTag('ev=PartnerLead&amp;PartnerId=tristate');" target="_blank"><img alt="" src="/contentimages/Campaigns/campaigns-au-tourismaus-award13-page01-hl7.jpg" /></a></p>
                    </td>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-bottom: 20px;">
                    <p><span style="color: rgb(51, 51, 51); font-size: 13px;"><strong><a name="7"></a>Tri State Safaris/Mutawintji Eco Tours, NSW<br />
                    </strong></span><span style="color: rgb(102, 102, 102); font-size: 11px;"><strong>2013 Winner for  Indigenous Tourism<br />
                    </strong></span></p>
                    <p>Mutawintji Eco Tours is based in Broken Hill and is part of the Tri State Safaris family. Our Aboriginal guides lead tours that focus on experience and quality interpretation. Customers are able to walk across ground that has been home to it’s original inhabitants for thousands of years.Our guides are part of the local community and have a connection to this country.  Our tours travel to places such as Mutawintji, Kinchega and Mungo National Parks. A tour to one of these places is a special experience, with people who are passionate about sharing their knowledge to others.</p>
                    <p><img alt="" src="/contentimages/arrow-red.png" />    <a href="http://www.tristate.com.au" onclick="ntptEventTag('ev=PartnerLead&amp;PartnerId=tristate');" target="_blank">Find Out More</a></p>
                    <p style="text-align: right;"><a href="#top">Back To Top</a></p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-top: 3px; padding-right: 5px;">
                    <p><a href="http://www.diytourguide.com.au" onclick="ntptEventTag('ev=PartnerLead&amp;PartnerId=diytourguide');" target="_blank"><img alt="" src="/contentimages/Campaigns/campaigns-au-tourismaus-award13-page01-hl8.jpg" /></a></p>
                    </td>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-bottom: 20px;">
                    <p><span style="color: rgb(51, 51, 51); font-size: 13px;"><strong><a name="8"></a>DIY Tourguide Australia, NT<br />
                    </strong></span><span style="color: rgb(102, 102, 102); font-size: 11px;"><strong>2013 Winner for Specialised Tourism Services<br />
                    </strong></span></p>
                    <p>DIY Tourguide is a specialised tourism service that offers audio travel guides for the self-drive traveller including commentary about history, geology, flora, fauna, culture and all the best places to stop en route. Audio guides are available in 3 formats - CD, MP3 download and iPhone app. Current tours are Alice Springs to Uluru and The West MacDonnell Ranges. Audio guides have been translated into Italian, French and Chinese.</p>
                    <p><img alt="" src="/contentimages/arrow-red.png" />    <a href="http://www.diytourguide.com.au" onclick="ntptEventTag('ev=PartnerLead&amp;PartnerId=diytourguide');" target="_blank">Find Out More</a></p>
                    <p style="text-align: right;"><a href="#top">Back To Top</a></p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-top: 3px; padding-right: 5px;">
                    <p><a href="http://www.visitfrankston.com" onclick="ntptEventTag('ev=PartnerLead&amp;PartnerId=visitfrankston');" target="_blank"><img alt="" src="/contentimages/Campaigns/campaigns-au-tourismaus-award13-page01-hl9.jpg" /></a></p>
                    </td>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-bottom: 20px;">
                    <p><span style="color: rgb(51, 51, 51); font-size: 13px;"><strong><a name="9"></a>Frankston Visitor Information Centre, VIC<br />
                    </strong></span><span style="color: rgb(102, 102, 102); font-size: 11px;"><strong>2013 Winner for Visitor Information &amp; Services<br />
                    </strong></span></p>
                    <p>Strategically located at the spectacular Frankston Waterfront, the Frankston Visitor Information Centre provides quality information and retailing which complements the Mornington Peninsula region. Opened in 2007 the Centre is owned and managed by Frankston City Council. The Centre provides a central point for a range of ticketing, booking and community services encompassing a wide range of customer needs. Visitors are encouraged to explore the vibrant, urban waterfront destination of Frankston where arts, nature and cultural experiences connect. This service is delivered by friendly and passionate locals with an intrinsic knowledge of the region. Frankston... where your Mornington Peninsula experience begins.</p>
                    <p><img alt="" src="/contentimages/arrow-red.png" />    <a href="http://www.visitfrankston.com" onclick="ntptEventTag('ev=PartnerLead&amp;PartnerId=visitfrankston');" target="_blank">Find Out More</a></p>
                    <p style="text-align: right;"><a href="#top">Back To Top</a></p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-top: 3px; padding-right: 5px;">
                    <p><a href="http://www.ulurumeetingplace.com.au/" onclick="ntptEventTag('ev=PartnerLead&amp;PartnerId=ulurumeetingplace');" target="_blank"><img alt="" src="/contentimages/Campaigns/campaigns-au-tourismaus-award13-page01-hl10.jpg" /></a></p>
                    </td>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-bottom: 20px;">
                    <p><span style="color: rgb(51, 51, 51); font-size: 13px;"><strong><a name="10"></a>Uluru Meeting Place, NT<br />
                    </strong></span><span style="color: rgb(102, 102, 102); font-size: 11px;"><strong>2013 Winner for  Business Tourism<br />
                    </strong></span></p>
                    <p>The Uluru Meeting Place, opening in November 2012, is a complete conference facility for up to 420 delegates. That allows delegates to not only immerse themselves in this stunning desert landscape but also learn more about the intricacies of Australia's indigenous culture.</p>
                    <p><img alt="" src="/contentimages/arrow-red.png" />    <a href="http://www.ulurumeetingplace.com.au/" onclick="ntptEventTag('ev=PartnerLead&amp;PartnerId=ulurumeetingplace');" target="_blank">Find Out More</a></p>
                    <p style="text-align: right;"><a href="#top">Back To Top</a></p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-top: 3px; padding-right: 5px;">
                    <p><a href="http://www.spiritoftasmania.com.au" onclick="ntptEventTag('ev=PartnerLead&amp;PartnerId=spiritoftasmania');" target="_blank"><img alt="" src="/contentimages/Campaigns/campaigns-au-tourismaus-award13-page01-hl11.jpg" /></a></p>
                    </td>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-bottom: 20px;">
                    <p><span style="color: rgb(51, 51, 51); font-size: 13px;"><strong><a name="11"></a>Spirit of Tasmania, TAS<br />
                    </strong></span><span style="color: rgb(102, 102, 102); font-size: 11px;"><strong>2013 Winner for Major Tour &amp;/or Transport Operator<br />
                    </strong></span></p>
                    <p>Spirit of Tasmania is one of Australia's most iconic journeys. The 232 nautical mile voyage between Port Melbourne in Victoria and Devonport in Tasmania, crosses the infamous Bass Strait, and takes approximately 9 hours, travelling at an average speed of 27 knots.Spirit of Tasmania I and II provide a leisurely cruise between Tasmania and Victoria for thousands of travellers seeking a high quality tourism experience to start and end their holiday. They also offer additional benefits of convenience, flexibility and affordability as passengers can take their vehicles, bikes and even their pets with them!The twin vessels depart every evening in opposite directions, leaving each port (Melbourne or Devonport) at 7.30pm and arriving the following morning at 6.00am. Day sailings also operate in peak season only. The ships each have four main decks, six vehicle decks, two restaurants, cafe, kids play area, games arcade, gift shop, tourist information centre, internet kiosks, four bars, gaming lounge, on board cinema ...</p>
                    <p><img alt="" src="/contentimages/arrow-red.png" />    <a href="http://www.spiritoftasmania.com.au" onclick="ntptEventTag('ev=PartnerLead&amp;PartnerId=spiritoftasmania');" target="_blank">Find Out More</a></p>
                    <p style="text-align: right;"><a href="#top">Back To Top</a></p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-top: 3px; padding-right: 5px;">
                    <p><a href="http://www.tourbarossa.com" onclick="ntptEventTag('ev=PartnerLead&amp;PartnerId=tourbarossa');" target="_blank"><img alt="" src="/contentimages/Campaigns/campaigns-au-tourismaus-award13-page01-hl12.jpg" /></a></p>
                    </td>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-bottom: 20px;">
                    <p><span style="color: rgb(51, 51, 51); font-size: 13px;"><strong><a name="12"></a>Tour Barossa, SA<br />
                    </strong></span><span style="color: rgb(102, 102, 102); font-size: 11px;"><strong>2013 Winner for Tour and Transport Operator</strong></span></p>
                    <p>Owners Steve and Kym Brown, commenced Tour Barossa in July 2008 with one 12 seat mini bus, we have grown to a fleet of 8 vehicles providing the exclusive, cost effective, flexible, fun solution for touring the Barossa Valley and beyond. Visiting small boutique wineries and some iconic favourites, sit back, relax, enjoy, and let a local driver take you to some Barossa highlights and exclusive experiences. You will indulge with our 'Charm, Chocolate, Wine and Wood Fire Tour' or 'Tantalise your Senses' all with the Advanced Ecotourism certified and multi Award Winning business, committed to exceeding expectations.</p>
                    <p><img alt="" src="/contentimages/arrow-red.png" />    <a href="http://www.tourbarossa.com" onclick="ntptEventTag('ev=PartnerLead&amp;PartnerId=tourbarossa');" target="_blank">Find Out More</a></p>
                    <p style="text-align: right;"><a href="#top">Back To Top</a></p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-top: 3px; padding-right: 5px;">
                    <p><a href="http://www.lifesanadventure.com.au" onclick="ntptEventTag('ev=PartnerLead&amp;PartnerId=lifesanadventure');" target="_blank"><img alt="" src="/contentimages/Campaigns/campaigns-au-tourismaus-award13-page01-hl13.jpg" /></a></p>
                    </td>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-bottom: 20px;">
                    <p><span style="color: rgb(51, 51, 51); font-size: 13px;"><strong><a name="13"></a>Life's An Adventure, NSW<br />
                    </strong></span><span style="color: rgb(102, 102, 102); font-size: 11px;"><strong>2013 Winner for  Adventure Tourism<br />
                    </strong></span></p>
                    <p>Life's An Adventure specialises in award-winning 4WD, hiking, biking and kayaking adventures in the Blue Mountains, Sydney and Australia.</p>
                    <p><img alt="" src="/contentimages/arrow-red.png" />    <a href="http://www.lifesanadventure.com.au" onclick="ntptEventTag('ev=PartnerLead&amp;PartnerId=lifesanadventure');" target="_blank">Find Out More</a></p>
                    <p style="text-align: right;"><a href="#top">Back To Top</a></p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-top: 3px; padding-right: 5px;">
                    <p><a href="http://humanbrochure.com.au" onclick="ntptEventTag('ev=PartnerLead&amp;PartnerId=humanbrochure');" target="_blank"><img alt="" src="/contentimages/Campaigns/campaigns-au-tourismaus-award13-page01-hl14.jpg" /></a></p>
                    </td>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-bottom: 20px;">
                    <p><span style="color: rgb(51, 51, 51); font-size: 13px;"><strong><a name="14"></a>The Human Brochure, ACT<br />
                    </strong></span><span style="color: rgb(102, 102, 102); font-size: 11px;"><strong>2013 Winner for Destination Marketing<br />
                    </strong></span></p>
                    <p>The Human Brochure optimises innovation. It is a world first tourism generation project that has received international interest and similar projects are now expected to be adopted across Australia and internationally. The project was conceived, developed and run by the Australian Capital Tourism team in EDD. Humans were split into four groups: foodies, family fun, adventure, arts and culture.</p>
                    <p><img alt="" src="/contentimages/arrow-red.png" />    <a href="http://humanbrochure.com.au" onclick="ntptEventTag('ev=PartnerLead&amp;PartnerId=humanbrochure');" target="_blank">Find Out More</a></p>
                    <p style="text-align: right;"><a href="#top">Back To Top</a></p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-top: 3px; padding-right: 5px;">
                    <p><a href="http://www.bluemountains.edu.au" onclick="ntptEventTag('ev=PartnerLead&amp;PartnerId=bluemountains');" target="_blank"><img alt="" src="/contentimages/Campaigns/campaigns-au-tourismaus-award13-page01-hl15.jpg" /></a></p>
                    </td>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-bottom: 20px;">
                    <p><span style="color: rgb(51, 51, 51); font-size: 13px;"><strong><a name="15"></a>Blue Mountains International Hotel Management School, NSW<br />
                    </strong></span><span style="color: rgb(102, 102, 102); font-size: 11px;"><strong>2013 Winner for  Tourism Education &amp; Training<br />
                    </strong></span></p>
                    <p>The Blue Mountains International Hotel Management School provides world class tertiary level tourism education and training. Students can graduate with a Bachelor of Business (International Hotel &amp; Resort Management), Bachelor of Business (International Event Management) and/or Master of International Hotel Management. Operating since 1991 BMIHMS has provided highly sought after tertiary qualifications to more than 3,700 international and domestic graduates with 100% employment. Recognised by industry as the first hotel school in Australia to incorporate substantial periods of industry placement (the Swiss approach), placing students in an operating hotel environment ensures real world experience and industry ready graduates.</p>
                    <p><img alt="" src="/contentimages/arrow-red.png" />    <a href="http://www.bluemountains.edu.au" onclick="ntptEventTag('ev=PartnerLead&amp;PartnerId=bluemountains');" target="_blank">Find Out More</a></p>
                    <p style="text-align: right;"><a href="#top">Back To Top</a></p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-top: 3px; padding-right: 5px;">
                    <p><a href="http://cornerrestaurant.com.au" onclick="ntptEventTag('ev=PartnerLead&amp;PartnerId=cornerrestaurant');" target="_blank"><img alt="" src="/contentimages/Campaigns/campaigns-au-tourismaus-award13-page01-hl16.jpg" /></a></p>
                    </td>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-bottom: 20px;">
                    <p><span style="color: rgb(51, 51, 51); font-size: 13px;"><strong><a name="16"></a>The Corner Restaurant, NSW<br />
                    </strong></span><span style="color: rgb(102, 102, 102); font-size: 11px;"><strong>2013 Winner for Tourism Restaurants &amp; Catering Services<br />
                    </strong></span></p>
                    <p>The Corner offers a contemporary vibe with a menu driven by seasonal produce, the freshest ingredients and passionate minds. The restaurant is open for breakfast and lunch 7 days from 7am and dinner Monday – Saturday. Serving the finest Campos coffee roast all day and located under the award winning Macquarie Waters boutique hotel.The restaurant is fully licensed with a quality wine list reflecting the best drops from the best regions. The Corner is passionate about fresh food, local produce, great service and ensuring visitors to our region have an exceptional experience.</p>
                    <p><img alt="" src="/contentimages/arrow-red.png" />    <a href="http://cornerrestaurant.com.au" onclick="ntptEventTag('ev=PartnerLead&amp;PartnerId=cornerrestaurant');" target="_blank">Find Out More</a></p>
                    <p style="text-align: right;"><a href="#top">Back To Top</a></p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-top: 3px; padding-right: 5px;">
                    <p><a href="http://www.pindarie.com.au" onclick="ntptEventTag('ev=PartnerLead&amp;PartnerId=pindarie');" target="_blank"><img alt="" src="/contentimages/Campaigns/campaigns-au-tourismaus-award13-page01-hl17.jpg" /></a></p>
                    </td>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-bottom: 20px;">
                    <p><span style="color: rgb(51, 51, 51); font-size: 13px;"><strong><a name="17"></a>Pindarie Cellar Door, SA<br />
                    </strong></span><span style="color: rgb(102, 102, 102); font-size: 11px;"><strong>2013 Winner for Tourism Wineries, Distilleries and Breweries<br />
                    </strong></span></p>
                    <p>Pindaries Cellar Door is set on the Barossa's Western Ridge, above the contoured farm, which provides spectacular, expansive views to the Barossa Ranges. The cellar door offers visitors premium wines for tasting and sale, regional food, heritage, family attraction and hospitality. Visitors can sample award-winning wine styles, whilst taking in the views or relaxing over our gourmet seasonal lunches. The adjacent stables and nearby historic buildings combine modern facilities with rustic charm, highlighting their original existence. Family friendly, with wonderful outdoor play area for children, disabled access. Open 7 days from 11 a.m.</p>
                    <p><img alt="" src="/contentimages/arrow-red.png" />    <a href="http://www.pindarie.com.au" onclick="ntptEventTag('ev=PartnerLead&amp;PartnerId=pindarie');" target="_blank">Find Out More</a></p>
                    <p style="text-align: right;"><a href="#top">Back To Top</a></p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-top: 3px; padding-right: 5px;">
                    <p><a href="http://www.coconut.com.au" onclick="ntptEventTag('ev=PartnerLead&amp;PartnerId=coconut');" target="_blank"><img alt="" src="/contentimages/Campaigns/campaigns-au-tourismaus-award13-page01-hl18.jpg" /></a></p>
                    </td>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-bottom: 20px;">
                    <p><span style="color: rgb(51, 51, 51); font-size: 13px;"><strong><a name="18"></a>Cairns Coconut Holiday Resort, QLD<br />
                    </strong></span><span style="color: rgb(102, 102, 102); font-size: 11px;"><strong>2013 Winner for  Tourist &amp; Caravan Parks<br />
                    </strong></span></p>
                    <p>Set amidst 28 acres of tropical landscaped gardens Cairns Coconut Holiday Resort is the perfect family holiday destination for holiday makers from Australia and all over the world. We offer a range of self-contained accommodation styles priced to suit all budgets, from luxury Condos, Villas, Holiday Units and Cabins to powered grass and slab sites suitable for caravans, motorhomes and campers.Free resort activities include the SPLASH waterpark, Australia's first NEOS 360ADA interactive playground attraction, gymnasium, 2 huge resort pools, 2 jumping pillows, day/night tennis, 18 hole mini-golf, beach volleyball, enormous adventure playground and so much more. </p>
                    <p><img alt="" src="/contentimages/arrow-red.png" />    <a href="http://www.coconut.com.au" onclick="ntptEventTag('ev=PartnerLead&amp;PartnerId=coconut');" target="_blank">Find Out More</a></p>
                    <p style="text-align: right;"><a href="#top">Back To Top</a></p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-top: 3px; padding-right: 5px;">
                    <p><a href="http://www.yha.com.au" onclick="ntptEventTag('ev=PartnerLead&amp;PartnerId=yha');" target="_blank"><img alt="" src="/contentimages/Campaigns/campaigns-au-tourismaus-award13-page01-hl19.jpg" /></a></p>
                    </td>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-bottom: 20px;">
                    <p><span style="color: rgb(51, 51, 51); font-size: 13px;"><strong><a name="19"></a>Sydney Harbour YHA, NSW<br />
                    </strong></span><span style="color: rgb(102, 102, 102); font-size: 11px;"><strong>2013 Winner for Backpacker  Accomodation<br />
                    </strong></span></p>
                    <p>Open since October 2009, Sydney Harbour YHA is the only backpacker accommodation in Sydney's historic Rocks precinct.This purpose-built, 354-bed hostel combines premium facilities with an environmentally sustainable design, and a unique Australian heritage experience, to set a new benchmark in backpacker accommodation.Built above an archaeological dig site, the YHA features ensuite multi-share, double/twin, and family rooms, plus added extras such as WiFi, tour desk, activities, coffee bar, and stunning Harbour views from the terrace.Priced from $41 per person per night, Sydney Harbour YHA provides affordable accommodation for budget travellers in a priceless location.  </p>
                    <p><img alt="" src="/contentimages/arrow-red.png" />    <a href="http://www.yha.com.au" onclick="ntptEventTag('ev=PartnerLead&amp;PartnerId=yha');" target="_blank">Find Out More</a></p>
                    <p style="text-align: right;"><a href="#top">Back To Top</a></p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-top: 3px; padding-right: 5px;">
                    <p><a href="http://www.narrowsescape.com.au" onclick="ntptEventTag('ev=PartnerLead&amp;PartnerId=narrowsescape');" target="_blank"><img alt="" src="/contentimages/Campaigns/campaigns-au-tourismaus-award13-page01-hl20.jpg" /></a></p>
                    </td>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-bottom: 20px;">
                    <p><span style="color: rgb(51, 51, 51); font-size: 13px;"><strong><a name="20"></a>Narrows Escape Rainforest Retreat, QLD<br />
                    </strong></span><span style="color: rgb(102, 102, 102); font-size: 11px;"><strong>2013 Winner for Hosted Accommodation<br />
                    </strong></span></p>
                    <p>Narrows Escape Rainforest Retreat is a romantic hideaway designed for couples set in magnificent rainforest at Montville on the Sunshine Coast hinterland. Owners Joanne and Mark Skinner work closely with onsite Managers Karen and Michael Cross to ensure guests are spoiled during their stay in this very special and secluded part of the world. The team at Narrows Escape delight in continuous quality improvement and in surpassing their guests expectations!</p>
                    <p><img alt="" src="/contentimages/arrow-red.png" />    <a href="http://www.narrowsescape.com.au" onclick="ntptEventTag('ev=PartnerLead&amp;PartnerId=narrowsescape');" target="_blank">Find Out More</a></p>
                    <p style="text-align: right;"><a href="#top">Back To Top</a></p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-top: 3px; padding-right: 5px;">
                    <p><a href="http://www.whitsundayescape.com/" onclick="ntptEventTag('ev=PartnerLead&amp;PartnerId=whitsundayescape');" target="_blank"><img alt="" src="/contentimages/Campaigns/campaigns-au-tourismaus-award13-page01-hl21.jpg" /></a></p>
                    </td>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-bottom: 20px;">
                    <p><span style="color: rgb(51, 51, 51); font-size: 13px;"><strong><a name="21"></a>Whitsunday Escape, QLD<br />
                    </strong></span><span style="color: rgb(102, 102, 102); font-size: 11px;"><strong>2013 Winner for Unique Accommodation</strong></span></p>
                    <p>Whitsunday Escape is a charter boat company specialising in skipper yourself charters or Bareboats. The guests rent the boat and skipper/drive the boats themselves without the assistance of a professional skipper or crew. The boats are self contained and fully equipped for extended cruising. The modern fleet of 30 consists of Power Cruisers, Power Catamarans, Sailing Catamarans and Sailing Yachts. They range in size from 33 to 50 ft and can accommodate from 6 to 12 people. With its countless anchorages, deserted beaches and pristine coral reefs, the Whitsundays offers one of the finest cruising destinations in the world.</p>
                    <p><img alt="" src="/contentimages/arrow-red.png" />    <a href="http://www.whitsundayescape.com/" onclick="ntptEventTag('ev=PartnerLead&amp;PartnerId=whitsundayescape');" target="_blank">Find Out More</a></p>
                    <p style="text-align: right;"><a href="#top">Back To Top</a></p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-top: 3px; padding-right: 5px;">
                    <p><a href="http://www.bluemooncottages.com.au" onclick="ntptEventTag('ev=PartnerLead&amp;PartnerId=bluemooncottages');" target="_blank"><img alt="" src="/contentimages/Campaigns/campaigns-au-tourismaus-award13-page01-hl22.jpg" /></a></p>
                    </td>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-bottom: 20px;">
                    <p><span style="color: rgb(51, 51, 51); font-size: 13px;"><strong><a name="22"></a>Blue Moon Cottages, VIC<br />
                    </strong></span><span style="color: rgb(102, 102, 102); font-size: 11px;"><strong>2013 Winner for  Standard Accommodation</strong></span></p>
                    <p>Blue Moon Cottages a group of three self-contained properties (now RACV 3.5 star rated) originally built some time in the 1940's represent a rare glimpse of the holiday accommodation that sprung up at that time.</p>
                    <p><img alt="" src="/contentimages/arrow-red.png" />    <a href="http://www.bluemooncottages.com.au" onclick="ntptEventTag('ev=PartnerLead&amp;PartnerId=bluemooncottages');" target="_blank">Find Out More</a></p>
                    <p style="text-align: right;"><a href="#top">Back To Top</a></p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-top: 3px; padding-right: 5px;">
                    <p><a href="http://www.lasseters.com.au" onclick="ntptEventTag('ev=PartnerLead&amp;PartnerId=lasseters');" target="_blank"><img alt="" src="/contentimages/Campaigns/campaigns-au-tourismaus-award13-page01-hl23.jpg" /></a></p>
                    </td>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-bottom: 20px;">
                    <p><span style="color: rgb(51, 51, 51); font-size: 13px;"><strong><a name="23"></a>Lasseters Hotel, NT<br />
                    </strong></span><span style="color: rgb(102, 102, 102); font-size: 11px;"><strong>2013 Winner for Deluxe Accommodation</strong></span></p>
                    <p>Lasseters is the centre of entertainment in Alice Springs with two bars, four restaurants including Tali – our newest restaurant, as well as an international standard casino, and adjoins the Alice Springs Convention Centre. Lasseters enjoys picture-perfect surroundings beneath the stunning MacDonnell Ranges, alongside the banks of the Todd River, and beside the Alice Springs Golf Course. Guests can enjoy the beautiful heated resort pool and spa, free wifi, in-house entertainment, gymnasium and complimentary mountain bikes to explore Alice Springs. Mid-2014 sees the completion of a new commercial fitness &amp; massage treatment centre and new hotel lobby.</p>
                    <p><img alt="" src="/contentimages/arrow-red.png" />    <a href="http://www.lasseters.com.au" onclick="ntptEventTag('ev=PartnerLead&amp;PartnerId=lasseters');" target="_blank">Find Out More</a></p>
                    <p style="text-align: right;"><a href="#top">Back To Top</a></p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-top: 3px; padding-right: 5px;">
                    <p><a href="http://www.emporiumhotel.com.au" onclick="ntptEventTag('ev=PartnerLead&amp;PartnerId=emporiumhotel');" target="_blank"><img alt="" src="/contentimages/Campaigns/campaigns-au-tourismaus-award13-page01-hl24.jpg" /></a></p>
                    </td>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-bottom: 20px;">
                    <p><span style="color: rgb(51, 51, 51); font-size: 13px;"><strong><a name="24"></a>Emporium Hotel, QLD<br />
                    </strong></span><span style="color: rgb(102, 102, 102); font-size: 11px;"><strong>2013 Winner for  Luxury Accommodation</strong></span></p>
                    <p>The Emporium Hotel is a luxury boutique property, recognised for delivering enchanting hospitality that is beautifully complemented with exquisite design and opulent finishes.Located in Fortitude Valley, Brisbane, this independently owned and managed Hotel has a proven track record of offering outstanding service and facilities, while also introducing innovative packages and touches that have raised the bar in the luxury hotel market.Featuring 102 luxury Guest Suites, Cocktail Bar, Belle &Atilde;poque Patisserie, Function Centre and Roof Top Terrace, the team of hospitality professionals at Emporium Hotel are constantly tuned to deliver on the brand promise of creating ˜exquisite stays".</p>
                    <p><img alt="" src="/contentimages/arrow-red.png" />    <a href="http://www.emporiumhotel.com.au" onclick="ntptEventTag('ev=PartnerLead&amp;PartnerId=emporiumhotel');" target="_blank">Find Out More</a></p>
                    <p style="text-align: right;"><a href="#top">Back To Top</a></p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-top: 3px; padding-right: 5px;">
                    <p><a href="http://www.rodneyfox.com.au" onclick="ntptEventTag('ev=PartnerLead&amp;PartnerId=rodneyfox');" target="_blank"><img alt="" src="/contentimages/Campaigns/campaigns-au-tourismaus-award13-page01-hl25.jpg" /></a></p>
                    </td>
                    <td valign="top">
                    <p><span style="color: rgb(51, 51, 51); font-size: 13px;"><strong><a name="25"></a>Rodney Fox Shark Expeditions - Great White Adventure, SA<br />
                    </strong></span><span style="color: rgb(102, 102, 102); font-size: 11px;"><strong>2013 Winner for  New Tourism Development</strong></span></p>
                    <p>The Great White Adventure is new shorter product offering guests a 2 night great white shark experience. This new product offers great white viewing, surface cage diving, Australian sea lion swims, research talks and many other elements of our longer great white expeditions. This was first piloted in the summer of 2012 and based on the initial interest is now in full product development and being strongly marketed internationally to time poor adventurers.</p>
                    <p><img alt="" src="/contentimages/arrow-red.png" />    <a href="http://www.rodneyfox.com.au" onclick="ntptEventTag('ev=PartnerLead&amp;PartnerId=rodneyfox');" target="_blank">Find Out More</a></p>
                    <p style="text-align: right;"><a href="#top">Back To Top</a></p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-top: 3px; padding-right: 5px;">
                    <p><a href="http://www.pennicottjourneys.com.au/" onclick="ntptEventTag('ev=PartnerLead&amp;PartnerId=pennicottjourneys');" target="_blank"><img alt="" src="/contentimages/Campaigns/campaigns-au-tourismaus-award13-page01-hl26.jpg" /></a></p>
                    </td>
                    <td valign="top">
                    <p><span style="color: rgb(51, 51, 51); font-size: 13px;"><strong><a name="26"></a>Pennicott Wilderness Journeys, TAS<br />
                    </strong></span><span style="color: rgb(102, 102, 102); font-size: 11px;"><strong>2013 Winner for  Qantas Award for Excellence in Sustainable Tourism</strong></span></p>
                    <p>Pennicott Wilderness Journeys is dedicated to operating in harmony with the environment and the local community. The business employs and trains local staff, and purchases goods and services from local suppliers wherever possible.Pennicott Wilderness Journeys is 100% Carbon Offset and an Advanced Ecotourism Certified operator. The business is assessed by EarthCheck and exceeds world's best practice standards for efficient water, fuel and energy use.</p>
                    <p><img alt="" src="/contentimages/arrow-red.png" />    <a href="http://www.pennicottjourneys.com.au" onclick="ntptEventTag('ev=PartnerLead&amp;PartnerId=pennicottjourneys');" target="_blank">Find Out More</a></p>
                    <p style="text-align: right;"><a href="#top">Back To Top</a></p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-top: 3px; padding-right: 5px;">
                    <p><a href="http://www.swan.wa.gov.au" onclick="ntptEventTag('ev=PartnerLead&amp;PartnerId=swan');" target="_blank"><img alt="" src="/contentimages/Campaigns/campaigns-au-tourismaus-award13-page01-hl27.jpg" /></a></p>
                    </td>
                    <td valign="top">
                    <p><span style="color: rgb(51, 51, 51); font-size: 13px;"><strong><a name="27"></a>City of Swan, WA<br />
                    </strong></span><span style="color: rgb(102, 102, 102); font-size: 11px;"><strong>2013 Winner for  Local Government </strong></span></p>
                    <p>The City of Swan has established a well-defined and strategic role that uniquely integrates visitor servicing with regional marketing, product development and interpretive infrastructure.Our innovative 'Adding Value Through Tourism' program has resulted in the delivery of high quality tourism infrastructure, services and facilities including management of the award-winning Swan Valley Food and Wine Trail and T-QUAL accredited Swan Valley Visitor Centre.The City of Swan's activities, implemented in partnership with local, state and federal tourism agencies, have significantly contributed to the growth of the Swan Valley - today Western Australia's most visited wine region, servicing about 2.1 million visitors per annum - and set benchmarks for local government involvement in tourism in Western Australia.</p>
                    <p><img alt="" src="/contentimages/arrow-red.png" />    <a href="http://www.swan.wa.gov.au" onclick="ntptEventTag('ev=PartnerLead&amp;PartnerId=swan');" target="_blank">Find Out More</a></p>
                    <p style="text-align: right;"><a href="#top">Back To Top</a></p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
            </tbody>
        </table>
    ]]></txt_Information>

				</TopCategoryHighlights>
			</con_Body>
			<con_RHSModules>
				<AtaGlance isTemplate="1">
					<hdl_Title><![CDATA[Award Winners]]></hdl_Title>
					<img_Map><![CDATA[]]>
					</img_Map>
					<stf_Title1><![CDATA[]]>
					</stf_Title1>
					<stf_Title2><![CDATA[]]>
					</stf_Title2>
					<stf_Title3><![CDATA[]]>
					</stf_Title3>
					<stf_Title4><![CDATA[]]>
					</stf_Title4>
					<stf_Title5><![CDATA[]]>
					</stf_Title5>
					<txt_Description1><![CDATA[
        <table width="100%">
            <tbody>
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-top: 4px; padding-right: 10px;">
                    <p><img alt="" src="/contentimages/arrow-green.png" /></p>
                    </td>
                    <td valign="top">
                    <p><a href="#1">Taronga Zoo</a></p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-top: 4px; padding-right: 10px;">
                    <p><img alt="" src="/contentimages/arrow-green.png" /></p>
                    </td>
                    <td valign="top">
                    <p><a href="#2">Taronga Western Plains Zoo</a></p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-top: 4px; padding-right: 10px;">
                    <p><img alt="" src="/contentimages/arrow-green.png" /></p>
                    </td>
                    <td valign="top">
                    <p><a href="#3">Melbourne Cup Carnival</a></p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-top: 4px; padding-right: 10px;">
                    <p><img alt="" src="/contentimages/arrow-green.png" /></p>
                    </td>
                    <td valign="top">
                    <p><a href="#4">Kings Park Festival</a></p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-top: 4px; padding-right: 10px;">
                    <p><img alt="" src="/contentimages/arrow-green.png" /></p>
                    </td>
                    <td valign="top">
                    <p><a href="#5">Bruny Island Cruises</a></p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-top: 4px; padding-right: 10px;">
                    <p><img alt="" src="/contentimages/arrow-green.png" /></p>
                    </td>
                    <td valign="top">
                    <p><a href="#6">Jenolan Caves: Written In Stone</a></p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-top: 4px; padding-right: 10px;">
                    <p><img alt="" src="/contentimages/arrow-green.png" /></p>
                    </td>
                    <td valign="top">
                    <p><a href="#7">Tri State Safaris/Mutawintji Eco Tours</a></p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-top: 4px; padding-right: 10px;">
                    <p><img alt="" src="/contentimages/arrow-green.png" /></p>
                    </td>
                    <td valign="top">
                    <p><a href="#8">DIY Tourguide Australia</a></p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-top: 4px; padding-right: 10px;">
                    <p><img alt="" src="/contentimages/arrow-green.png" /></p>
                    </td>
                    <td valign="top">
                    <p><a href="#9">Frankston Visitor Information Centre</a></p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-top: 4px; padding-right: 10px;">
                    <p><img alt="" src="/contentimages/arrow-green.png" /></p>
                    </td>
                    <td valign="top">
                    <p><a href="#10">Uluru Meeting Place</a></p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-top: 4px; padding-right: 10px;">
                    <p><img alt="" src="/contentimages/arrow-green.png" /></p>
                    </td>
                    <td valign="top">
                    <p><a href="#11">Spirit of Tasmania</a></p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-top: 4px; padding-right: 10px;">
                    <p><img alt="" src="/contentimages/arrow-green.png" /></p>
                    </td>
                    <td valign="top">
                    <p><a href="#12">Tour Barossa</a></p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-top: 4px; padding-right: 10px;">
                    <p><img alt="" src="/contentimages/arrow-green.png" /></p>
                    </td>
                    <td valign="top">
                    <p><a href="#13">Life's An Adventure</a></p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-top: 4px; padding-right: 10px;">
                    <p><img alt="" src="/contentimages/arrow-green.png" /></p>
                    </td>
                    <td valign="top">
                    <p><a href="#14">The Human Brochure</a></p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-top: 4px; padding-right: 10px;">
                    <p><img alt="" src="/contentimages/arrow-green.png" /></p>
                    </td>
                    <td valign="top">
                    <p><a href="#15">Blue Mountains International Hotel Management School</a></p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-top: 4px; padding-right: 10px;">
                    <p><img alt="" src="/contentimages/arrow-green.png" /></p>
                    </td>
                    <td valign="top">
                    <p><a href="#16">The Corner Restaurant</a></p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-top: 4px; padding-right: 10px;">
                    <p><img alt="" src="/contentimages/arrow-green.png" /></p>
                    </td>
                    <td valign="top">
                    <p><a href="#17">Pindarie Cellar Door</a></p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-top: 4px; padding-right: 10px;">
                    <p><img alt="" src="/contentimages/arrow-green.png" /></p>
                    </td>
                    <td valign="top">
                    <p><a href="#18">Cairns Coconut Holiday Resort</a></p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-top: 4px; padding-right: 10px;">
                    <p><img alt="" src="/contentimages/arrow-green.png" /></p>
                    </td>
                    <td valign="top">
                    <p><a href="#19">Sydney Harbour YHA</a></p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-top: 4px; padding-right: 10px;">
                    <p><img alt="" src="/contentimages/arrow-green.png" /></p>
                    </td>
                    <td valign="top">
                    <p><a href="#20">Narrows Escape Rainforest Retreat</a></p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-top: 4px; padding-right: 10px;">
                    <p><img alt="" src="/contentimages/arrow-green.png" /></p>
                    </td>
                    <td valign="top">
                    <p><a href="#21">Whitsunday Escape</a></p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-top: 4px; padding-right: 10px;">
                    <p><img alt="" src="/contentimages/arrow-green.png" /></p>
                    </td>
                    <td valign="top">
                    <p><a href="#22">Blue Moon Cottages</a></p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-top: 4px; padding-right: 10px;">
                    <p><img alt="" src="/contentimages/arrow-green.png" /></p>
                    </td>
                    <td valign="top">
                    <p><a href="#23">Lasseters Hotel</a></p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-top: 4px; padding-right: 10px;">
                    <p><img alt="" src="/contentimages/arrow-green.png" /></p>
                    </td>
                    <td valign="top">
                    <p><a href="#24">Emporium Hotel</a></p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-top: 4px; padding-right: 10px;">
                    <p><img alt="" src="/contentimages/arrow-green.png" /></p>
                    </td>
                    <td valign="top">
                    <p><a href="#25">Rodney Fox Shark Expeditions - Great White Adventure</a></p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-top: 4px; padding-right: 10px;">
                    <p><img alt="" src="/contentimages/arrow-green.png" /></p>
                    </td>
                    <td valign="top">
                    <p><a href="#26">Pennicott Wilderness Journeys</a></p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td valign="top" style="padding-top: 4px; padding-right: 10px;">
                    <p><img alt="" src="/contentimages/arrow-green.png" /></p>
                    </td>
                    <td valign="top">
                    <p><a href="#27">City of Swan</a></p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
            </tbody>
        </table>
        <br />
    ]]></txt_Description1>
					<txt_Description2><![CDATA[]]>
					</txt_Description2>
					<txt_Description3><![CDATA[]]>
					</txt_Description3>
					<txt_Description4><![CDATA[]]>
					</txt_Description4>
					<txt_Description5><![CDATA[]]>
					</txt_Description5>
				</AtaGlance>
			</con_RHSModules>
			<con_Category></con_Category>
			<lst_Subpages>
			</lst_Subpages>
		</StandardCampaignLayout>
	</con_Body>
	<lst_Subpages>
	</lst_Subpages>
</ConsumerBaseFoundation>