<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<ConsumerBaseFoundation pageID="15225"
	isTemplate="1">
	<breadcrumb>
		<element level="1">
			<headline><![CDATA[Homepage ]]></headline>
			<href><![CDATA[/index.xml]]></href>
		</element>
		<element level="2">
			<headline><![CDATA[Tools and Campaigns]]></headline>
			<href><![CDATA[/tools-campaigns.xml]]></href>
		</element>
		<element level="4">
			<headline><![CDATA[IN]]></headline>
			<href><![CDATA[/15223.ignore]]></href>
		</element>
		<element level="5">
			<headline><![CDATA[Traveller Testimonials]]></headline>
			<href><![CDATA[/traveller-testimonials-in.xml]]></href>
		</element>

	</breadcrumb>
	<img_background><![CDATA[/contentimages/Campaigns/campaigns-sydney2.jpg]]></img_background>
	<hdl_Title><![CDATA[Traveller Testimonials]]></hdl_Title>
	<img_Banner><![CDATA[]]>
	</img_Banner>
	<img_SearchThumbnail><![CDATA[/thumbnails/campaigns-sydney2-search.jpg]]></img_SearchThumbnail>
	<img_Thumbnail><![CDATA[/contentimages/about-key-facts-weather-sydney-th.jpg]]></img_Thumbnail>
	<opt_HideInBreadcrumbs><![CDATA[Show]]></opt_HideInBreadcrumbs>
	<opt_HidePage><![CDATA[no]]></opt_HidePage>
	<opt_hideTitle><![CDATA[0]]></opt_hideTitle>
	<opt_hide_in_sitemap><![CDATA[no]]></opt_hide_in_sitemap>
	<opt_IncludeVideo><![CDATA[0]]></opt_IncludeVideo>
	<opt_isHubPage><![CDATA[0]]></opt_isHubPage>
	<opt_isNewWindow><![CDATA[_self]]></opt_isNewWindow>
	<opt_PageLayout><![CDATA[]]>
	</opt_PageLayout>
	<opt_PartnerLead><![CDATA[no]]></opt_PartnerLead>
	<stf_description><![CDATA[]]>
	</stf_description>
	<stf_ExcludedCountries><![CDATA[]]>
	</stf_ExcludedCountries>
	<stf_hideInXmlSitemap><![CDATA[]]>
	</stf_hideInXmlSitemap>
	<stf_ImageLocation><![CDATA[]]>
	</stf_ImageLocation>
	<stf_intro_title><![CDATA[]]>
	</stf_intro_title>
	<stf_IsExternalSiteArticle><![CDATA[]]>
	</stf_IsExternalSiteArticle>
	<stf_IsMobile><![CDATA[n]]></stf_IsMobile>
	<stf_keywords><![CDATA[]]>
	</stf_keywords>
	<stf_LinkLearnMore><![CDATA[Learn More]]></stf_LinkLearnMore>
	<stf_NavigationTagLine><![CDATA[]]>
	</stf_NavigationTagLine>
	<stf_PageHeading><![CDATA[]]>
	</stf_PageHeading>
	<stf_TargetedCountries><![CDATA[]]>
	</stf_TargetedCountries>
	<stf_TrackingTitle><![CDATA[]]>
	</stf_TrackingTitle>
	<TA_Title><![CDATA[Traveller Testimonials: Read what travellers have to say about Australia]]></TA_Title>
	<txt_Intro>
        <![CDATA[]]>
	</txt_Intro>
	<txt_MobileContentOnly>
        <![CDATA[]]>
	</txt_MobileContentOnly>
	<txt_SpotlightTag>
        <![CDATA[]]>
	</txt_SpotlightTag>
	<txt_Teaser>
        <![CDATA[]]>
	</txt_Teaser>
	<con_Body>
		<SubPageLayout isTemplate="1">
			<con_Banner>
				<ImageBanner isTemplate="1">
					<img_Banner><![CDATA[/contentimages/Campaigns/campaigns-in-testimonials-hero.jpg]]></img_Banner>
					<stf_BackgroundImageAlt><![CDATA[Background image Alt text]]></stf_BackgroundImageAlt>
					<stf_TargetedCountries><![CDATA[]]>
					</stf_TargetedCountries>
				</ImageBanner>
			</con_Banner>
			<con_RHSModules>
				<AtaGlance isTemplate="1">
					<hdl_Title><![CDATA[Traveller Testimonials]]></hdl_Title>
					<img_Map><![CDATA[]]>
					</img_Map>
					<stf_Title1><![CDATA[]]>
					</stf_Title1>
					<stf_Title2><![CDATA[]]>
					</stf_Title2>
					<stf_Title3><![CDATA[]]>
					</stf_Title3>
					<stf_Title4><![CDATA[]]>
					</stf_Title4>
					<stf_Title5><![CDATA[]]>
					</stf_Title5>
					<txt_Description1><![CDATA[
        <table border="0" cellspacing="0" cellpadding="0" width="100%">
            <tbody>
                <tr>
                    <td style="padding-right: 10px;">
                    <p><img alt="" src="http://www.australia.com/contentimages/arrow.gif" /></p>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                    <p><a href="/traveller-testimonials-more-in.xml" target="_self"><strong>Read more testimonials</strong></a></p>
                    </td>
                </tr>
            </tbody>
        </table>
        <br />
    ]]></txt_Description1>
					<txt_Description2><![CDATA[]]>
					</txt_Description2>
					<txt_Description3><![CDATA[]]>
					</txt_Description3>
					<txt_Description4><![CDATA[]]>
					</txt_Description4>
					<txt_Description5><![CDATA[]]>
					</txt_Description5>
				</AtaGlance>
			</con_RHSModules>
			<con_Video>

			</con_Video>
			<con_Body>
				<TopCategoryHighlights isTemplate="1">
					<stf_Heading><![CDATA[Read what travellers have to say about Australia]]></stf_Heading>
					<stf_InformationTitle><![CDATA[]]>
					</stf_InformationTitle>
					<txt_Information><![CDATA[
        <a name="piya"></a><br />
    ]]></txt_Information>
					<con_CenterContent>
						<CenterContent isTemplate="1">
							<hdl_Title><![CDATA[Sujata Modi]]></hdl_Title>
							<img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/Campaigns/campaigns-in-testimonials-sujata-modi.jpg" alt="Sujata Modi">]]></img_MainImage>
							<stf_Caption><![CDATA[Sujata Modi]]></stf_Caption>
							<anc_link><![CDATA[]]>
							</anc_link>
							<txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[
        What has etched this Australia holiday in my memory forever is the sheer exoticism of this virgin place, with ADELAIDE being the perfect example of a contemporary yet classic Aussie city with fairy tale churches, homes, hills and trams at one end and then at the other is its hustle-bustle of young energy and spanking newness of cafes and restaurants ,the shopper's haven, the brightly lit squares, streets and fountains lending glamour to its nightlife. One of the great wine growing regions, the BAROSSA VALLEY with its miles and miles of stunning vineyards, Italianats, Chateaux, Boutique Wineries offering the best 'Shiraz' and 'Sauvignon Blanc', was a heady mix!
        <p>But then KANGAROO ISLAND simply blows you away! With its sheer virgin seascapes, sparcely populated and unpolluted expanses of land, mammoth natural rock formations and animal exoticism, it is a land yet untouched and untarnished. But I had gone for the Kangaroos and Koalas! Now instead of just watching them sit on my bed's headrest in their stuffed creations, I got to really feel, touch, smell, hold, cuddle the Real Ones! Simply awesome! That wasn't all, as I was witness to a Seal Fight between 2 seals over a female at Seal Bay, which I captured on tape. Wallabies ate out of our hands, we fed hoards of Pelicans with fish in the cold of the evening then watched little penguins cross the sands in the dark of the night ! But the trip wouldn't have been the same without 'Dave' our guide, a quintessential Australian, hardy, casual, friendly and extremely well informed, who became best friend to us and bonded our small yet diverse group, as he masterfully educated us about the scrub land or Yacca Flats, introduced us to the Whiting Fish or helped us up the wet, slippery granite boulders against the tremendous velocity of the icy wind! Such powerful erosion has left in its wake remarkably unusually shaped rocks, thus the name REMARKABLE ROCKS. Then another spectacular natural arch formed by the elements is The Admiral's Arch, under which we stood small and shivering against the sheer power of nature! </p>
        <p>What I came back home with is not just wonderful memories on my camera, but with real life friendships I made with all in our group, Dave, and all the warm and hospitable people I met throughout! Another misconception down and under! Aussies make great friends!</p>
        <p style="text-align: right;"><span style="font-size: 9px;"><a href="#top">Back To Top</a></span></p>
        <a name="piya"></a>
    ]]>
							</txt_Information>
						</CenterContent>
						<CenterContent isTemplate="1">
							<hdl_Title><![CDATA[Piya Mukherjee]]></hdl_Title>
							<img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/Campaigns/campaigns-in-testimonials-piya-mukherjee.jpg" alt="Piya Mukherjee">]]></img_MainImage>
							<stf_Caption><![CDATA[Piya Mukherjee]]></stf_Caption>
							<anc_link><![CDATA[]]>
							</anc_link>
							<txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[
        Our overall experience of Australia was superb - there is stunning natural beauty and the people are refreshingly forthright and quite friendly. We enjoyed some literally out-of-the-world experiences, like hot air ballooning over the Yarra Valley vineyards. This was one memorable holiday!
        <p style="text-align: right;"><span style="font-size: 9px;"><a href="#top">Back To Top</a></span></p>
        <a name="naeem"></a>
    ]]>
							</txt_Information>
						</CenterContent>
						<CenterContent isTemplate="1">
							<hdl_Title><![CDATA[Naeem Sayed]]></hdl_Title>
							<img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/Campaigns/campaigns-in-testimonials-naeem-sayed.jpg" alt="Naeem Sayed">]]></img_MainImage>
							<stf_Caption><![CDATA[Naeem Sayed]]></stf_Caption>
							<anc_link><![CDATA[]]>
							</anc_link>
							<txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[
        If you have wanted to visit a city with a medley of wild bush-lands, great dining experience and romantic theatre experience, Sydney is really the place to be in. Situated on the eastern coast and washed by the Tasman Sea, Sydney offers beautiful landscape. This Australian city unlike any other is very versatile and allows you to choose from a wide array of a hundred different moods, all the things you've ever wanted to see.
        <p>As if Sydney weren't enough to take out breath away, Gold Coast was prying on us. From the aircraft itself, we could see the delicate green coastline of Gold Coast bordered by the blue sea. This city also enjoys decorations of many theme parks. Go fishing by the coast and devour on the delicacies of the sea. Watch your loved one enjoy a sunset by the sea as you revel in a mouthful of the great Australian wine.</p>
        <p style="text-align: right;"><span style="font-size: 9px;"><a href="#top">Back To Top</a></span></p>
        <a name="himanshi"></a>
    ]]>
							</txt_Information>
						</CenterContent>
						<CenterContent isTemplate="1">
							<hdl_Title><![CDATA[Himanshi Munshaw]]></hdl_Title>
							<img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/Campaigns/campaigns-in-testimonials-himanshi-munshaw.jpg" alt="Himanshi Munshaw">]]></img_MainImage>
							<stf_Caption><![CDATA[Himanshi Munshaw]]></stf_Caption>
							<anc_link><![CDATA[]]>
							</anc_link>
							<txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[
        I Love Australia, the 1st time I travelled there it was just plain and simple fun! The reef and rainforest of cairns and theme parks and beaches of Gold coast. Sydney with all its icons and Melbourne...Ahh... that's a city you fall in love with.... walking through the streets with all the caf&eacute;s and restaurants, and evening by the yarra... But by far my favourite place is Ayers Rock or Uluru... it brings to you a feeling of peace and thankfulness... Truly a holy place.
        <p style="text-align: right;"><span style="font-size: 9px;"><a href="#top">Back To Top</a></span></p>
        <a name="amod"></a>
    ]]>
							</txt_Information>
						</CenterContent>
						<CenterContent isTemplate="1">
							<hdl_Title><![CDATA[Amod Thatte]]></hdl_Title>
							<img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/Campaigns/campaigns-in-testimonials-amod-thatte.jpg" alt="Amod Thatte">]]></img_MainImage>
							<stf_Caption><![CDATA[Amod Thatte]]></stf_Caption>
							<anc_link><![CDATA[]]>
							</anc_link>
							<txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[
        Australia is a destination for all ages. Here kids can enjoy theme parks and beaches, honeymooners can develop a strong bonding doing a self drive package exploring the unknown regions while seniors can enjoy some of the most diverse experiences from the Sydney bridge climb, visit to the Opera House and seeing the Mecca of cricket down under the MCG – it's all there is Australia. The local Australian is a fun loving happy go lucky chap. Their informal attitude makes one feel at home while interacting with them.
        <p style="text-align: right;"><span style="font-size: 9px;"><a href="#top">Back To Top</a></span></p>
        <a name="charukesi"></a>
    ]]>
							</txt_Information>
						</CenterContent>
						<CenterContent isTemplate="1">
							<hdl_Title><![CDATA[Charukesi Ramadurai]]></hdl_Title>
							<img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/Campaigns/campaigns-in-testimonials-charukesi-ramadurai.jpg" alt="Charukesi Ramadurai">]]></img_MainImage>
							<stf_Caption><![CDATA[Charukesi Ramadurai]]></stf_Caption>
							<anc_link><![CDATA[]]>
							</anc_link>
							<txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[
        Australia has always been a dream destination and in my recent trip to Victoria and South Australia, I saw that I was fully justified. The country is as beautiful as I had always expected it to be. And the people even friendlier than I expected! If Melbourne worked its quiet charm on me with its big city vibe, Kangaroo Island's natural wonders blew me away. In Melbourne, I particularly enjoyed the inner city walk (Lanes and Arcades Walking Tour) which gave me a glimpse into the heart of the city. And in KI, Southern Ocean Lodge's spectacular setting and warm personalized service has made it one of the best places I have ever stayed in.
        <p>Tourism Australia did a great job planning my visit to make sure that I got the maximum out of my few days in the country. Thank you, team Australia!</p>
        <p style="text-align: right;"><span style="font-size: 9px;"><a href="#top">Back To Top</a></span></p>
        <a name="riaan"></a>
    ]]>
							</txt_Information>
						</CenterContent>
						<CenterContent isTemplate="1">
							<hdl_Title><![CDATA[Riaan George]]></hdl_Title>
							<img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/Campaigns/campaigns-in-testimonials-rian-george.jpg" alt="Riaan George">]]></img_MainImage>
							<stf_Caption><![CDATA[Riaan George]]></stf_Caption>
							<anc_link><![CDATA[]]>
							</anc_link>
							<txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[
        It would be absolutely unfair to describe my Australian experience in a few lines but I'l give it my best shot. Australia truly is one of the most beautiful country's in the world. Never ever have I seen such stunning diversity in landscapes, such quality in food and such excellence in wine, as I have seen in Australia. Even the streetside cafes in Sydney make their cappuccinos with love and passion. Being a hardcore city dweller, it was in Australia that I learnt to fall in love with the great outdoors, appreciate trees, spot flowers in the wild, talk about kangaroos, look for koalas in the gum trees and have picnics amidst the lush greenery. It was in Australia, and not in Europe, that I learnt to enjoy every bite of my salad, sip my wine slowly and take on life slowly. Moreover, the people were absolutely wonderful to me. Every Aussie that I met seemed genuinely happy to welcome me to their majestic country and went out of their way to make me feel comfortable. It is not often that a visitor feels that.
        <p>Australia is, in my opinion, one of the most tourist friendly countries in the world and an absolute must-visit. Believe me, you won't be disappointed.</p>
        <p style="text-align: right;"><span style="font-size: 9px;"><a href="#top">Back To Top</a></span></p>
        <a name="susheela"></a>
    ]]>
							</txt_Information>
						</CenterContent>
						<CenterContent isTemplate="1">
							<hdl_Title><![CDATA[Susheela Nair]]></hdl_Title>
							<img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/Campaigns/campaigns-in-testimonials-susheela-nair.jpg" alt="Susheela Nair">]]></img_MainImage>
							<stf_Caption><![CDATA[Susheela Nair]]></stf_Caption>
							<anc_link><![CDATA[]]>
							</anc_link>
							<txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[
        The highlight of my trip to Australia was the visit to Kangaroo Island. I wish I were shipwrecked at Kangaroo Island for a week so that I could spend more time traversing leisurely across the length and breadth of the island capturing wonderful sights. One can spend endless hours gaping in wonder at the Remarkable Rocks and Admirals Arch, indulge in koala spotting, watch the sea lions basking on snow white beaches and the kangaroos hopping around nonchalantly.
        <p>The Sydney Bridge Climb is equally fascinating! It was not as daunting as I anticipated. I was bowled over by the care, professionalism, attention to safety and the cheery commentary of the climb leader. What make the climb memorable are the incredible views of the Sydney CBD, Opera House and Sydney Harbour from the top of the icon.</p>
        <p style="text-align: right;"><span style="font-size: 9px;"><a href="#top">Back To Top</a></span></p>
        <a name="rishad"></a>
    ]]>
							</txt_Information>
						</CenterContent>
						<CenterContent isTemplate="1">
							<hdl_Title><![CDATA[Rishad Saam Mehta]]></hdl_Title>
							<img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/Campaigns/campaigns-in-testimonials-rishad-saam-mehta.jpg" alt="Rishad Saam Mehta">]]></img_MainImage>
							<stf_Caption><![CDATA[Rishad Saam Mehta]]></stf_Caption>
							<anc_link><![CDATA[]]>
							</anc_link>
							<txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[
        Australia keeps drawing me back. Not because it's such a huge country and there is always stuff to see - that is the natural reason to go - but because it holds promise of adventure, good food and drink, superb driving roads, charming cities and a rollicking party scene. Australia is like this bubble at the bottom of the world within which life is unimaginably good and I keep wanting to jump into it every few years.
        <p style="text-align: right;"><span style="font-size: 9px;"><a href="#top">Back To Top</a></span></p>
        <a name="baradwaj"></a>
    ]]>
							</txt_Information>
						</CenterContent>
						<CenterContent isTemplate="1">
							<hdl_Title><![CDATA[Baradwaj Rangan]]></hdl_Title>
							<img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/Campaigns/campaigns-in-testimonials-baradwaj-rangan.jpg" alt="Baradwaj Rangan">]]></img_MainImage>
							<stf_Caption><![CDATA[Baradwaj Rangan]]></stf_Caption>
							<anc_link><![CDATA[]]>
							</anc_link>
							<txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[
        <a name="baradwaj"></a>Australia is filled with so much extraordinary scenery that a single trip, like mine, just isn't enough. But even in a couple of weeks, there was so much to see -- hidden beaches, colonies of seals, islands filled with native wildlife... The man-made attractions, like the Sydney bridge climb, are no less wonderful.
        <p style="text-align: right;"><span style="font-size: 9px;"><a href="#top">Back To Top</a></span></p>
        <a name="kiran"></a>
    ]]>
							</txt_Information>
						</CenterContent>
						<CenterContent isTemplate="1">
							<hdl_Title><![CDATA[Kiran Mehta]]></hdl_Title>
							<img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/Campaigns/campaigns-in-testimonials-kiran-mehta.jpg" alt="Kiran Mehta">]]></img_MainImage>
							<stf_Caption><![CDATA[Kiran Mehta]]></stf_Caption>
							<anc_link><![CDATA[]]>
							</anc_link>
							<txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[
        <a name="kiran"></a>My first trip to Australia consisted of reluctantly jumping out of a plane 14,000 feet in the air; snorkelling in the Great Barrier Reef even though I could barely swim; rafting the river Barron where eddies can suck you in, and many other scary stunts. My friends thought I'd lost my mind, while I thought that these extreme sports had earned me bragging rights. But when I relayed my adventures to Australians I met along the way, they considered it a rite of passage!
        <p>And that's what I loved about the Australian spirit – where hair-raising feats aren't feared, but given into. After all these are the experiences that help us realise that there's more to us, and to our world, than we ever dreamed possible. And that to me is what travel is really about.</p>
        <p>Yet apart from the adrenalin-pumping adventure, there are many other memories of this continent that I formed on subsequent visits – the view of the Sydney Harbour Bridge light up by night, cuddling a koala in Brisbane, watching penguins waddle their way home on Phillip Island etc.</p>
        <p>Despite having experienced so much, having visited on extended vacations spanning months, and having travelled through various states, I realise that there's much more to Australia than I've managed to sample. And that's why I'll be back for more. Time and again.</p>
        <p style="text-align: right;"><span style="font-size: 9px;"><a href="#top">Back To Top</a></span></p>
        <a name="aarti"></a>
    ]]>
							</txt_Information>
						</CenterContent>
						<CenterContent isTemplate="1">
							<hdl_Title><![CDATA[Aarti Dua]]></hdl_Title>
							<img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/Campaigns/campaigns-in-testimonials-aarti-dua.jpg" alt="Aarti Dua">]]></img_MainImage>
							<stf_Caption><![CDATA[Aarti Dua]]></stf_Caption>
							<anc_link><![CDATA[]]>
							</anc_link>
							<txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[
        How do I describe a country that surprises travellers at every step with its never-ending treasure trove of delights? A land that's so varied that you're on a constant roller-coaster ride of discovery and surprise? Yes, my Australian sojourn was just that: A Grand Adventure. And I revelled in it all from the utterly gorgeous Kangaroo Islands, where I encountered seals and koalas and kangaroos, to the charming Phillip Island with its cute colonies of penguins, from the exhilarating Sydney Harbour Bridge Climb to the breathtakingly beautiful Great Ocean Road. I savoured walking through the quaint laneways of Melbourne and driving to the scenic Yarra valley -- and gorged on culinary delicacies at Australia's famed restaurants too. And how can I ever forget the thrill of watching cricket for the first time ever outside India - I watched not one but three matches at Adelaide and Sydney and the MCG too. Need I say any more?
        <p style="text-align: right;"><span style="font-size: 9px;"><a href="#top">Back To Top</a></span></p>
        <a name="kalyani"></a>
    ]]>
							</txt_Information>
						</CenterContent>
						<CenterContent isTemplate="1">
							<hdl_Title><![CDATA[Kalyani Prasher]]></hdl_Title>
							<img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/Campaigns/campaigns-in-testimonials-kalyani-prasher.jpg" alt="Kalyani Prasher">]]></img_MainImage>
							<stf_Caption><![CDATA[Kalyani Prasher]]></stf_Caption>
							<anc_link><![CDATA[]]>
							</anc_link>
							<txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[
        For me Australia has so far meant Melbourne, a city I love for its art, food and its relaxed vibe, and perhaps also because two of my close friends live there. On a recent work visit to Australia, however, I had the chance to see one of the most beautiful parts of the world – Kangaroo Islands. Lush greenery, wide open skies, near empty beaches, (and yes, kangaroos), this is a great place for nature lovers. I think its biggest advantage is its raw, natural setting aided by, somewhat ironically, the lack of tourists for now.
        <p style="text-align: right;"><span style="font-size: 9px;"><a href="#top">Back To Top</a></span></p>
    ]]>
							</txt_Information>
						</CenterContent>
					</con_CenterContent>
				</TopCategoryHighlights>
			</con_Body>
		</SubPageLayout>
	</con_Body>
	<lst_Subpages>
		<lst_Subpage><![CDATA[<a href="/traveller-testimonials-more-in.xml">Great Stories About Australia</a>]]></lst_Subpage>
	</lst_Subpages>
</ConsumerBaseFoundation>