<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<ConsumerBaseFoundation pageID="14081" isTemplate="1">
    <breadcrumb>
        <element level="1">
            <headline><![CDATA[Homepage ]]></headline>
            <href><![CDATA[/index.xml]]></href>
        </element>
<element level="2">
            <headline><![CDATA[Explore ]]></headline>
            <href><![CDATA[/explore.xml]]></href>
        </element>
<element level="4">
            <headline><![CDATA[Australia’s Arts Events]]></headline>
            <href><![CDATA[/explore/australian-events/art-events.xml]]></href>
        </element>

    </breadcrumb>
    <img_background><![CDATA[/contentimages/explore-events-arts-events.jpg]]></img_background>
    <hdl_Title><![CDATA[Australia’s Arts Events]]></hdl_Title>
    <img_Banner><![CDATA[]]></img_Banner>
    <img_SearchThumbnail><![CDATA[/thumbnails/explore-events-arts-events-search.jpg]]></img_SearchThumbnail>
    <img_Thumbnail><![CDATA[/contentimages/explore-events-arts-events-th.jpg]]></img_Thumbnail>
    <opt_HideInBreadcrumbs><![CDATA[Show]]></opt_HideInBreadcrumbs>
    <opt_HidePage><![CDATA[no]]></opt_HidePage>
    <opt_hideTitle><![CDATA[0]]></opt_hideTitle>
    <opt_hide_in_sitemap><![CDATA[no]]></opt_hide_in_sitemap>
    <opt_IncludeVideo><![CDATA[0]]></opt_IncludeVideo>
    <opt_isHubPage><![CDATA[0]]></opt_isHubPage>
    <opt_isNewWindow><![CDATA[_self]]></opt_isNewWindow>
    <opt_PageLayout><![CDATA[]]></opt_PageLayout>
    <opt_PartnerLead><![CDATA[no]]></opt_PartnerLead>
    <stf_description><![CDATA[Learn more about Australia's flourishing arts scene. From theatre and opera to concerts and film festivals, Australia offers art events to suit all tastes.]]></stf_description>
    <stf_ExcludedCountries><![CDATA[]]></stf_ExcludedCountries>
    <stf_hideInXmlSitemap><![CDATA[]]></stf_hideInXmlSitemap>
    <stf_ImageLocation><![CDATA[MONA FOMA, Hobart, TAS. &copy; Remi Chauvin &amp; MONA]]></stf_ImageLocation>
    <stf_intro_title><![CDATA[]]></stf_intro_title>
    <stf_IsExternalSiteArticle><![CDATA[]]></stf_IsExternalSiteArticle>
    <stf_IsMobile><![CDATA[y]]></stf_IsMobile>
    <stf_keywords><![CDATA[arts festivals australia, arts in australia, film festivals australia, australian film festivals]]></stf_keywords>
    <stf_LinkLearnMore><![CDATA[Learn More]]></stf_LinkLearnMore>
    <stf_NavigationTagLine><![CDATA[]]></stf_NavigationTagLine>
    <stf_PageHeading><![CDATA[]]></stf_PageHeading>
    <stf_TargetedCountries><![CDATA[]]></stf_TargetedCountries>
    <stf_TrackingTitle><![CDATA[]]></stf_TrackingTitle>
    <TA_Title><![CDATA[Australia’s Arts Events]]></TA_Title>
    <txt_Intro>
        <![CDATA[]]>
    </txt_Intro>
    <txt_MobileContentOnly>
        <![CDATA[]]>
    </txt_MobileContentOnly>
    <txt_SpotlightTag>
        <![CDATA[]]>
    </txt_SpotlightTag>
    <txt_Teaser>
        <![CDATA[
        Australia has a flourishing arts scene, with everything from opera to the avant-garde. 
    ]]>
    </txt_Teaser>
    <con_Body>
        <EventsLayout isTemplate="1">
    <con_Body>
        <TopCategoryHighlights isTemplate="1">
            <stf_Heading><![CDATA[Australia’s Arts Events]]></stf_Heading>
            <stf_InformationTitle><![CDATA[]]></stf_InformationTitle>
            <txt_Information><![CDATA[
        Throughout the year Australian cities present a series of major arts festivals, showcasing local and international theatre, dance, visual arts, music, food and wine. Join Sydneysiders and film lovers from around the world at the Sydney International Film Festival. Or see the Sydney Harbour lit up with opera performances and light shows. Be immersed in culture at the Perth International Arts Festival. See the latest avant-garde performers and artworks at the MONA FOMA or Melbourne and Adelaide Fringe Festivals. From the contemporary to the classical; from flowers to fringe, there is an art event to suit all styles and tastes.
    ]]></txt_Information>
            <con_CenterContent>
                <CenterContent isTemplate="1">
                    <hdl_Title><![CDATA[Melbourne Fringe Festival]]></hdl_Title>
                    <img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/explore-events-arts-events-melbourne-fringe-festival-hl.jpg" alt="Melbourne Fringe Festival">]]></img_MainImage>
                    <stf_Caption><![CDATA[Melbourne Fringe Festival]]></stf_Caption>
                    <anc_link><![CDATA[]]></anc_link>
                    <txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[
        <strong>Melbourne, Victoria <br />
        September - October</strong>
        <p>The Melbourne Fringe Festival presents the work of thousands of artists in a diverse range of contemporary art forms. The festival has been running for more than 30 years and is a highlight on the Victorian arts calendar. Recent festivals have attracted more than quarter of a million people and presented the work of more than 3000 artists in events, performances and exhibitions in venues and locations across <a href="/explore/states/vic.xml" target="_self">Victoria</a>. Victoria has long been known as ‘the state of the arts’. Visit other exhibitions at the National Gallery of Victoria, Melbourne Museum and Australian Centre for the Moving Image in Federation Square.</p>
    ]]>
                    </txt_Information>
                </CenterContent><CenterContent isTemplate="1">
                    <hdl_Title><![CDATA[Floriade]]></hdl_Title>
                    <img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/explore-events-arts-events-floriade-hl.jpg" alt="Floriade">]]></img_MainImage>
                    <stf_Caption><![CDATA[Floriade]]></stf_Caption>
                    <anc_link><![CDATA[/explore/events/floriade.xml]]></anc_link>
                    <txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[
        <strong>Australian Capital Territory <br />
        September - October</strong>
        <p>For 30 fragrant days in September and October, <a href="/explore/cities/canberra.xml" target="_self">Canberra</a> comes alive with a million spring blooms during <a href="/explore/events/floriade.xml" target="_self">Floriade</a>, Australia biggest flower festival. Incredible images are created as the flowers open their petals. Each year illustrates a different theme. It is a colourful seasonal addition to Canberra’s green parks and native gardens. Soak up the floral colour while browsing markets and gourmet stalls. Attend workshops, exhibitions and live concerts. Learn about gardening, enjoy films or follow the Floriade Trail to the galleries, monuments and attractions of the nation’s capital. Floriade welcomes more than 400,000 local, interstate and international visitors each year.</p>
    ]]>
                    </txt_Information>
                </CenterContent><CenterContent isTemplate="1">
                    <hdl_Title><![CDATA[Junction Arts Festival]]></hdl_Title>
                    <img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/explore-events-arts-events-junction-arts-festival-hl.jpg" alt="Junction Arts Festival">]]></img_MainImage>
                    <stf_Caption><![CDATA[Junction Arts Festival]]></stf_Caption>
                    <anc_link><![CDATA[]]></anc_link>
                    <txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[
        <strong>Launceston, Tasmania <br />
        August</strong>
        <p>Junction Arts Festival is an annual arts festival that fills up Launceston’s CBD with playful, contemporary art and performance that invite the audience to take part. Held over five days and nights, the festival features over 50 free unique audience experience. Events include live performance, theatre, visual and media art, literature, music and dance from leading local, national and international artists. There are events to suit all ages. The festival provides an opportunity to explore the city of <a href="/explore/cities/regional-cities/tas-launceston-devonport-burnie.xml" target="_self">Launceston</a> in new ways, bringing the city to life through its bars, cafes, parks, rooftops, sidewalks and heritage buildings.</p>
    ]]>
                    </txt_Information>
                </CenterContent><CenterContent isTemplate="1">
                    <hdl_Title><![CDATA[SALA Festival]]></hdl_Title>
                    <img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/explore-events-arts-events-sala-festival-hl.jpg" alt="SALA Festival">]]></img_MainImage>
                    <stf_Caption><![CDATA[SALA Festival]]></stf_Caption>
                    <anc_link><![CDATA[]]></anc_link>
                    <txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[
        <strong>Adelaide, South Australia <br />
        August</strong>
        <p>Over the past 15 years the SALA Festival has celebrated and promoted the diverse talents of South Australian Living Artists. Recognised as Australia's most innovative, community based visual arts festival, more than 3000 artists join in unique collaborations and exhibitions with more than 500 wineries, cafes, bars, galleries and unique and creative spaces throughout metropolitan and regional <a href="/explore/states/sa.xml" target="_self">South Australia</a>. Admission to events and venues during the SALA Festival is free, and is a not to be missed state-wide celebration of South Australia’s visual arts. Take time to explore South Australia’s nearby wine regions and other historic attractions while you’re there.</p>
    ]]>
                    </txt_Information>
                </CenterContent><CenterContent isTemplate="1">
                    <hdl_Title><![CDATA[Melbourne International Art Fair]]></hdl_Title>
                    <img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/explore-events-arts-events-melbourne-international-art-fair-hl.jpg" alt="Melbourne International Art Fair">]]></img_MainImage>
                    <stf_Caption><![CDATA[Melbourne International Art Fair]]></stf_Caption>
                    <anc_link><![CDATA[]]></anc_link>
                    <txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[
        <strong>Melbourne, Victoria <br />
        August</strong>
        <p>Melbourne Art Fair is an exhibition of leading contemporary art, presented by more than 80 selected national and international galleries. The biennial event features paintings, sculpture, photography, installation and multi-media art works from over 900 artists. There are exhibitions of contemporary art from across the Asia Pacific region; and free lectures and forums with artists and curators. The four-day event attracts around 30,000 visitors. Melbourne Art Fair offers visitors a chance to view and purchase quality artwork by some of Australia’s and the world’s well-known artists as well as view works by a new generation of exciting emerging artists.</p>
    ]]>
                    </txt_Information>
                </CenterContent><CenterContent isTemplate="1">
                    <hdl_Title><![CDATA[Adelaide Cabaret Festival]]></hdl_Title>
                    <img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/explore-events-arts-events-adelaide-cabaret-festival-hl.jpg" alt="Adelaide Cabaret Festival">]]></img_MainImage>
                    <stf_Caption><![CDATA[Adelaide Cabaret Festival]]></stf_Caption>
                    <anc_link><![CDATA[]]></anc_link>
                    <txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[
        <strong>Adelaide, South Australia <br />
        July</strong>
        <p>Adelaide Cabaret Festival is a major event in the international arts calendar. Since it started in 2001, the festival has become the most comprehensive cabaret festival in the world, earning a reputation for showcasing the best local, national and international artists in cabaret performance. Performances range from comedy, satire, contemporary, rock, pop, blues, soul, swing and gypsy jazz to the Broadway classics over the two week-long festival. Acts feature some of the world’s leading cabaret singer and songwriters and living legends. The festival features more than 30 performances staged in both intimate cabaret venues and the Adelaide Festival Centre.</p>
    ]]>
                    </txt_Information>
                </CenterContent><CenterContent isTemplate="1">
                    <hdl_Title><![CDATA[City of Perth Winter Arts Season]]></hdl_Title>
                    <img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/explore-events-arts-events-city-of-perth-winter-arts-season-hl.jpg" alt="City of Perth Winter Arts Season">]]></img_MainImage>
                    <stf_Caption><![CDATA[City of Perth Winter Arts Season]]></stf_Caption>
                    <anc_link><![CDATA[]]></anc_link>
                    <txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[
        <strong>Perth, Western Australia <br />
        June - August</strong>
        <p>Perth fills the Australian winter with colour, warmth and creative offerings from Western Australia’s leading arts organisations. The City of Perth Winter Arts Season continues to grow in numbers, diversity and international recognition. The season combines a world-class selection of events and performances including theatre, film, comedy, opera, literature, dance, visual arts, poetry, cabaret and a range of free and family events. There are more than 150 events from more than 60 participating arts organisations. Wine and dine in some of Perth’s high end restaurants and chic bars. Take the opportunity to explore Western Australia’s wine regions.</p>
    ]]>
                    </txt_Information>
                </CenterContent><CenterContent isTemplate="1">
                    <hdl_Title><![CDATA[Vivid Sydney]]></hdl_Title>
                    <img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/explore-events-arts-events-vivid-sydney-hl.jpg" alt="Vivid Sydney">]]></img_MainImage>
                    <stf_Caption><![CDATA[Vivid Sydney]]></stf_Caption>
                    <anc_link><![CDATA[/explore/events/vivid-sydney.xml]]></anc_link>
                    <txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[
        <strong>Sydney, New South Wales <br />
        June</strong>
        <p>Each year the city of <a href="/explore/cities/sydney.xml" target="_self">Sydney</a> is transformed into a spectacular canvas of light, music and ideas when <a href="/explore/events/vivid-sydney.xml" target="_self">Vivid Sydney</a> takes over the city after dark. Colouring the city with creativity and inspiration, Vivid Sydney highlights include the hugely popular illumination of the Sydney Opera House sails and performances from local and international musicians at Sydney Opera House. The Vivid Ideas Exchange features public talks and debates from leading global creative thinkers. For 18 days, creative types, corporate professionals, families and people of all generations take advantage of Sydney's mild winter weather and immerse themselves in the truly spectacular show.</p>
    ]]>
                    </txt_Information>
                </CenterContent><CenterContent isTemplate="1">
                    <hdl_Title><![CDATA[Sydney Film Festival]]></hdl_Title>
                    <img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/explore-events-arts-events-sydney-film-festival-hl.jpg" alt="Sydney Film Festival">]]></img_MainImage>
                    <stf_Caption><![CDATA[Sydney Film Festival]]></stf_Caption>
                    <anc_link><![CDATA[]]></anc_link>
                    <txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[
        <strong>Sydney, New South Wales <br />
        June</strong>
        <p>Sydney Film Festival is one of the world's longest-running film festivals, and is a major event on the NSW cultural calendar. The 12-day festival screens more than 100 feature films, documentaries, short films and animation from more than 50 countries around the world and in almost as many languages. Films are shown at venues across the city, including the State Theatre, Event Cinemas George Street, Dendy Opera Quays and the Art Gallery of NSW. The official competition is endorsed by Federation Internationale des Associations de Producteurs de Films. The Travelling Film Festival of the Sydney Film Festival visits locations around the country throughout the year.</p>
    ]]>
                    </txt_Information>
                </CenterContent><CenterContent isTemplate="1">
                    <hdl_Title><![CDATA[Melbourne Winter Masterpieces]]></hdl_Title>
                    <img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/explore-events-arts-melbourne-winter-masterpieces-hl.jpg" alt="Melbourne Winter Masterpieces">]]></img_MainImage>
                    <stf_Caption><![CDATA[Melbourne Winter Masterpieces]]></stf_Caption>
                    <anc_link><![CDATA[]]></anc_link>
                    <txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[
        <strong>Melbourne, Victoria <br />
        March - June</strong>
        <p>Melbourne Winter Masterpieces is the name for an annual series of major exhibitions during winter at Melbourne’s most renowned cultural venues. The exhibitions are sourced from the most prestigious galleries and institutions around the world and present exclusive art of the highest international standards. The event attracts high numbers of international and local visitors. Previous Melbourne Winter Masterpieces exhibitions have included works by Picasso, Dali, the European Masters, and exhibitions from the Guggenheim Collection. The exhibitions rotate every year to venues which include the National Gallery of Victoria, Melbourne Museum and Australian Centre for the Moving Image.</p>
    ]]>
                    </txt_Information>
                </CenterContent><CenterContent isTemplate="1">
                    <hdl_Title><![CDATA[Opera on Sydney Harbour]]></hdl_Title>
                    <img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/explore-events-arts-events-opera-on-the-harbour-hl.jpg" alt="Opera on Sydney Harbour">]]></img_MainImage>
                    <stf_Caption><![CDATA[Opera on Sydney Harbour]]></stf_Caption>
                    <anc_link><![CDATA[/explore/events/opera-sydney-harbour.xml]]></anc_link>
                    <txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[
        <strong>Sydney, New South Wales <br />
        March/April</strong>
        <p>Experience the grandeur of a world famous opera performed against the backdrop of stunning Sydney Harbour with spectacular views over the <a href="http://www.australia.com/campaigns/nothinglike/au/sydney-product9.htm" target="_blank">Sydney Opera House</a> and the Sydney Harbour Bridge. These annual <a href="/explore/events/opera-sydney-harbour.xml" target="_self">outdoor productions by Opera Australia</a> feature magnificent sets, beautiful costumes, dazzling lighting and some of the world’s most much-loved operas all performed on a giant shimmering stage which is purpose-built for the occasion on Sydney Harbour. Opera Australia is Australia's national opera company and Australia's largest and busiest performing arts organisation staging more than 600 opera performances per year.</p>
    ]]>
                    </txt_Information>
                </CenterContent><CenterContent isTemplate="1">
                    <hdl_Title><![CDATA[ENLIGHTEN]]></hdl_Title>
                    <img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/explore-events-arts-events-enlighten-hl.jpg" alt="ENLIGHTEN">]]></img_MainImage>
                    <stf_Caption><![CDATA[ENLIGHTEN]]></stf_Caption>
                    <anc_link><![CDATA[]]></anc_link>
                    <txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[
        <strong>Canberra, Australian Capital Territory <br />
        March</strong>
        <p>ENLIGHTEN is part of the Canberra Festival and provides a new perspective on some of Australia’s most famous attractions through late night openings. Explore after hours exhibitions at the <a href="http://www.australia.com/campaigns/nothinglike/au/canberra-product1.htm" target="_blank">National Gallery of Australia</a>; National Library of Australia and <a href="/explore/states/act/act-science-tech.xml" target="_self">Questacon</a>. Many of Canberra’s national buildings such as <a href="http://www.australia.com/campaigns/nothinglike/au/canberra-product9.htm" target="_blank">Parliament House</a> are lit up in a dazzling light show by night. There are also live performances, tours and talks and exclusive dining experiences. Many of the ENLIGHTEN experiences are small and intimate events and tickets need to be purchased in advance. There are also many free events and entertainment for the whole family.</p>
    ]]>
                    </txt_Information>
                </CenterContent><CenterContent isTemplate="1">
                    <hdl_Title><![CDATA[Adelaide Fringe]]></hdl_Title>
                    <img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/explore-events-arts-events-adelaide-fringe-hl.jpg" alt="Adelaide Fringe">]]></img_MainImage>
                    <stf_Caption><![CDATA[Adelaide Fringe]]></stf_Caption>
                    <anc_link><![CDATA[]]></anc_link>
                    <txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[
        <strong>Adelaide, South Australia <br />
        March</strong>
        <p>Adelaide Fringe is an annual open-access arts festival run over four weeks in <a href="/explore/cities/adelaide.xml" target="_self">Adelaide</a> during February and March. The open nature of Adelaide Fringe means that anyone with a show, exhibition or cultural event is able to register and be part of Australia’s largest arts event. The result is one of the most diverse arts festivals in the world, renowned for fresh ideas, spontaneity and fun. More the 4000 artists from around Australia and the world participate in more than 900 events from cabaret, comedy, circus, dance, film, theatre and music to visual art and design.</p>
    ]]>
                    </txt_Information>
                </CenterContent><CenterContent isTemplate="1">
                    <hdl_Title><![CDATA[Perth International Arts Festival]]></hdl_Title>
                    <img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/explore-events-arts-events-perth-international-arts-festival-hl.jpg" alt="Perth International Arts Festival">]]></img_MainImage>
                    <stf_Caption><![CDATA[Perth International Arts Festival]]></stf_Caption>
                    <anc_link><![CDATA[]]></anc_link>
                    <txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[
        <strong>Perth, Western Australia <br />
        February</strong>
        <p>Have the quintessential <a href="/explore/cities/perth.xml" target="_self">Perth</a> summer experience at the Perth International Arts Festival. The festival teams Australia’s top artistic talents with big-name international artists at venues across the city. See cutting-edge plays and contemporary dance, dramatic classics and classical ballet. Listen to symphonies or see bands in the late-night festival bar. Attend artists’ talks and view a rich spectrum of visual arts in indoor and outdoor galleries. Watch films under the stars or indulge your love of writing, storytelling and ideas at the Perth Writers Festival. The week-long program features more than 100 literary events, including a dedicated day for children.</p>
    ]]>
                    </txt_Information>
                </CenterContent><CenterContent isTemplate="1">
                    <hdl_Title><![CDATA[MONA FOMA]]></hdl_Title>
                    <img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/explore-events-arts-events-mona-foma-hl.jpg" alt="MONA FOMA">]]></img_MainImage>
                    <stf_Caption><![CDATA[MONA FOMA]]></stf_Caption>
                    <anc_link><![CDATA[]]></anc_link>
                    <txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[
        <strong>Hobart, Tasmania <br />
        January</strong>
        <p>MONA FOMA is a boutique cultural festival that offers locals and visitors to <a href="/explore/states/tas.xml" target="_self">Tasmania</a> a chance to experience internationally renowned performers and upcoming local acts. It is presented in conjunction with the <a href="http://www.australia.com/campaigns/nothinglike/au/freycinet-product10.htm" target="_blank">Museum of Old and New Art (MONA)</a>, in the magnificent setting of Tasmania’s historic waterfront. MONA has developed a reputation for presenting the world’s most thought-provoking contemporary art. Past performers have included artists such as Nick Cave and the Bad Seeds, PJ Harvey; the Dresden Dolls and other cutting edge acts. The Moorilla winery is located upstairs from MONA and luxury accommodation is also available on the property.</p>
    ]]>
                    </txt_Information>
                </CenterContent>
            </con_CenterContent>
        </TopCategoryHighlights>
    </con_Body>
    <con_RHSModules>
        <EventsResultsRHS isTemplate="1">
    <!-- no user content -->
</EventsResultsRHS><Listing isTemplate="1">
<anc_List1><![CDATA[/explore/australian-events/major-events.xml]]></anc_List1>
<anc_MoreLink><![CDATA[]]></anc_MoreLink>
<hdl_Title><![CDATA[More Australian Ideas]]></hdl_Title>
<img_Thumbnail><![CDATA[]]></img_Thumbnail>
<med_File><![CDATA[]]></med_File>
<opt_isNewWindow><![CDATA[]]></opt_isNewWindow>
<stf_externalLink><![CDATA[]]></stf_externalLink>
<stf_ExternalLinkTitle><![CDATA[]]></stf_ExternalLinkTitle>
<stf_IsExternalSiteArticle><![CDATA[]]></stf_IsExternalSiteArticle>
<stf_LinkLearnMore><![CDATA[]]></stf_LinkLearnMore>
<txt_Teaser><![CDATA[]]></txt_Teaser>
<opt_national_landscapes_id><![CDATA[]]></opt_national_landscapes_id>
<stf_hideInXmlSitemap><![CDATA[]]></stf_hideInXmlSitemap>
<stf_TargetedCountry><![CDATA[]]></stf_TargetedCountry>
<con_Banner></con_Banner>
<con_Body></con_Body>
<con_RHSModules></con_RHSModules>
<con_Category></con_Category>
<lst_Subpages></lst_Subpages>
</Listing><PlanYourVisit isTemplate="1">
<anc_AccommodationSearch><![CDATA[/AccommodationSearch.ignore]]></anc_AccommodationSearch>
<anc_ASPSearch><![CDATA[/plan/plan-your-trip/find-travel-agent.xml]]></anc_ASPSearch>
<anc_Attraction><![CDATA[/AttractionSearchResults.ignore]]></anc_Attraction>
<anc_Destinfo><![CDATA[/DestinfoSearchResults.ignore]]></anc_Destinfo>
<anc_EventsSearch><![CDATA[/EventsSearch.xml]]></anc_EventsSearch>
<anc_GeneralSearch><![CDATA[/GeneralSearch.ignore]]></anc_GeneralSearch>
<anc_Hire><![CDATA[/Hire.ignore]]></anc_Hire>
<anc_Info><![CDATA[/InfoSearchResults.ignore]]></anc_Info>
<anc_More><![CDATA[]]></anc_More>
<anc_RestaurantSearch><![CDATA[/RestaurantSearch.ignore]]></anc_RestaurantSearch>
<anc_Tour><![CDATA[/TourSearchResults.ignore]]></anc_Tour>
<anc_Transport><![CDATA[/Transport.ignore]]></anc_Transport>
<hdl_Title><![CDATA[Plan Your Visit]]></hdl_Title>
<language><![CDATA[ENA]]></language>
<stf_Accomodation><![CDATA[]]></stf_Accomodation>
<stf_AreaFilter><![CDATA[]]></stf_AreaFilter>
<stf_Attractions><![CDATA[]]></stf_Attractions>
<stf_AussieSpecialist><![CDATA[]]></stf_AussieSpecialist>
<stf_Destinationinfo><![CDATA[]]></stf_Destinationinfo>
<stf_DomesticRegion><![CDATA[]]></stf_DomesticRegion>
<stf_Events><![CDATA[]]></stf_Events>
<stf_Hire><![CDATA[]]></stf_Hire>
<stf_Informationservices><![CDATA[]]></stf_Informationservices>
<stf_PlanYourVisitTitle><![CDATA[Plan Your Visit]]></stf_PlanYourVisitTitle>
<stf_StateFilter><![CDATA[]]></stf_StateFilter>
<stf_Tours><![CDATA[]]></stf_Tours>
<stf_Transport><![CDATA[]]></stf_Transport>
</PlanYourVisit>
    </con_RHSModules> 
</EventsLayout>
    </con_Body>
    <lst_Subpages>
    </lst_Subpages>
</ConsumerBaseFoundation>