<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<ConsumerBaseFoundation pageID="9761" isTemplate="1">
    <breadcrumb>
        <element level="1">
            <headline><![CDATA[Homepage ]]></headline>
            <href><![CDATA[/index.xml]]></href>
        </element>
<element level="2">
            <headline><![CDATA[Plan]]></headline>
            <href><![CDATA[/plan.xml]]></href>
        </element>
<element level="4">
            <headline><![CDATA[Work, Study Abroad in Australia]]></headline>
            <href><![CDATA[/plan/before-you-go/work-study-abroad.xml]]></href>
        </element>

    </breadcrumb>
    <img_background><![CDATA[/contentimages/plan-before-you-go-work-volunteer-study.jpg]]></img_background>
    <hdl_Title><![CDATA[Work, Study Abroad in Australia]]></hdl_Title>
    <img_Banner><![CDATA[]]></img_Banner>
    <img_SearchThumbnail><![CDATA[/thumbnails/plan-before-you-go-work-volunteer-study-search.jpg]]></img_SearchThumbnail>
    <img_Thumbnail><![CDATA[/contentimages/plan-before-you-go-work-volunteer-study-th.jpg]]></img_Thumbnail>
    <opt_HideInBreadcrumbs><![CDATA[Show]]></opt_HideInBreadcrumbs>
    <opt_HidePage><![CDATA[no]]></opt_HidePage>
    <opt_hideTitle><![CDATA[0]]></opt_hideTitle>
    <opt_hide_in_sitemap><![CDATA[no]]></opt_hide_in_sitemap>
    <opt_IncludeVideo><![CDATA[0]]></opt_IncludeVideo>
    <opt_isHubPage><![CDATA[0]]></opt_isHubPage>
    <opt_isNewWindow><![CDATA[_self]]></opt_isNewWindow>
    <opt_PageLayout><![CDATA[]]></opt_PageLayout>
    <opt_PartnerLead><![CDATA[no]]></opt_PartnerLead>
    <stf_description><![CDATA[Join the droves of young people who choose Australia for a gap year, career break, working holiday or overseas study.]]></stf_description>
    <stf_ExcludedCountries><![CDATA[]]></stf_ExcludedCountries>
    <stf_hideInXmlSitemap><![CDATA[]]></stf_hideInXmlSitemap>
    <stf_ImageLocation><![CDATA[Journal Canteen, Flinders Lane, Melbourne, VIC]]></stf_ImageLocation>
    <stf_intro_title><![CDATA[]]></stf_intro_title>
    <stf_IsExternalSiteArticle><![CDATA[]]></stf_IsExternalSiteArticle>
    <stf_IsMobile><![CDATA[y]]></stf_IsMobile>
    <stf_keywords><![CDATA[Australia for youth, Australia for youthful travelers, backpacking Australia, Gap Year Australia, study in Australia, youth travel Australia, working holiday australia ]]></stf_keywords>
    <stf_LinkLearnMore><![CDATA[Learn More]]></stf_LinkLearnMore>
    <stf_NavigationTagLine><![CDATA[]]></stf_NavigationTagLine>
    <stf_PageHeading><![CDATA[]]></stf_PageHeading>
    <stf_TargetedCountries><![CDATA[]]></stf_TargetedCountries>
    <stf_TrackingTitle><![CDATA[]]></stf_TrackingTitle>
    <TA_Title><![CDATA[Work, Study Abroad in Australia]]></TA_Title>
    <txt_Intro>
        <![CDATA[]]>
    </txt_Intro>
    <txt_MobileContentOnly>
        <![CDATA[]]>
    </txt_MobileContentOnly>
    <txt_SpotlightTag>
        <![CDATA[]]>
    </txt_SpotlightTag>
    <txt_Teaser>
        <![CDATA[Join the droves of young people who choose Australia for a gap year, career break, working holiday or overseas study.]]>
    </txt_Teaser>
    <con_Body>
        <SubPageLayout isTemplate="1">
    <con_Banner>
        
    </con_Banner>
    <con_RHSModules>
        
    </con_RHSModules>
    <con_Video>
        
    </con_Video>
    <con_Body>
        <TopCategoryHighlights isTemplate="1">
            <stf_Heading><![CDATA[Work, Study Abroad in Australia]]></stf_Heading>
            <stf_InformationTitle><![CDATA[]]></stf_InformationTitle>
            <txt_Information><![CDATA[
        Join the droves of young people who choose Australia to fulfil their dream of a gap year, career break, working holiday or overseas study. Australia offers endless opportunities for adventure and a warm, friendly, relaxed lifestyle.
        <p>Learn about Australia’s working holiday visas, study visas and volunteer opportunities. Find out where backpackers and travellers stay, hang out and play. </p>
        <p>Australia’s cities offer a warm, friendly and relaxed lifestyle with their festivals, hip urban enclaves and <a href="/explore/things-to-do/shopping/nat-australias-markets.xml" target="_self">markets</a>.  They form the backdrop for iconic Australian events such as the <a href="/explore/events/vic-australian-grand-prix.xml" target="_self">Grand Prix</a>, the <a href="/explore/events/syd-hobart-yacht-race.xml" target="_self">Sydney to Hobart Yacht Race</a> and the <a href="/explore/events/melbourne-cup-carnival.xml" target="_self">Melbourne Cup</a>. Australian cities come alive with the Australian passion for all manner of sport.  There’s also a host of <a href="/explore/australian-events/nat-uniquely-australian-events.xml" target="_self">uniquely Australian events</a> happening in Australia’s outback and along the coast like the Camel Cup and the Gama Festival in the Northern Territory and the open water <a href="/explore/events/qld-coolangatta-ocean-swim.xml" target="_self">Cooly Classic</a> on the Gold Coast.  </p>
        <p>Australia is the land of adventure, and we’ve compiled a few ideas to get you started. Take a camel trek through the Simpson Desert in the Northern Territory, 4WD across South Australia’s rugged <a href="/explore/icons/flinders.xml" target="_self">Flinders Ranges</a> or do the <a href="http://www.australia.com/campaigns/nothinglike/au/great-ocean-road-product8.htm" target="_blank">Great Ocean Walk</a> in Victoria.  Ski or snowboard winter slopes, trek through ancient rainforests or pick one of our pristine islands to combine adventure with true relaxation. You can dive, snorkel, canoe, kayak and surf all around Australia.</p>
        <p>To truly experience Australia, you need to travel it. Check out our classic <a href="/explore/itineraries-ideas/holiday-ideas.xml" target="_self">road trips</a> and <a href="/explore/itineraries-ideas/walking-australia.xml" target="_self">long-distance walks</a>. Spot Australia’s Big Things on the spectacular coastal route from Sydney to Cairns, hike Sydney Harbour’s coastal walks or drive the <a href="/explore/icons/great-ocean-road.xml" target="_self">Great Ocean Road</a> from Melbourne to Adelaide. </p>
        <p>Discover our outstanding wine regions, including the picturesque <a href="/explore/states/nsw/hunter-valley.xml" target="_self">Hunter Valley</a> near Sydney, the <a href="/about/australias-landscapes/wine-regions/yarra-valley.xml" target="_self">Yarra Valley</a> near Melbourne and the Swan Valley, not far from Perth. Wine, dine, surf and abseil in Western Australia’s <a href="/explore/states/wa/wa-margaret-river.xml" target="_self">Margaret River</a> region or day trip from Adelaide to the <a href="/explore/states/sa/barossa-valley.xml" target="_self">Barossa Valley</a>. </p>
        <p>Learn about iconic Australian places such as the World Heritage-listed <a href="/explore/icons/great-barrier-reef.xml" target="_self">Great Barrier Reef</a>, <a href="/explore/icons/kakadu.xml" target="_self">Kakadu National Park</a> and <a href="/explore/icons/tas-wilderness.xml" target="_self">Tasmanian wilderness</a>. Australian landscapes are so diverse, from our sacred <a href="/explore/icons/red-centre.xml" target="_self">Red Centre</a> to Western Australia’s <a href="/explore/icons/ningaloo.xml" target="_self">Ningaloo Reef</a> and the mountainous, seasonally snow-capped <a href="/explore/icons/alps.xml" target="_self">Australian Alps</a>. </p>
        <p>A holiday, a working holiday or study experience, Australia much to offer.a</p>
    ]]></txt_Information>
            <con_CenterContent>
                <CenterContent isTemplate="1">
                    <hdl_Title><![CDATA[Work, volunteer and study in Australia]]></hdl_Title>
                    <img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/plan-before-you-go-work-volunteer-study-youth-visa-hl.jpg" alt="Work, volunteer and study in Australia">]]></img_MainImage>
                    <stf_Caption><![CDATA[Work, volunteer &amp; study in Australia]]></stf_Caption>
                    <anc_link><![CDATA[/plan/before-you-go/work-volunteer-study/youth-visa.xml]]></anc_link>
                    <txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[
        Depending on what kind of holiday you have planned, you’ll need to sort out your visas. Australia is so big, and so far from many countries, that many travellers choose to spend a large chunk of time here to experience it fully. Find out how if you are eligible to apply for a year-long Working Holiday Visa, and how you can extend your stay by working in regional areas. Plus learn about volunteering and studying in Australia - both great ways to immerse yourself into Australian life and enrich your adventure.
    ]]>
                    </txt_Information>
                </CenterContent><CenterContent isTemplate="1">
                    <hdl_Title><![CDATA[Backpacker Essentials]]></hdl_Title>
                    <img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/plan-before-you-go-work-volunteer-study-backpacker-essentials-hl.jpg" alt="Backpacker Essentials">]]></img_MainImage>
                    <stf_Caption><![CDATA[Backpacker Essentials]]></stf_Caption>
                    <anc_link><![CDATA[/plan/before-you-go/work-volunteer-study/backpacker-essentials.xml]]></anc_link>
                    <txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[
        Before hitting Australia’s shores, get some <a href="/plan/before-you-go/work-volunteer-study/backpacker-essentials.xml" target="_self">backpacker basics</a>. Learn about our budget accommodation, which ranges from classic country pubs to huge hostels. Find out more about the options for exploring Australia, whether you want a 4WD adventure, epic train journey or a hop-on-and-off backpacker bus. Brush up on the key Australian road rules, find out where you can log on with your laptop and get the low-down on Australian tour companies. It’s all here, in bite-sized pieces! 
    ]]>
                    </txt_Information>
                </CenterContent><CenterContent isTemplate="1">
                    <hdl_Title><![CDATA[Backpacker Precincts]]></hdl_Title>
                    <img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/plan-before-you-go-work-volunteer-study-backpacker-precincts-hl.jpg" alt="Backpacker Precincts">]]></img_MainImage>
                    <stf_Caption><![CDATA[Backpacker Precincts]]></stf_Caption>
                    <anc_link><![CDATA[/plan/before-you-go/work-volunteer-study/backpacker-precincts.xml]]></anc_link>
                    <txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[
        Join the backpacker brigade in Australia’s <a href="/plan/before-you-go/work-volunteer-study/backpacker-precincts.xml" target="_self">hippest urban enclaves</a>. From Bondi Beach in Sydney to Brisbane’s Fortitude Valley, these are places the young and young-at-heart come to stay during their Australian adventure. You’ll find hostels, nightlife, places to eat and drink and a vibrant sense of community. Soak up the historic seaside charm in Perth’s <a href="/explore/cities/perth/wa-fremantle.xml" target="_self">Fremantle</a> or experience Melbourne’s alternative culture in Fitzroy. Swap travel tales beneath the palm trees along Darwin’s Mitchell Street or along Cairns’ oceanfront esplanade.   Explore Adelaide’s attractions from the stylish, central East End, dine out in Hobart’s <a href="/explore/cities/hobart/hobart-salamanca-place.xml" target="_self">Salamanca Place</a> or throw yourself into the high-energy nightlife of Surfers Paradise. 
    ]]>
                    </txt_Information>
                </CenterContent><CenterContent isTemplate="1">
                    <hdl_Title><![CDATA[Adventure in Australia]]></hdl_Title>
                    <img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/explore-things-to-see-do-adventure-adventure-hl.jpg" alt="Adventure in Australia">]]></img_MainImage>
                    <stf_Caption><![CDATA[Adventure in Australia]]></stf_Caption>
                    <anc_link><![CDATA[/explore/things-to-do/australian-adventure/adventure-australia.xml]]></anc_link>
                    <txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[
        Leave your safe life behind - Australia has vast deserts, snow-capped mountains, sea-sculpted coastlines and ancient rainforest to <a href="/explore/things-to-do/australian-adventure/adventure-australia.xml" target="_self">feel alive</a> in. Ride a Harley from Sydney to Melbourne or take a helicopter between Victoria’s powdered slopes. See the Simpson Desert on camelback or soar over Canberra in a <a href="http://www.australia.com/campaigns/nothinglike/au/canberra-product2.htm" target="_blank">hot-air balloon</a>. Hike the Great Ocean Walk alongside the wild Southern Ocean or squeeze through limestone caves in the Margaret River. Hike, bike, horse-ride or hang-glide. Winch your way down a mountain with just intense focus and thick rope.  In Australia, there’s no excuse not to get amongst it. 
    ]]>
                    </txt_Information>
                </CenterContent><CenterContent isTemplate="1">
                    <hdl_Title><![CDATA[Adventure on Australia's Waterways]]></hdl_Title>
                    <img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/explore-things-to-see-do-adventure-waterways-hl.jpg" alt="Adventure on Australia's Waterways">]]></img_MainImage>
                    <stf_Caption><![CDATA[Adventure on Australia's Waterways]]></stf_Caption>
                    <anc_link><![CDATA[/explore/things-to-do/australian-adventure/adventure-waterways.xml]]></anc_link>
                    <txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[
        Make a splash with any of the many adventure activities happening in, on and around <a href="/explore/things-to-do/australian-adventure/adventure-waterways.xml" target="_self">Australia’s waterways</a>. White water raft through Tasmania’s World heritage wilderness or set sail on Sydney Harbour. Cage dive with great white sharks or reel in a barramundi big enough to boast about. It doesn’t matter whether you’re hankering to surf glassy, 10-foot waves or canoe through the towering walls of an ancient gorge. Australia is the place for anyone with a love of water and thirst for adventure. Here are some ideas to whet your adventurous spirit! 
    ]]>
                    </txt_Information>
                </CenterContent><CenterContent isTemplate="1">
                    <hdl_Title><![CDATA[The BIG Pacific Coast Touring Route]]></hdl_Title>
                    <img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/explore-itineraries-big-pacific-coast-touring-route-hl.jpg" alt="The BIG Pacific Coast Touring Route">]]></img_MainImage>
                    <stf_Caption><![CDATA[The BIG Pacific Coast Touring Route]]></stf_Caption>
                    <anc_link><![CDATA[/explore/itineraries/big-pacific-coast-touring-route.xml]]></anc_link>
                    <txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[
        Australia is a big country with a fondness for Big Things – super-sized sculptures commemorating everything from prawns and pineapples to native animals and Ned Kelly. You’ll find them all along the spectacular <a href="/explore/itineraries/big-pacific-coast-touring-route.xml" target="_self">Pacific Coast Touring</a> Route, which stretches all the way from Sydney to Cairns. Weave through the Hunter Valley, <a href="/explore/icons/byron-bay.xml" target="_self">Byron Bay</a>, the glittering Gold Coast and see the World Heritage-listed wonders of <a href="/explore/icons/fraser-island.xml" target="_self">Fraser Island</a> and Great Barrier Reef. Stop to snap the Big Banana, a giant gumboot, a herculean pelican and many more larger-than-life monuments along the way.  Whether you consider them highway art or just humourous, the Big Things are worth spotting on this stunning Australian road trip. 
    ]]>
                    </txt_Information>
                </CenterContent><CenterContent isTemplate="1">
                    <hdl_Title><![CDATA[Exploring Australia]]></hdl_Title>
                    <img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/explore-hub-hl.jpg" alt="Exploring Australia">]]></img_MainImage>
                    <stf_Caption><![CDATA[Exploring Australia]]></stf_Caption>
                    <anc_link><![CDATA[/explore.xml]]></anc_link>
                    <txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[
        Your options for <a href="/explore.xml" target="_self">exploring Australia</a> are as diverse as the country itself.  Choose the journeys which best suit your holiday, whether you’ve got two weeks to see the sights or six months to cover the country in a campervan. Drive, fly, sail, take a train or tackle an epic walk. 
    ]]>
                    </txt_Information>
                </CenterContent>
            </con_CenterContent>
        </TopCategoryHighlights>
    </con_Body>
</SubPageLayout>
    </con_Body>
    <lst_Subpages>
        <lst_Subpage><![CDATA[<a href="/plan/before-you-go/work-volunteer-study/youth-visa.xml">Work, Volunteer and Study in Australia</a>]]></lst_Subpage>
        <lst_Subpage><![CDATA[<a href="/plan/before-you-go/work-volunteer-study/backpacker-essentials.xml">Backpacker Essentials</a>]]></lst_Subpage>
        <lst_Subpage><![CDATA[<a href="/plan/before-you-go/work-volunteer-study/backpacker-precincts.xml">Backpacker Precincts</a>]]></lst_Subpage>
    </lst_Subpages>
</ConsumerBaseFoundation>