<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<ConsumerBaseFoundation pageID="9502" isTemplate="1">
	<breadcrumb>
		<element level="1">
			<headline><![CDATA[Homepage ]]></headline>
			<href><![CDATA[/index.xml]]></href>
		</element>
		<element level="2">
			<headline><![CDATA[Explore ]]></headline>
			<href><![CDATA[/explore.xml]]></href>
		</element>
		<element level="4">
			<headline><![CDATA[Shopping]]></headline>
			<href><![CDATA[/explore/things-to-do/shopping.xml]]></href>
		</element>
		<element level="5">
			<headline><![CDATA[Australia's Markets]]></headline>
			<href><![CDATA[/explore/things-to-do/shopping/nat-australias-markets.xml]]></href>
		</element>

	</breadcrumb>
	<img_background><![CDATA[/contentimages/explore-things-to-see-do-shopping-markets.jpg]]></img_background>
	<hdl_Title><![CDATA[Australia's Markets]]></hdl_Title>
	<img_Banner><![CDATA[]]>
	</img_Banner>
	<img_SearchThumbnail><![CDATA[/thumbnails/explore-things-to-see-do-shopping-markets-search.jpg]]></img_SearchThumbnail>
	<img_Thumbnail><![CDATA[/contentimages/explore-things-to-see-do-shopping-markets-th.jpg]]></img_Thumbnail>
	<opt_HideInBreadcrumbs><![CDATA[Show]]></opt_HideInBreadcrumbs>
	<opt_HidePage><![CDATA[no]]></opt_HidePage>
	<opt_hideTitle><![CDATA[0]]></opt_hideTitle>
	<opt_hide_in_sitemap><![CDATA[no]]></opt_hide_in_sitemap>
	<opt_IncludeVideo><![CDATA[0]]></opt_IncludeVideo>
	<opt_isHubPage><![CDATA[0]]></opt_isHubPage>
	<opt_isNewWindow><![CDATA[_self]]></opt_isNewWindow>
	<opt_PageLayout><![CDATA[]]>
	</opt_PageLayout>
	<opt_PartnerLead><![CDATA[no]]></opt_PartnerLead>
	<stf_description><![CDATA[Get a taste of Australia’s vibrant markets, selling everything from fresh produce to hand-crafted gifts and high fashion. Read more about Aussie markets.]]></stf_description>
	<stf_ExcludedCountries><![CDATA[]]>
	</stf_ExcludedCountries>
	<stf_hideInXmlSitemap><![CDATA[]]>
	</stf_hideInXmlSitemap>
	<stf_ImageLocation><![CDATA[Adelaide Central Markets, Adelaide, SA. &copy; SATC]]></stf_ImageLocation>
	<stf_intro_title><![CDATA[]]>
	</stf_intro_title>
	<stf_IsExternalSiteArticle><![CDATA[]]>
	</stf_IsExternalSiteArticle>
	<stf_IsMobile><![CDATA[y]]></stf_IsMobile>
	<stf_keywords><![CDATA[Australia’s markets, food markets Australia, art markets Australia, Queen Victoria Market, Mindil beach market,  Salamanca markets, market shopping Australia, Adelaide Central markets]]></stf_keywords>
	<stf_LinkLearnMore><![CDATA[Learn More]]></stf_LinkLearnMore>
	<stf_NavigationTagLine><![CDATA[]]>
	</stf_NavigationTagLine>
	<stf_PageHeading><![CDATA[]]>
	</stf_PageHeading>
	<stf_TargetedCountries><![CDATA[]]>
	</stf_TargetedCountries>
	<stf_TrackingTitle><![CDATA[]]>
	</stf_TrackingTitle>
	<TA_Title><![CDATA[Australia's Markets]]></TA_Title>
	<txt_Intro>
        <![CDATA[]]>
	</txt_Intro>
	<txt_MobileContentOnly>
        <![CDATA[]]>
	</txt_MobileContentOnly>
	<txt_SpotlightTag>
        <![CDATA[]]>
	</txt_SpotlightTag>
	<txt_Teaser>
        <![CDATA[
        Get a taste of Australia’s vibrant markets, which sell everything from fresh produce to hand-crafted gifts and high fashion.
    ]]>
	</txt_Teaser>
	<con_Body>
		<SubPageLayout isTemplate="1">
			<con_Banner>

			</con_Banner>
			<con_RHSModules>
				<ExperienceLocationMap isTemplate="1">
					<!-- no user content -->
				</ExperienceLocationMap>
				<Listing isTemplate="1">
					<anc_List1><![CDATA[/explore/cities/melbourne/melbourne-surrounds.xml]]></anc_List1>
					<anc_MoreLink><![CDATA[]]>
					</anc_MoreLink>
					<hdl_Title><![CDATA[More Australian Ideas]]></hdl_Title>
					<img_Thumbnail><![CDATA[]]>
					</img_Thumbnail>
					<med_File><![CDATA[]]>
					</med_File>
					<opt_isNewWindow><![CDATA[]]>
					</opt_isNewWindow>
					<stf_externalLink><![CDATA[]]>
					</stf_externalLink>
					<stf_ExternalLinkTitle><![CDATA[]]>
					</stf_ExternalLinkTitle>
					<stf_IsExternalSiteArticle><![CDATA[]]>
					</stf_IsExternalSiteArticle>
					<stf_LinkLearnMore><![CDATA[]]>
					</stf_LinkLearnMore>
					<txt_Teaser><![CDATA[]]>
					</txt_Teaser>
					<opt_national_landscapes_id><![CDATA[]]>
					</opt_national_landscapes_id>
					<stf_hideInXmlSitemap><![CDATA[]]>
					</stf_hideInXmlSitemap>
					<stf_TargetedCountry><![CDATA[]]>
					</stf_TargetedCountry>
					<con_Banner></con_Banner>
					<con_Body></con_Body>
					<con_RHSModules></con_RHSModules>
					<con_Category></con_Category>
					<lst_Subpages></lst_Subpages>
				</Listing>
				<PlanYourVisit isTemplate="1">
					<anc_AccommodationSearch><![CDATA[/AccommodationSearch.ignore]]></anc_AccommodationSearch>
					<anc_ASPSearch><![CDATA[/plan/plan-your-trip/find-travel-agent.xml]]></anc_ASPSearch>
					<anc_Attraction><![CDATA[/AttractionSearchResults.ignore]]></anc_Attraction>
					<anc_Destinfo><![CDATA[/DestinfoSearchResults.ignore]]></anc_Destinfo>
					<anc_EventsSearch><![CDATA[/EventsSearch.xml]]></anc_EventsSearch>
					<anc_GeneralSearch><![CDATA[/GeneralSearch.ignore]]></anc_GeneralSearch>
					<anc_Hire><![CDATA[/Hire.ignore]]></anc_Hire>
					<anc_Info><![CDATA[/InfoSearchResults.ignore]]></anc_Info>
					<anc_More><![CDATA[]]>
					</anc_More>
					<anc_RestaurantSearch><![CDATA[/RestaurantSearch.ignore]]></anc_RestaurantSearch>
					<anc_Tour><![CDATA[/TourSearchResults.ignore]]></anc_Tour>
					<anc_Transport><![CDATA[/Transport.ignore]]></anc_Transport>
					<hdl_Title><![CDATA[Plan Your Visit]]></hdl_Title>
					<language><![CDATA[ENA]]></language>
					<stf_Accomodation><![CDATA[]]>
					</stf_Accomodation>
					<stf_AreaFilter><![CDATA[]]>
					</stf_AreaFilter>
					<stf_Attractions><![CDATA[]]>
					</stf_Attractions>
					<stf_AussieSpecialist><![CDATA[]]>
					</stf_AussieSpecialist>
					<stf_Destinationinfo><![CDATA[]]>
					</stf_Destinationinfo>
					<stf_DomesticRegion><![CDATA[]]>
					</stf_DomesticRegion>
					<stf_Events><![CDATA[]]>
					</stf_Events>
					<stf_Hire><![CDATA[]]>
					</stf_Hire>
					<stf_Informationservices><![CDATA[]]>
					</stf_Informationservices>
					<stf_PlanYourVisitTitle><![CDATA[Plan Your Visit]]></stf_PlanYourVisitTitle>
					<stf_StateFilter><![CDATA[]]>
					</stf_StateFilter>
					<stf_Tours><![CDATA[]]>
					</stf_Tours>
					<stf_Transport><![CDATA[]]>
					</stf_Transport>
				</PlanYourVisit>
			</con_RHSModules>
			<con_Video>

			</con_Video>
			<con_Body>
				<TopCategoryHighlights isTemplate="1">
					<stf_Heading><![CDATA[Australia's Markets]]></stf_Heading>
					<stf_InformationTitle><![CDATA[]]>
					</stf_InformationTitle>
					<txt_Information><![CDATA[Get a taste of Australia’s vibrant markets, which sell everything from fresh produce to hand-crafted gifts and high fashion.&nbsp; Browse boutique souvenirs in Sydney’s historic Rocks precinct or see the creations of local potters, painters and glassblowers in Hobart’s Salamanca Markets. Stock up on fresh, organic food from Brisbane’s many farmers markets or discover the country’s largest arts and crafts markets in Canberra. Sample the spices of five continents at Darwin’s Mindil Beach Sunset Markets or create the perfect picnic with ingredients from Adelaide Central Market. Grab an original fashion creation at Melbourne’s Rose Street Markets or join busking musicians at Fremantle’s lively weekend markets. You’ll find a vibrant market almost everywhere you go in Australia.]]></txt_Information>
					<con_CenterContent>
						<CenterContent isTemplate="1">
							<hdl_Title><![CDATA[Sydney, New South Wales]]></hdl_Title>
							<img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/9.5.5_Australia_markets_hl1.jpg.jpg" alt="The Rocks Markets, Sydney, NSW">]]></img_MainImage>
							<stf_Caption><![CDATA[The Rocks Markets, Sydney, NSW]]></stf_Caption>
							<anc_link><![CDATA[/explore/cities/sydney.xml]]></anc_link>
							<txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[
        Embrace the colour and chaos of Paddy’s Market in Chinatown, open Wednesday to Sundays.  Stall-holders sing out their bargains as you trawl the aisles of fresh produce, souvenirs and clothing. For fresh seafood, head to the daily Sydney Fish Markets in Pyrmont. Sign up for a seafood cooking class or take a behind-the-scenes tour.  Shop for elegant, hand-crafted Australian art and jewellery at <a href="/explore/cities/sydney/sydney-the-rocks.xml" target="_self">The Rocks Markets</a> on Saturdays. Snap up a second-hand bargain at Rozelle’s weekend markets or the Glebe markets on Saturday. Check out emerging designers in Paddington’s Saturdays Markets or Bondi’s Sunday markets, which also does vintage chic. 
    ]]>
							</txt_Information>
						</CenterContent>
						<CenterContent isTemplate="1">
							<hdl_Title><![CDATA[Canberra, Australian Capital Territory]]></hdl_Title>
							<img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/9.5.5_Australia_markets_hl2.jpg" alt="Old Bus Depot Markets, Canberra, ACT">]]></img_MainImage>
							<stf_Caption><![CDATA[Old Bus Depot Markets, ACT]]></stf_Caption>
							<anc_link><![CDATA[/explore/cities/canberra.xml]]></anc_link>
							<txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[You can buy almost anything from Canberra’s popular Old Bus Depot Markets, open every Sunday. More than 200 stalls sell art, homewares, handcrafted jewellery, clothing, together with regional produce and wine. Lunch here is a local tradition, with a huge array of cuisines to tempt you. Held every Saturday morning, the Capital Regional Farmers Market peddles fruit, vegetables, plants, flowers, seafood, meat and cheeses. Find vintage treasures, second-hand books, jewellery and international foods at the Gorman House Markets in Braddon each Saturday. Head to Hall for Australia’s largest craft markets, held on the first Sunday of the month.]]>
							</txt_Information>
						</CenterContent>
						<CenterContent isTemplate="1">
							<hdl_Title><![CDATA[Melbourne, Victoria]]></hdl_Title>
							<img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/9.5.5_Australia_markets_hl3.jpg" alt="Queen Victoria Market, Melbourne, VIC">]]></img_MainImage>
							<stf_Caption><![CDATA[Queen Victoria Market, VIC]]></stf_Caption>
							<anc_link><![CDATA[/explore/cities/melbourne.xml]]></anc_link>
							<txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[The Queen Victoria Market is reputed to be the largest and oldest market in the southern hemisphere. Immerse yourself in fresh produce, gourmet delicatessen products, bargain clothing and all manner of goods to the tune of buskers and the bustle of the local crowd.&nbsp; The Prahran Market,has been selling divine gourmet delights since 1864. For unique hand-made gifts try the Sunday Market at the Victorian Arts Centre or the Rose Street Markets in the heart of funky Fitzroy. On Sundays, browse the work of local artists at St Kilda’s Esplanade Markets or visit the Docklands Sunday Markets for unique, original artworks and pre-loved treasures. Try the busy Camberwell Sunday market for an eclectic mix of pre-loved and hand crafted goods.&nbsp; ]]>
							</txt_Information>
						</CenterContent>
						<CenterContent isTemplate="1">
							<hdl_Title><![CDATA[Brisbane, Queensland]]></hdl_Title>
							<img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/9.5.5_Australia_markets_hl4.jpg" alt="West End Markets, Brisbane, QLD">]]></img_MainImage>
							<stf_Caption><![CDATA[West End Markets, Brisbane, QLD]]></stf_Caption>
							<anc_link><![CDATA[/explore/cities/brisbane.xml]]></anc_link>
							<txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[Fill your eco-friendly bag with a rainbow of seasonal produce from the Powers Farmers markets in Michelton, Manly and New Farm’s Powerhouse. The people manning the stalls have all grown, cooked or crafted the produce they’re selling.&nbsp; More fresh foods, as well as flowers, plants, lifestyle products and craft, are on offer at the Rocklea Saturday Market.&nbsp; Check out a diverse mix of products and fresh produce at the popular West End Markets, which has stalls beneath the fig trees every Saturday. Shop for local designers, sample delicious snacks and soak up the vibrant riverside atmosphere at the South Bank Lifestyle Market, held every Friday evening, Saturday and Sunday. ]]>
							</txt_Information>
						</CenterContent>
						<CenterContent isTemplate="1">
							<hdl_Title><![CDATA[Adelaide, South Australia]]></hdl_Title>
							<img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/9.5.5_Australia_markets_hl5.jpg" alt="Adelaide Central Markets, SA">]]></img_MainImage>
							<stf_Caption><![CDATA[Adelaide Central Markets, SA]]></stf_Caption>
							<anc_link><![CDATA[/explore/cities/adelaide.xml]]></anc_link>
							<txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[
        Don’t miss the old-fashioned bustle of <a href="/explore/cities/adelaide/adelaide-central-market.xml" target="_self">Adelaide Central Markets</a>, which sells premium produce from growers across the state. From Tuesday to Saturday you can come here to compile the perfect picnic, source ingredients for an exotic recipe or enjoy a first-rate coffee in a stylish cafe. Shop for everything from fashion to food in the Brickworks Markets, open Fridays, weekends and public holidays. Open across the same period is the Adelaide Hills Markets in Lobethal, selling gourmet grub, arts and crafts, clothes, furniture and homewares. When you’re tired of shopping, relax in the courtyard with live entertainment. 
    ]]>
							</txt_Information>
						</CenterContent>
						<CenterContent isTemplate="1">
							<hdl_Title><![CDATA[Hobart, Tasmania]]></hdl_Title>
							<img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/9.5.5_Australia_markets_hl6.jpg" alt="Salamanca Markets, Hobart, TAS">]]></img_MainImage>
							<stf_Caption><![CDATA[Salamanca Markets, Hobart, TAS]]></stf_Caption>
							<anc_link><![CDATA[/explore/cities/hobart.xml]]></anc_link>
							<txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[
        Shop for fresh produce and uniquely Tasmanian art and craft in <a href="/explore/cities/hobart/hobart-salamanca-place.xml" target="_self">Salamanca Markets</a>, held every Saturday morning in the historic cobblestone square of Salamanca Place. Buy a one-off piece from a local glassblower, potter, wood-worker or painter. Drink coffee under the sun umbrellas, listen to buskers and chat to friendly local growers about their organic apples. On Sundays, the vibrant Hobart Showground Market in Glenorchy sells fresh fruit and vegetables, garden products and budget gifts. It hosts wood chopping competitions, dog shows and equestrian displays.  Take advantage of the fresh food specials at Moonah Island Markets, open Wednesday to Sunday. 
    ]]>
							</txt_Information>
						</CenterContent>
						<CenterContent isTemplate="1">
							<hdl_Title><![CDATA[Perth, Western Australia]]></hdl_Title>
							<img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/9.5.5_Australia_markets_hl7.jpg" alt="E-Shed Markets, Perth, WA">]]></img_MainImage>
							<stf_Caption><![CDATA[E-Shed Markets, Perth, WA]]></stf_Caption>
							<anc_link><![CDATA[/explore/cities/perth.xml]]></anc_link>
							<txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[
        There are more than 150 stalls in Fremantle’s buzzing weekend markets, held in a grand old Victorian market hall. Shop for local opals and <a href="/explore/states/wa/wa-wildflowers.xml" target="_self">Western Australian wildflowers</a>, pick up an antique, find fashion bargains or sample fresh Indian Ocean seafood.  You’ll also find hand-crafted gifts and souvenirs in the E-Shed Markets, held every weekend in an old cargo shed on Fremantle Harbour. Head to the weekend markets in the Perth Cultural Centre for fruit and veg, flowers, art, fashion, jewellery and organic foods. Or taste the best and freshest regional flavours at farmers markets in Subiaco, Albany and Kalamunda. 
    ]]>
							</txt_Information>
						</CenterContent>
						<CenterContent isTemplate="1">
							<hdl_Title><![CDATA[Darwin, Northern Territory]]></hdl_Title>
							<img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/9.5.5_Australia_markets_hl8.jpg" alt="Mindil Beach Markets, Darwin, NT">]]></img_MainImage>
							<stf_Caption><![CDATA[Mindil Beach Markets, Darwin, NT]]></stf_Caption>
							<anc_link><![CDATA[]]>
							</anc_link>
							<txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[
        Open from May to October, the <a href="/explore/cities/darwin/nt-mindil-markets.xml" target="_self">Mindil Beach Sunset Markets</a> are famed for the exotic array of food stalls and relaxed, tropical setting. Sample spice-laden specialities from five continents and watch the unforgettable, flamingo pink sunset.  A local institution and must-visit for tourists, the markets also sell handicrafts from across the world. For original, quirky or second-hand stuff, head to Nightcliff Markets, held Sundays from April to December. Browse Aboriginal artwork at the evening markets on Mitchell Street or get breakfast with your art and crafts at the colourful Parap markets on Saturdays. Rapid Creek Markets are the oldest in <a href="/explore/cities/darwin.xml" target="_self">Darwin</a> and sell food and knick-knacks every Sunday. 
    ]]>
							</txt_Information>
						</CenterContent>
					</con_CenterContent>
				</TopCategoryHighlights>
			</con_Body>
		</SubPageLayout>
	</con_Body>
	<lst_Subpages>
	</lst_Subpages>
</ConsumerBaseFoundation>