<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<ConsumerBaseFoundation pageID="10780"
	isTemplate="1">
	<breadcrumb>
		<element level="1">
			<headline><![CDATA[Homepage ]]></headline>
			<href><![CDATA[/index.xml]]></href>
		</element>
		<element level="2">
			<headline><![CDATA[About]]></headline>
			<href><![CDATA[/about.xml]]></href>
		</element>
		<element level="4">
			<headline><![CDATA[Cities]]></headline>
			<href><![CDATA[/about/australias-landscapes/cities.xml]]></href>
		</element>
		<element level="5">
			<headline><![CDATA[Australia's City Waterways]]></headline>
			<href><![CDATA[/about/australias-landscapes/cities/nat-city-waterways.xml]]></href>
		</element>

	</breadcrumb>
	<img_background><![CDATA[/contentimages/about-australias-landscapes-cities-nat-city-waterways.jpg]]></img_background>
	<hdl_Title><![CDATA[Australia's City Waterways]]></hdl_Title>
	<img_Banner><![CDATA[]]>
	</img_Banner>
	<img_SearchThumbnail><![CDATA[/thumbnails/about-australias-landscapes-cities-nat-city-waterways-search.jpg]]></img_SearchThumbnail>
	<img_Thumbnail><![CDATA[/contentimages/about-australias-landscapes-cities-nat-city-waterways-th.jpg]]></img_Thumbnail>
	<opt_HideInBreadcrumbs><![CDATA[Show]]></opt_HideInBreadcrumbs>
	<opt_HidePage><![CDATA[no]]></opt_HidePage>
	<opt_hideTitle><![CDATA[0]]></opt_hideTitle>
	<opt_hide_in_sitemap><![CDATA[no]]></opt_hide_in_sitemap>
	<opt_IncludeVideo><![CDATA[0]]></opt_IncludeVideo>
	<opt_isHubPage><![CDATA[0]]></opt_isHubPage>
	<opt_isNewWindow><![CDATA[_self]]></opt_isNewWindow>
	<opt_PageLayout><![CDATA[]]>
	</opt_PageLayout>
	<opt_PartnerLead><![CDATA[no]]></opt_PartnerLead>
	<stf_description><![CDATA[Experience life around Australia’s vital city waterways, from iconic Sydney Harbour to the wide rivers which meander through Melbourne, Perth, Adelaide and Brisbane.]]></stf_description>
	<stf_ExcludedCountries><![CDATA[]]>
	</stf_ExcludedCountries>
	<stf_hideInXmlSitemap><![CDATA[]]>
	</stf_hideInXmlSitemap>
	<stf_ImageLocation><![CDATA[Hobart, Tasmania. &copy; Tourism Tasmania]]></stf_ImageLocation>
	<stf_intro_title><![CDATA[]]>
	</stf_intro_title>
	<stf_IsExternalSiteArticle><![CDATA[]]>
	</stf_IsExternalSiteArticle>
	<stf_IsMobile><![CDATA[n]]></stf_IsMobile>
	<stf_keywords><![CDATA[Australian waterways, Australia waterways, Australia’s waterways, Sydney Harbour, Hobart Harbour, Yarra River, Swan River, Torrens River, Port Adelaide, Cairns Esplanade, Lake Burley Griffin, Roebuck Bay, Cable Beach, Darwin Harbour, Fannie Bay,]]></stf_keywords>
	<stf_LinkLearnMore><![CDATA[Learn More]]></stf_LinkLearnMore>
	<stf_NavigationTagLine><![CDATA[]]>
	</stf_NavigationTagLine>
	<stf_PageHeading><![CDATA[]]>
	</stf_PageHeading>
	<stf_TargetedCountries><![CDATA[]]>
	</stf_TargetedCountries>
	<stf_TrackingTitle><![CDATA[]]>
	</stf_TrackingTitle>
	<TA_Title><![CDATA[Australia's City Waterways]]></TA_Title>
	<txt_Intro>
        <![CDATA[]]>
	</txt_Intro>
	<txt_MobileContentOnly>
        <![CDATA[]]>
	</txt_MobileContentOnly>
	<txt_SpotlightTag>
        <![CDATA[]]>
	</txt_SpotlightTag>
	<txt_Teaser>
        <![CDATA[Experience life around Australia’s vital city waterways, from iconic Sydney Harbour to the wide rivers which meander through Melbourne, Perth, Adelaide and Brisbane.]]>
	</txt_Teaser>
	<con_Body>
		<SubPageLayout isTemplate="1">
			<con_Banner>

			</con_Banner>
			<con_RHSModules>
				<Listing isTemplate="1">
					<anc_List1><![CDATA[]]>
					</anc_List1>
					<anc_MoreLink><![CDATA[]]>
					</anc_MoreLink>
					<hdl_Title><![CDATA[More Australian Ideas]]></hdl_Title>
					<img_Thumbnail><![CDATA[]]>
					</img_Thumbnail>
					<med_File><![CDATA[]]>
					</med_File>
					<opt_isNewWindow><![CDATA[]]>
					</opt_isNewWindow>
					<stf_externalLink><![CDATA[]]>
					</stf_externalLink>
					<stf_ExternalLinkTitle><![CDATA[]]>
					</stf_ExternalLinkTitle>
					<stf_IsExternalSiteArticle><![CDATA[]]>
					</stf_IsExternalSiteArticle>
					<stf_LinkLearnMore><![CDATA[]]>
					</stf_LinkLearnMore>
					<txt_Teaser><![CDATA[]]>
					</txt_Teaser>
					<opt_national_landscapes_id><![CDATA[]]>
					</opt_national_landscapes_id>
					<stf_hideInXmlSitemap><![CDATA[]]>
					</stf_hideInXmlSitemap>
					<stf_TargetedCountry><![CDATA[]]>
					</stf_TargetedCountry>
					<con_Banner></con_Banner>
					<con_Body></con_Body>
					<con_RHSModules></con_RHSModules>
					<con_Category></con_Category>
					<lst_Subpages></lst_Subpages>
				</Listing>
				<PlanYourVisit isTemplate="1">
					<anc_AccommodationSearch><![CDATA[/AccommodationSearch.ignore]]></anc_AccommodationSearch>
					<anc_ASPSearch><![CDATA[/plan/plan-your-trip/find-travel-agent.xml]]></anc_ASPSearch>
					<anc_Attraction><![CDATA[/AttractionSearchResults.ignore]]></anc_Attraction>
					<anc_Destinfo><![CDATA[/DestinfoSearchResults.ignore]]></anc_Destinfo>
					<anc_EventsSearch><![CDATA[/EventsSearch.xml]]></anc_EventsSearch>
					<anc_GeneralSearch><![CDATA[/GeneralSearch.ignore]]></anc_GeneralSearch>
					<anc_Hire><![CDATA[/Hire.ignore]]></anc_Hire>
					<anc_Info><![CDATA[/InfoSearchResults.ignore]]></anc_Info>
					<anc_More><![CDATA[]]>
					</anc_More>
					<anc_RestaurantSearch><![CDATA[/RestaurantSearch.ignore]]></anc_RestaurantSearch>
					<anc_Tour><![CDATA[/TourSearchResults.ignore]]></anc_Tour>
					<anc_Transport><![CDATA[/Transport.ignore]]></anc_Transport>
					<hdl_Title><![CDATA[Plan Your Visit]]></hdl_Title>
					<language><![CDATA[ENA]]></language>
					<stf_Accomodation><![CDATA[]]>
					</stf_Accomodation>
					<stf_AreaFilter><![CDATA[]]>
					</stf_AreaFilter>
					<stf_Attractions><![CDATA[]]>
					</stf_Attractions>
					<stf_AussieSpecialist><![CDATA[]]>
					</stf_AussieSpecialist>
					<stf_Destinationinfo><![CDATA[]]>
					</stf_Destinationinfo>
					<stf_DomesticRegion><![CDATA[]]>
					</stf_DomesticRegion>
					<stf_Events><![CDATA[]]>
					</stf_Events>
					<stf_Hire><![CDATA[]]>
					</stf_Hire>
					<stf_Informationservices><![CDATA[]]>
					</stf_Informationservices>
					<stf_PlanYourVisitTitle><![CDATA[Plan Your Visit]]></stf_PlanYourVisitTitle>
					<stf_StateFilter><![CDATA[]]>
					</stf_StateFilter>
					<stf_Tours><![CDATA[]]>
					</stf_Tours>
					<stf_Transport><![CDATA[]]>
					</stf_Transport>
				</PlanYourVisit>
			</con_RHSModules>
			<con_Video>

			</con_Video>
			<con_Body>
				<TopCategoryHighlights isTemplate="1">
					<stf_Heading><![CDATA[Australia’s city waterways]]></stf_Heading>
					<stf_InformationTitle><![CDATA[]]>
					</stf_InformationTitle>
					<txt_Information><![CDATA[Discover Australia’s vital city waterways, where locals come for adventure, relaxation and celebration. Our cities draw their distinct energy and personality from these waterways, whether it’s Sydney’s huge, bustling harbour, Hobart’s historic waterfront or Perth’s tranquil, blue Swan River. Wander along the Brisbane River’s floating walkway or kayak the Yarra River past Melbourne’s cultural institutions. Bike ride alongside Adelaide’s River Torrens, dive World War II shipwrecks in Darwin Harbour and windsurf on Canberra’s Lake Burley Griffin. Relax along Cairns’s lively oceanfront esplanade or spot birds and natural marvels in Broome’s Roebuck Bay. Australia’s city waterfronts are also the backdrop for&nbsp;cultural and sporting events.]]></txt_Information>
					<con_CenterContent>
						<CenterContent isTemplate="1">
							<hdl_Title><![CDATA[Sydney]]></hdl_Title>
							<img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/waterways_sydney.jpg" alt="Sydney, NSW">]]></img_MainImage>
							<stf_Caption><![CDATA[Sydney, NSW]]></stf_Caption>
							<anc_link><![CDATA[]]>
							</anc_link>
							<txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[
        You can’t visit Sydney without seeing its stunning harbour, flanked at Circular Quay by the iconic Opera House and Harbour Bridge. This is the most famous harbour view, but the city unfurls around the water in every direction.  Hike around the bush-fringed foreshore or take a scenic cruise past the waterfront mansions, historic islands and national parks. Go sailing or kayaking or hop on a ferry to <a href="/explore/cities/sydney/nsw-manly-beach.xml" target="_self">Manly</a>, Watsons Bay, Balmain and Taronga Zoo. At one end the harbour curves to meet a golden chain of ocean beaches. At the other end it narrows into the Parramatta River, fringed by walking trails and historic, multicultural Parramatta. Celebrate Australia Day, New Year’s Eve, the Sydney Festival and Vivid on and around Sydney Harbour.
    ]]>
							</txt_Information>
						</CenterContent>
						<CenterContent isTemplate="1">
							<hdl_Title><![CDATA[Brisbane]]></hdl_Title>
							<img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/waterways_brisbane.jpg" alt="Brisbane, QLD">]]></img_MainImage>
							<stf_Caption><![CDATA[Brisbane, QLD]]></stf_Caption>
							<anc_link><![CDATA[]]>
							</anc_link>
							<txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[So much happens along the wide, winding Brisbane River, lined by funky suburbs, lush gardens and the huge cultural complex of South Bank. Swim in South Bank’s sandy lagoon, browse markets and art exhibitions and catch a performance of ballet, opera or theatre. A floating walkway winds alongside both South Bank and the wild City Botanic Gardens on the river’s northern edge. Catch a ferry to suburbs such as Fortitude Valley or cruise the river in a golden gondola or wooden paddlesteamer. For adventure, go canoeing or kayaking, abseil down Kangaroo Point Cliffs or climb the Story Bridge.&nbsp; Day trip to Moreton Bay and its islands or frolic riverside during the Brisbane Festival from mid-September to early October.]]>
							</txt_Information>
						</CenterContent>
						<CenterContent isTemplate="1">
							<hdl_Title><![CDATA[Melbourne]]></hdl_Title>
							<img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/waterways_melbourne.jpg" alt="Melbourne, VIC">]]></img_MainImage>
							<stf_Caption><![CDATA[Melbourne, VIC]]></stf_Caption>
							<anc_link><![CDATA[]]>
							</anc_link>
							<txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[Melbournians relax, exercise and celebrate along the Yarra River, which&nbsp; flows through the city’s heart. Jog round the riverside Royal Botanic Gardens, known as ‘The Tan’ to locals, or meander past the iconic sporting ground of the MCG and Flinders Park, home of the Australian Open.&nbsp; Cycle the Yarra trail from Melbourne’s eastern suburbs to Southbank, which bustles with bars, restaurants and the cultural centre of&nbsp; Federation Square. Jump on a gondola, take a leisurely cruise, hire a row boat or go canoeing or kayaking. Dine out in the revitalised Docklands precinct or kayak down to St Kilda Beach, both on Port Phillip Bay, the city’s other main waterway. The Yarra River is the backdrop for rowing regattas and dragon boat races while the St Kilda Festival hits St Kilda Beach each February.]]>
							</txt_Information>
						</CenterContent>
						<CenterContent isTemplate="1">
							<hdl_Title><![CDATA[Adelaide]]></hdl_Title>
							<img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/waterways_adelaide.jpg" alt="Adelaide, SA">]]></img_MainImage>
							<stf_Caption><![CDATA[Adelaide, SA]]></stf_Caption>
							<anc_link><![CDATA[]]>
							</anc_link>
							<txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[You can picnic, feed the ducks, row past rose gardens and wander over footbridges along the River Torrens. The more adventurous can walk or cycle the tranquil riverside trail that stretches all the way from Adelaide’s hills to its beachside suburbs. Stop to visit the Adelaide Festival Centre, the Adelaide Zoo or continue straight to popular Henley Beach, where you can fish from the jetty, picnic on the grass or dine out at one of the many ethnic eateries.&nbsp; Further along the coast is Port Adelaide, the city’s historic harbour. Explore the museums and markets and wander the heritage-listed seaside streetscapes.]]>
							</txt_Information>
						</CenterContent>
						<CenterContent isTemplate="1">
							<hdl_Title><![CDATA[Perth]]></hdl_Title>
							<img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/waterways_perth.jpg" alt="Perth, WA">]]></img_MainImage>
							<stf_Caption><![CDATA[Perth, WA]]></stf_Caption>
							<anc_link><![CDATA[]]>
							</anc_link>
							<txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[There are many ways to enjoy the wide, blue Swan River&nbsp;that winds through Perth’s centre. Walk or cycle along riverside tracks, stopping at picturesque picnic spots and cafes. Fish along the river’s edge and swim from sandy bays and beaches such as Matilda Bay, on the edge of vast Kings Park. Go windsurfing, ski-biscuiting or parasailing, hire a jet-ski or sign up for twilight sailing. Cruise past Perth’s riverfront mansions to the vibrant port of Fremantle.&nbsp;In the other direction you can stop for wine tasting in the Swan River vineyards or&nbsp; visit historic Guildford. Perth ocean beaches are known for golden sand and excellent surf.]]>
							</txt_Information>
						</CenterContent>
						<CenterContent isTemplate="1">
							<hdl_Title><![CDATA[Darwin]]></hdl_Title>
							<img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/waterways_darwin.jpg" alt="Darwin, NT">]]></img_MainImage>
							<stf_Caption><![CDATA[Darwin, NT]]></stf_Caption>
							<anc_link><![CDATA[]]>
							</anc_link>
							<txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[Darwin’s huge harbour is rich in history, and a great place to fish, sail&nbsp; and watch the famous Top End sunset over the Arafura Sea. Join a sunset cruise, where your guide can tell you about the Japanese air raids over Darwin Harbour in 1942 and 1943. Wander down to World War II oil tunnels from the Darwin Wharf Precinct, where today you’ll also find bars, seafood restaurants and pearl shops. Dive the harbour’s World War II shipwrecks and coral reefs or join a deep sea fishing excursion. Further round Darwin’s coastline lies Fannie Bay, home to a historic jail, and the mansions and mega yachts of Cullen Bay Marina.]]>
							</txt_Information>
						</CenterContent>
						<CenterContent isTemplate="1">
							<hdl_Title><![CDATA[Canberra]]></hdl_Title>
							<img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/Paddle-boating-on-Lake-Burley-Griffin.jpg" alt="Canberra, ACT">]]></img_MainImage>
							<stf_Caption><![CDATA[Canberra, ACT]]></stf_Caption>
							<anc_link><![CDATA[]]>
							</anc_link>
							<txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[Join joggers, cyclists, sailors and determined dragon boat teams on and around Lake Burley Griffin, the huge artificial lake at Canberra’s centre. It’s surrounded by many of the city’s national institutions, so you can row past our politicians or windsurf past wigged judges descending the steps of Australia’s High Court. In the lake’s centre is the National Carillon on Aspen Island, where you hear the daily chiming of 55 bronze bells. Just beyond the city’s fringes is the Murrumbidgee River Corridor, where the locals escape to fish, swim, canoe, picnic and bushwalk. Do short riverside walks or camp along the 27km Murrumbidgee Discovery Track.]]>
							</txt_Information>
						</CenterContent>
						<CenterContent isTemplate="1">
							<hdl_Title><![CDATA[Hobart]]></hdl_Title>
							<img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/waterways_hobart.jpg" alt="Hobart, TAS">]]></img_MainImage>
							<stf_Caption><![CDATA[Hobart, TAS]]></stf_Caption>
							<anc_link><![CDATA[]]>
							</anc_link>
							<txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[Hobart’s waterfront heart is Sullivans Cove, where convicts once stumbled ashore and whalers hauled in their cargo.&nbsp; Wander the cobblestone streets of Salamanca Place, where the 1830s Georgian warehouses now house cafes, restaurants, galleries and boutiques. The neighbouring wharves are lined with yachts, fishing boats and seafood restaurants. Visit Constitution Dock, where crowds welcome in the wind-battered participants of the Sydney to Hobart yacht race each December. For a week over the new year the historic waterfront also hosts the Taste of Tasmania Festival. Hobart stretches inland from its harbour along the winding Derwent River. Join a kayaking tour to experience a different perspective on the city.]]>
							</txt_Information>
						</CenterContent>
						<CenterContent isTemplate="1">
							<hdl_Title><![CDATA[Cairns]]></hdl_Title>
							<img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/waterways_cairns.jpg" alt="Cairns, QLD">]]></img_MainImage>
							<stf_Caption><![CDATA[Cairns, QLD]]></stf_Caption>
							<anc_link><![CDATA[]]>
							</anc_link>
							<txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[Every day, boats of every size and shape depart Cairns Harbour for the treasures of the World Heritage-listed Great Barrier Reef. Go snorkelling, learn to dive or see the coral and marine life from a glass-bottomed boat. Between day trips, Cairns’ lively waterfront promenade is the place to hang out.&nbsp; Swim in the huge saltwater lagoon or relax beneath the palm trees, alongside picnicking families and travellers topping up their tans. Meander between the stylish restaurants, hotels and bars or walk, cycle or rollerblade along the boardwalk. Nearby lie the tranquil mangrove-lined waterways of Trinity Inlet, where you can cruise past native birds and visit a working crocodile farm.]]>
							</txt_Information>
						</CenterContent>
						<CenterContent isTemplate="1">
							<hdl_Title><![CDATA[Broome]]></hdl_Title>
							<img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/waterways_broome.jpg" alt="Broome, WA">]]></img_MainImage>
							<stf_Caption><![CDATA[Broome, WA]]></stf_Caption>
							<anc_link><![CDATA[]]>
							</anc_link>
							<txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[
        Camel rides, bird-watching and natural marvels are just some of the delights along Broome’s waterfront. Ride a camel along dreamy <a href="/explore/cities/broome/wa-cable-beach.xml" target="_self">Cable Beach</a>, the place to watch a blazing sun sink into the Indian Ocean. In nearby Roebuck Bay you’ll find Broome Bird Observatory, which shelters around 40 per cent of Australia’s bird species and is a stopover for migratory birds between September and April. Between March and October Roebuck Bay is the place to see the ‘Staircase to the Moon’, a spectacular, silvery illusion created by a rising full moon reflecting off tidal flats.   Visit Gantheaume Point, where dinosaur footprints are preserved in rock.
    ]]>
							</txt_Information>
						</CenterContent>
					</con_CenterContent>
				</TopCategoryHighlights>
			</con_Body>
		</SubPageLayout>
	</con_Body>
	<lst_Subpages>
	</lst_Subpages>
</ConsumerBaseFoundation>