<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<ConsumerBaseFoundation pageID="10781"
	isTemplate="1">
	<breadcrumb>
		<element level="1">
			<headline><![CDATA[Homepage ]]></headline>
			<href><![CDATA[/index.xml]]></href>
		</element>
		<element level="2">
			<headline><![CDATA[About]]></headline>
			<href><![CDATA[/about.xml]]></href>
		</element>
		<element level="4">
			<headline><![CDATA[Cities]]></headline>
			<href><![CDATA[/about/australias-landscapes/cities.xml]]></href>
		</element>
		<element level="5">
			<headline><![CDATA[Australia's Botanic Gardens]]></headline>
			<href><![CDATA[/about/australias-landscapes/cities/nat-botantic-gardens.xml]]></href>
		</element>

	</breadcrumb>
	<img_background><![CDATA[/contentimages/about-australias-landscapes-cities-nat-botantic-gardens.jpg]]></img_background>
	<hdl_Title><![CDATA[Australia's Botanic Gardens]]></hdl_Title>
	<img_Banner><![CDATA[]]>
	</img_Banner>
	<img_SearchThumbnail><![CDATA[/thumbnails/about-australias-landscapes-cities-nat-botantic-gardens-search.jpg]]></img_SearchThumbnail>
	<img_Thumbnail><![CDATA[/contentimages/about-australia-landscapes-cities-botanic-gardens-th.jpg]]></img_Thumbnail>
	<opt_HideInBreadcrumbs><![CDATA[Show]]></opt_HideInBreadcrumbs>
	<opt_HidePage><![CDATA[no]]></opt_HidePage>
	<opt_hideTitle><![CDATA[0]]></opt_hideTitle>
	<opt_hide_in_sitemap><![CDATA[no]]></opt_hide_in_sitemap>
	<opt_IncludeVideo><![CDATA[0]]></opt_IncludeVideo>
	<opt_isHubPage><![CDATA[0]]></opt_isHubPage>
	<opt_isNewWindow><![CDATA[_self]]></opt_isNewWindow>
	<opt_PageLayout><![CDATA[]]>
	</opt_PageLayout>
	<opt_PartnerLead><![CDATA[no]]></opt_PartnerLead>
	<stf_description><![CDATA[Discover the botanic gardens and parks in Australia’s cities –home to an array of native plants and animals, walking trails, lookouts, picnic spots and rich traces of Aboriginal culture.]]></stf_description>
	<stf_ExcludedCountries><![CDATA[]]>
	</stf_ExcludedCountries>
	<stf_hideInXmlSitemap><![CDATA[]]>
	</stf_hideInXmlSitemap>
	<stf_ImageLocation><![CDATA[Adelaide Botanic Gardens, SA. &copy; South Australia Tourism ]]></stf_ImageLocation>
	<stf_intro_title><![CDATA[]]>
	</stf_intro_title>
	<stf_IsExternalSiteArticle><![CDATA[]]>
	</stf_IsExternalSiteArticle>
	<stf_IsMobile><![CDATA[n]]></stf_IsMobile>
	<stf_keywords><![CDATA[Australia’s botanic gardens, botanic gardens Australia, Sydney Royal Botanic Gardens, The Domain, Centennial Park, Brisbane City Botanic Gardens, South Bank, Adelaide Botanic Gardens, Kings Park, George Brown Darwin Botanic Gardens,]]></stf_keywords>
	<stf_LinkLearnMore><![CDATA[Learn More]]></stf_LinkLearnMore>
	<stf_NavigationTagLine><![CDATA[]]>
	</stf_NavigationTagLine>
	<stf_PageHeading><![CDATA[]]>
	</stf_PageHeading>
	<stf_TargetedCountries><![CDATA[]]>
	</stf_TargetedCountries>
	<stf_TrackingTitle><![CDATA[]]>
	</stf_TrackingTitle>
	<TA_Title><![CDATA[Australia's Botanic Gardens]]></TA_Title>
	<txt_Intro>
        <![CDATA[]]>
	</txt_Intro>
	<txt_MobileContentOnly>
        <![CDATA[]]>
	</txt_MobileContentOnly>
	<txt_SpotlightTag>
        <![CDATA[]]>
	</txt_SpotlightTag>
	<txt_Teaser>
        <![CDATA[Discover the botanic gardens and parks in Australia’s cities –home to an array of native plants and animals, walking trails, lookouts, picnic spots and rich traces of Aboriginal culture.]]>
	</txt_Teaser>
	<con_Body>
		<SubPageLayout isTemplate="1">
			<con_Banner>

			</con_Banner>
			<con_RHSModules>
				<Listing isTemplate="1">
					<anc_List1><![CDATA[/about/australias-landscapes/cities.xml]]></anc_List1>
					<anc_MoreLink><![CDATA[]]>
					</anc_MoreLink>
					<hdl_Title><![CDATA[More Australian Ideas ]]></hdl_Title>
					<img_Thumbnail><![CDATA[]]>
					</img_Thumbnail>
					<med_File><![CDATA[]]>
					</med_File>
					<opt_isNewWindow><![CDATA[]]>
					</opt_isNewWindow>
					<stf_externalLink><![CDATA[]]>
					</stf_externalLink>
					<stf_ExternalLinkTitle><![CDATA[]]>
					</stf_ExternalLinkTitle>
					<stf_IsExternalSiteArticle><![CDATA[]]>
					</stf_IsExternalSiteArticle>
					<stf_LinkLearnMore><![CDATA[]]>
					</stf_LinkLearnMore>
					<txt_Teaser><![CDATA[]]>
					</txt_Teaser>
					<opt_national_landscapes_id><![CDATA[]]>
					</opt_national_landscapes_id>
					<stf_hideInXmlSitemap><![CDATA[]]>
					</stf_hideInXmlSitemap>
					<stf_TargetedCountry><![CDATA[]]>
					</stf_TargetedCountry>
					<con_Banner></con_Banner>
					<con_Body></con_Body>
					<con_RHSModules></con_RHSModules>
					<con_Category></con_Category>
					<lst_Subpages></lst_Subpages>
				</Listing>
				<PlanYourVisit isTemplate="1">
					<anc_AccommodationSearch><![CDATA[/AccommodationSearch.ignore]]></anc_AccommodationSearch>
					<anc_ASPSearch><![CDATA[/plan/plan-your-trip/find-travel-agent.xml]]></anc_ASPSearch>
					<anc_Attraction><![CDATA[/AttractionSearchResults.ignore]]></anc_Attraction>
					<anc_Destinfo><![CDATA[/DestinfoSearchResults.ignore]]></anc_Destinfo>
					<anc_EventsSearch><![CDATA[/EventsSearch.xml]]></anc_EventsSearch>
					<anc_GeneralSearch><![CDATA[/GeneralSearch.ignore]]></anc_GeneralSearch>
					<anc_Hire><![CDATA[/Hire.ignore]]></anc_Hire>
					<anc_Info><![CDATA[/InfoSearchResults.ignore]]></anc_Info>
					<anc_More><![CDATA[]]>
					</anc_More>
					<anc_RestaurantSearch><![CDATA[/RestaurantSearch.ignore]]></anc_RestaurantSearch>
					<anc_Tour><![CDATA[/TourSearchResults.ignore]]></anc_Tour>
					<anc_Transport><![CDATA[/Transport.ignore]]></anc_Transport>
					<hdl_Title><![CDATA[Plan Your Visit]]></hdl_Title>
					<language><![CDATA[ENA]]></language>
					<stf_Accomodation><![CDATA[]]>
					</stf_Accomodation>
					<stf_AreaFilter><![CDATA[]]>
					</stf_AreaFilter>
					<stf_Attractions><![CDATA[]]>
					</stf_Attractions>
					<stf_AussieSpecialist><![CDATA[]]>
					</stf_AussieSpecialist>
					<stf_Destinationinfo><![CDATA[]]>
					</stf_Destinationinfo>
					<stf_DomesticRegion><![CDATA[]]>
					</stf_DomesticRegion>
					<stf_Events><![CDATA[]]>
					</stf_Events>
					<stf_Hire><![CDATA[]]>
					</stf_Hire>
					<stf_Informationservices><![CDATA[]]>
					</stf_Informationservices>
					<stf_PlanYourVisitTitle><![CDATA[Plan Your Visit]]></stf_PlanYourVisitTitle>
					<stf_StateFilter><![CDATA[]]>
					</stf_StateFilter>
					<stf_Tours><![CDATA[]]>
					</stf_Tours>
					<stf_Transport><![CDATA[]]>
					</stf_Transport>
				</PlanYourVisit>
			</con_RHSModules>
			<con_Video>

			</con_Video>
			<con_Body>
				<TopCategoryHighlights isTemplate="1">
					<stf_Heading><![CDATA[Australia's Botanic Gardens]]></stf_Heading>
					<stf_InformationTitle><![CDATA[]]>
					</stf_InformationTitle>
					<txt_Information><![CDATA[There are gardens galore in Australia’s cities - tranquil, green spaces for walking, picnicking, recreation and contemplation. These urban sanctuaries protect plants and animals from Australia and around the world, as well as rich traces of Aboriginal culture.&nbsp; Picnic next to the harbour on the green lawns of Sydney’s Royal Botanic Gardens or follow a floating walkway through Brisbane’s lush riverside gardens.&nbsp; Walk or run around ‘the Tan’ in Melbourne, cycle through Adelaide’s expansive parklands and look over Perth from vast Kings Park. Wander through monsoon forest in Darwin, travel through different Australian eco-systems in Canberra and explore the lovely gardens on the edge of Hobart’s Derwent River.]]></txt_Information>
					<con_CenterContent>
						<CenterContent isTemplate="1">
							<hdl_Title><![CDATA[Sydney]]></hdl_Title>
							<img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/Sydney_botanic_gardens.jpg" alt="Sydney, NSW">]]></img_MainImage>
							<stf_Caption><![CDATA[Sydney, NSW]]></stf_Caption>
							<anc_link><![CDATA[]]>
							</anc_link>
							<txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[You’ll find countless spectacular picnic spots in the Royal Botanic Gardens, 30 lush hectares curved around Sydney Harbour. Smell the roses in the dedicated rose garden or wander past rare and threatened plants from around the world. There’s a garden display dedicated to Sydney’s first inhabitants, the Cadigal people, and Aboriginal tour guides can offer a deeper insight into their lives. Adjoining the gardens is the grassy Domain, where outdoor jazz, opera and symphony are held during the Sydney Festival each summer. Further east is huge Centennial Park, where you can walk, cycle, picnic and feed ducks. As well as the city’s lungs, these parklands host lots of summer music festivals.]]>
							</txt_Information>
						</CenterContent>
						<CenterContent isTemplate="1">
							<hdl_Title><![CDATA[Brisbane]]></hdl_Title>
							<img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/brisbane_botanic_gardens.jpg" alt="Brisbane, QLD">]]></img_MainImage>
							<stf_Caption><![CDATA[Brisbane, QLD]]></stf_Caption>
							<anc_link><![CDATA[]]>
							</anc_link>
							<txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[It’s a riverside oasis in Brisbane’s City Botanic Gardens, a swathe of rainforest glades, mangroves and macadamia trees. Wander through the park to Parliament House or walk, bike ride or cycle along the Brisbane Riverwalk. This floating walkway also runs alongside the lush, sprawling gardens of South Bank, on the other side of the river.&nbsp; You can lose yourself in the 52 sub-tropical hectares of the Brisbane Botanic Gardens, at the foot of Mount Coot-Tha. Explore the rainforests and Japanese gardens before heading to the mountain’s summit for panoramic views over Brisbane. Look out for native wildlife and Aboriginal art as you wind through the surrounding bushland.]]>
							</txt_Information>
						</CenterContent>
						<CenterContent isTemplate="1">
							<hdl_Title><![CDATA[Melbourne]]></hdl_Title>
							<img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/melbourne_botanic_thumb.jpg" alt="Melbourne, VIC">]]></img_MainImage>
							<stf_Caption><![CDATA[Melbourne, VIC]]></stf_Caption>
							<anc_link><![CDATA[]]>
							</anc_link>
							<txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[The bustle of Melbourne is far away in the Royal Botanic Gardens, known just as ‘The Tan’ to locals. The outer rim is one of the city’s favourite running circuits, while walking trails weave past lakes and diverse plant collections in the centre. Spot black swans, eels, bell birds, cockatoos and kookaburras and try to name a few of the 50,000 plants, which range from cacti to camellias. Join the award-winning Aboriginal heritage walk or meet microbats in their nests on an overnight eco-adventure. Also fringing the CBD is Fitzroy Gardens, with its elegant garden beds, walking paths, conservatory and cottage where Captain Cook once lived.]]>
							</txt_Information>
						</CenterContent>
						<CenterContent isTemplate="1">
							<hdl_Title><![CDATA[Adelaide]]></hdl_Title>
							<img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/Adelaide_botanic_thumb.jpg" alt="Adelaide, SA">]]></img_MainImage>
							<stf_Caption><![CDATA[Adelaide, SA]]></stf_Caption>
							<anc_link><![CDATA[]]>
							</anc_link>
							<txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[There’s no shortage of green space in Adelaide, where 29 parks sprawl across almost half of the city.&nbsp; Explore them on foot or go cycling – there’s free hourly bike hire in the CBD. You can ride all the way between the hills and the coast in River Torrens Linear Park. Picnic in the local’s beloved Botanic Park, where musicians from across the globe gather for the huge WOMADelaide festival each March. Hire paddleboats in Elder Park or row past formal rose gardens in Rymill Park. Adelaide-Himjei Garden is a Japanese-inspired oasis offering serious tranquillity. Adelaide’s parklands also have walking trails and sporting fields for everything from football to archery.]]>
							</txt_Information>
						</CenterContent>
						<CenterContent isTemplate="1">
							<hdl_Title><![CDATA[Perth]]></hdl_Title>
							<img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/Perth_botanic_garden_thumb.jpg" alt="Perth, WA">]]></img_MainImage>
							<stf_Caption><![CDATA[Perth, WA]]></stf_Caption>
							<anc_link><![CDATA[]]>
							</anc_link>
							<txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[Spread across 400 hectares on the edge of the Swan River, Kings Park and Botanic Gardens is a true city sanctuary. It’s criss-crossed with walking trails and dottted with&nbsp; spectacular vantage points over Perth, the Swan River and Darling Ranges. Enjoy the panormaras from the State War Memorial or DNA Tower and walk, bike or roller blade past the sculpted gardens, mirrored lakes and tranquil bushland. Do the treetop walk and see abundant birds and colourful Western Australian wildflowers. Relax with a barbeque or a picnic beneath the gum trees. Local Aboriginal guides can lead you through the park, teaching you about bush survival and the Dreamtime explots of the Rainbow Serpent.]]>
							</txt_Information>
						</CenterContent>
						<CenterContent isTemplate="1">
							<hdl_Title><![CDATA[Darwin]]></hdl_Title>
							<img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/Darwin_botanic_thumb.jpg" alt="Darwin, NT">]]></img_MainImage>
							<stf_Caption><![CDATA[Darwin, NT]]></stf_Caption>
							<anc_link><![CDATA[]]>
							</anc_link>
							<txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[There are lots of lush tropical gardens to wander through in Darwin. Explore monsoon forests, mangroves and open woodlands in the George Brown Darwin Botanic Gardens, created in the 1870s to supplement the city’s food supply. The rainforest gully has a waterfall, ponds and around 400 species of cycads and palm trees. See exotic flora such as orchids and bromeliads and learn about the use of traditional Aboriginal plants on the signposted walk. Along Darwin’s coast sits Casuarina Coastal Reserve, where you can swim from white beaches and discover sacred Aboriginal sites. Spot birds in the monsoon forest and swim and fish from crystal-clear swimming holes in Berry Springs Nature Park.]]>
							</txt_Information>
						</CenterContent>
						<CenterContent isTemplate="1">
							<hdl_Title><![CDATA[Canberra]]></hdl_Title>
							<img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/Canberra_botanic_garden_thumb.jpg" alt="Canberra, ACT">]]></img_MainImage>
							<stf_Caption><![CDATA[Canberra, ACT]]></stf_Caption>
							<anc_link><![CDATA[]]>
							</anc_link>
							<txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[Gardens were all part of the plan in Canberra, our very own ‘bush capital’.&nbsp; In the Australian National Botanic Gardens, you’ll find a cool rainforest gully, the living fossil of the Wollemi Pine, mallee shrublands and a eucalypt lawn, all five minutes from the CBD. The city also has 27 separate native bushland and grassland reserves as part of Canberra Nature Park. Hike through the bushland around Black Mountain, which has spectacular views over the city and is rife with bright wildflowers in spring and early summer. Other areas to explore include Jerrabomberra Wetlands, Remembrance Nature Park, Black Mountain, Mulligans Flat, The Pinnacle and Mt Ainslie.]]>
							</txt_Information>
						</CenterContent>
						<CenterContent isTemplate="1">
							<hdl_Title><![CDATA[Hobart]]></hdl_Title>
							<img_MainImage><![CDATA[<img src="/contentimages/hobart_botanic_gardens_thumb.jpg" alt="Hobart, TAS">]]></img_MainImage>
							<stf_Caption><![CDATA[Hobart, TAS]]></stf_Caption>
							<anc_link><![CDATA[]]>
							</anc_link>
							<txt_Information>
                        <![CDATA[A world of plants awaits you in the Royal Tasmanian Botanical Gardens, which rambles across 13 green hectares on the banks of the Derwent River. Join a guided tour for an expert insight into the Japanese garden, traditional herb garden and the southern hemisphere’s largest public conifer collection. See rare plants from Macquarie Island in the sub-Antarctic plant house, then visit more exotic eco-systems in the internally-heated Arthurs Wall. In spring the gardens come alive with the colours of the annual Tasmanian Tulip Festival. Outside Hobart, spilling down to North West Bay, is Inverawe Native Gardens, where poems and sculptures adorn a winding path past the native vegetation.]]>
							</txt_Information>
						</CenterContent>
					</con_CenterContent>
				</TopCategoryHighlights>
			</con_Body>
		</SubPageLayout>
	</con_Body>
	<lst_Subpages>
	</lst_Subpages>
</ConsumerBaseFoundation>